<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Bollywood-Classic-RU">
    <display-name>Bollywood Classic</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Bollywood-Classic-RU.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505000409 +0500" stop="20260505030754 +0500">
    <title>Pakhandi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Circumstances separate two brothers in their childhood. However, they reunite in their adulthood after a series of events.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505030754 +0500" stop="20260505064512 +0500">
    <title>Pratigyabadh</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Shankar grows up to become the right hand man of a gangster. His goal in life is to take revenge on the moneylender who left his family homeless and a truck driver who molested and killed his mother.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505064512 +0500" stop="20260505101454 +0500">
    <title>Zamana</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ravi and Vinod's father is killed by a gangster for developing a photo that depicts a crime scene. Ravi, a criminal, and Vinod, a police officer, decide to exact revenge on their father's murderer.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505101454 +0500" stop="20260505135524 +0500">
    <title>Be-Reham</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kumar Anand, an honest police officer, gets into trouble after he accidentally kills a gangster at his ex-lover Mala's house.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505135524 +0500" stop="20260505170218 +0500">
    <title>Tyagi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Village-based Shankar makes his living as a farmer, living with his dad, and two brothers. He borrows money to fund his brothers education in the city. But once in the city they meet with the underworld and begin to carry on illegal activities.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505170218 +0500" stop="20260505194104 +0500">
    <title>Qatil</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kumar's father is a public prosecutor and a strong advocate of the death penalty. Kumar, who opposes his father's views, decides to teach his father a lesson by implicating himself in a murder case.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505194104 +0500" stop="20260505225047 +0500">
    <title>Resham Ki Dori</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ajit, an orphan, loves his younger sister, Rajjo, and plans on getting her married into a respectable family. Things change when he tries to save her from a sexual assault.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505225047 +0500" stop="20260506014851 +0500">
    <title>Sadhna</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Mohan, a professor, is nagged by his mother to get married. In a bid to pacify her, he comes up with a plan to fake a marriage with a woman named Rajani, unaware of her true identity.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506014851 +0500" stop="20260506052036 +0500">
    <title>Sagar Sangam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Upon growing to be a criminal, Gopi's conviction sends him to Devipur where he uncovers the truth about his traumatic childhood and sets off to seek revenge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506052036 +0500" stop="20260506084056 +0500">
    <title>Bandhan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A wastrel father and his righteous son have a showdown and the son is charged with his father's murder. Court-room drama follows as friends and family aren't sure whom to believe and testify for.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506084056 +0500" stop="20260506114834 +0500">
    <title>Gair</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>An abandoned child raised by a wealthy household takes over the family business. However, he is resented by their natural son who, fueled by a bitter uncle, tries his best to make him lose face.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506114834 +0500" stop="20260506150037 +0500">
    <title>Sunghursh</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bhawani Prasad, a criminal who poses as a holy man and is estranged from his wife and son, forcibly takes his grandson, Kundan, with him to follow in his footsteps.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506150037 +0500" stop="20260506184108 +0500">
    <title>Dastaan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vishnu, a reputed judge, is assumed to be Anil, an absconding murderer. However, he decides to travel to Anil's home town and unravel the mystery behind his lookalike's existence.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506184108 +0500" stop="20260506213216 +0500">
    <title>Aakhri Kasam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jagga, a labourer, loses both his wife and son after an attack by an evil zamindar. He abducts one of the zamindar's sons, raises him as a good person and pits him against his father to get revenge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506213216 +0500" stop="20260507004142 +0500">
    <title>Yakeen 1969</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rajesh, a scientist, works with the Indian Government on a confidential research project. He is forced to deal with miscreants who wish to steal his research.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507004142 +0500" stop="20260507040123 +0500">
    <title>Zara Si Zindagi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>An MA in philosophy, Raja arrives in Delhi to look for employment and comes across Kusum, a struggling stage actress. They both face hardships in order to make a living.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>