<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Bollywood-Classic-RU">
    <display-name>Bollywood Classic</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Bollywood-Classic-RU.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506014851 +0500" stop="20260506052036 +0500">
    <title>Sagar Sangam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Upon growing to be a criminal, Gopi's conviction sends him to Devipur where he uncovers the truth about his traumatic childhood and sets off to seek revenge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506052036 +0500" stop="20260506084056 +0500">
    <title>Bandhan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A wastrel father and his righteous son have a showdown and the son is charged with his father's murder. Court-room drama follows as friends and family aren't sure whom to believe and testify for.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506084056 +0500" stop="20260506114834 +0500">
    <title>Gair</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>An abandoned child raised by a wealthy household takes over the family business. However, he is resented by their natural son who, fueled by a bitter uncle, tries his best to make him lose face.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506114834 +0500" stop="20260506150037 +0500">
    <title>Sunghursh</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bhawani Prasad, a criminal who poses as a holy man and is estranged from his wife and son, forcibly takes his grandson, Kundan, with him to follow in his footsteps.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506150037 +0500" stop="20260506184108 +0500">
    <title>Dastaan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vishnu, a reputed judge, is assumed to be Anil, an absconding murderer. However, he decides to travel to Anil's home town and unravel the mystery behind his lookalike's existence.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506184108 +0500" stop="20260506213216 +0500">
    <title>Aakhri Kasam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jagga, a labourer, loses both his wife and son after an attack by an evil zamindar. He abducts one of the zamindar's sons, raises him as a good person and pits him against his father to get revenge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260506213216 +0500" stop="20260507004142 +0500">
    <title>Yakeen 1969</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rajesh, a scientist, works with the Indian Government on a confidential research project. He is forced to deal with miscreants who wish to steal his research.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507004142 +0500" stop="20260507040123 +0500">
    <title>Zara Si Zindagi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>An MA in philosophy, Raja arrives in Delhi to look for employment and comes across Kusum, a struggling stage actress. They both face hardships in order to make a living.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507040123 +0500" stop="20260507062646 +0500">
    <title>Train to Pakistan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The people of Mano Majra, a village on the Indo-Pak border, live in harmony. However, things change when a train arrives from Pakistan containing the dead bodies of the people coming to India.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507062646 +0500" stop="20260507095627 +0500">
    <title>Zamana</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ravi and Vinod's father is killed by a gangster for developing a photo that depicts a crime scene. Ravi, a criminal, and Vinod, a police officer, decide to exact revenge on their father's murderer.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507095627 +0500" stop="20260507133652 +0500">
    <title>Be-Reham</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kumar Anand, an honest police officer, gets into trouble after he accidentally kills a gangster at his ex-lover Mala's house.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507133652 +0500" stop="20260507161330 +0500">
    <title>Naalayak</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Laxman has always been the black sheep of the family. He swindles his brother’s money to impress a girl.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507161330 +0500" stop="20260507194651 +0500">
    <title>Aadmi Aur Insaan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jai and Munish's friendship is ruined when both of them fall in love with the same girl, Meena. Things take a turn when Munish finds out Jai was involved in the case of a faulty railway bridge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507194651 +0500" stop="20260507222703 +0500">
    <title>Besharam 1978</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Digvijay Singh falsely implicates Mayor Ramchandra in a corruption case, which leads him to commit suicide. Years later, Ramchandra's son Ram Kumar returns to teach Digvijay a lesson.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260507222703 +0500" stop="20260508012245 +0500">
    <title>The Burning Train</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>An engineer's dream of making the perfect train is given hope when the company commissions his prototype. He hopes to make up for all this sacrifice with the train's triumphant inaugural journey. However an embittered fellow employee has other ideas.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260508012245 +0500" stop="20260508034029 +0500">
    <title>Chhoti Si Baat</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Arun, a timid young man, falls in love with Prabha but is too afraid to share his feelings with her. Things take a turn when another man attempts to woo Prabha.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>