<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Bollywood-Classic-RU">
    <display-name>Bollywood Classic</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Bollywood-Classic-RU.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260504015755 +0500" stop="20260504053831 +0500">
    <title>Dastaan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vishnu, a reputed judge, is assumed to be Anil, an absconding murderer. However, he decides to travel to Anil's home town and unravel the mystery behind his lookalike's existence.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260504053831 +0500" stop="20260504084814 +0500">
    <title>Resham Ki Dori</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ajit, an orphan, loves his younger sister, Rajjo, and plans on getting her married into a respectable family. Things change when he tries to save her from a sexual assault.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260504084814 +0500" stop="20260504112535 +0500">
    <title>Kanoon 1960</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A lawyer decides to defend a man who has been falsely accused of murder as he knows the real killer is his future father-in-law, who is also the judge presiding over the case.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260504112535 +0500" stop="20260504143500 +0500">
    <title>Yakeen 1969</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rajesh, a scientist, works with the Indian Government on a confidential research project. He is forced to deal with miscreants who wish to steal his research.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260504143500 +0500" stop="20260504172006 +0500">
    <title>Khoon Ka Karz</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Raised by Savitri, orphans Kishan and Arjun grow up to become gangsters. Karan, her another foster child shows them the right path.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260504172006 +0500" stop="20260504202857 +0500">
    <title>Ustadon Ke Ustad</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vishwanath and Jaikishan are two thieves and good friends. When they try to lead an honest life for the sake of their women, Pukhraj turns them against each other and the two become sworn enemies.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260504202857 +0500" stop="20260505000409 +0500">
    <title>Waqt Ki Deewar</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two brothers are separated after their mother is raped and commits suicide. One turns into a criminal and he unknowingly works for the same rapist, whereas the other becomes a policeman.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505000409 +0500" stop="20260505030754 +0500">
    <title>Pakhandi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Circumstances separate two brothers in their childhood. However, they reunite in their adulthood after a series of events.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505030754 +0500" stop="20260505064512 +0500">
    <title>Pratigyabadh</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Shankar grows up to become the right hand man of a gangster. His goal in life is to take revenge on the moneylender who left his family homeless and a truck driver who molested and killed his mother.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505064512 +0500" stop="20260505101454 +0500">
    <title>Zamana</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ravi and Vinod's father is killed by a gangster for developing a photo that depicts a crime scene. Ravi, a criminal, and Vinod, a police officer, decide to exact revenge on their father's murderer.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505101454 +0500" stop="20260505135524 +0500">
    <title>Be-Reham</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kumar Anand, an honest police officer, gets into trouble after he accidentally kills a gangster at his ex-lover Mala's house.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505135524 +0500" stop="20260505170218 +0500">
    <title>Tyagi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Village-based Shankar makes his living as a farmer, living with his dad, and two brothers. He borrows money to fund his brothers education in the city. But once in the city they meet with the underworld and begin to carry on illegal activities.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505170218 +0500" stop="20260505194104 +0500">
    <title>Qatil</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kumar's father is a public prosecutor and a strong advocate of the death penalty. Kumar, who opposes his father's views, decides to teach his father a lesson by implicating himself in a murder case.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505194104 +0500" stop="20260505225047 +0500">
    <title>Resham Ki Dori</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ajit, an orphan, loves his younger sister, Rajjo, and plans on getting her married into a respectable family. Things change when he tries to save her from a sexual assault.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260505225047 +0500" stop="20260506014851 +0500">
    <title>Sadhna</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Mohan, a professor, is nagged by his mother to get married. In a bid to pacify her, he comes up with a plan to fake a marriage with a woman named Rajani, unaware of her true identity.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>