<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504060000 +0500" stop="20260504070500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504070500 +0500" stop="20260504090000 +0500">
    <title>Blue Valentine</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dean grew up in a broken home.He never planned to build a lasting relationship until he met Cindy, with whom he fell in love at first sight.When, after a few weeks of dating, it turns out that the girl is expecting another man's child, she makes the difficult decision to get married.The couple tries to create a happy family, but over time they begin to face a serious crisis.The infatuation disappears, and everyday problems make it difficult for them to find understanding.Dean abuses alcohol and does simple physical work, unable to guarantee his wife real stability and support.The couple falls into conflicts more and more often.However, he still tries to rebuild his relationships for the sake of little Frankie.This perfectly portrayed study of the breakdown of a relationship was nominated for the Grand Jury Prize at the Sundance Film Festival.The role of Michelle Williams was nominated for an Oscar and a Golden Globe.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Derek Cianfrance</director>
      <actor>Dean - Ryan Gosling</actor>
      <actor>Cindy - Michelle Williams</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - John Doman</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Mike Vogel</actor>
      <actor>Frankie - Faith Wladyka</actor>
      <actor>Marshall - Marshall Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Gramma - Jen Jones</actor>
      <actor>Glenda - Maryann Plunkett</actor>
      <actor>Jamie - James Benatti</actor>
      <actor>Jo - Barbara Troy</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504090000 +0500" stop="20260504103500 +0500">
    <title>Detective Monk: One last thing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brilliant detective Adrian Monk (Tony Shalhoub) is going through difficult times.The contract to publish his autobiography was canceled, and the coronavirus pandemic intensified his fears and phobias.All this makes the master of deduction start thinking about ending his life and joining his beloved Truda.He is jolted out of his torpor by the tragedy that befalls his stepdaughter Molly (Caitlin McGee).The girl is getting ready to marry journalist Griffin Briggs (Austin Scott).However, her fiancé dies while bungee jumping.Molly is convinced that it was not an accident, but a carefully planned murder.The trail leads to the influential billionaire Rick Eden (James Purefoy).Retired Captain Stottlemeyer (Ted Levine) now works for the rich man as his security chief.Monk is assisted in the investigation by former assistant and now real estate agent Natalie Teeger (Traylor Howard) and Randy Disher (Jason Gray-Stanford), now the New Jersey police commissioner.Continuation of the cult series.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Randy Zisk</director>
      <actor>Adrian Monk - Tony Shalhoub</actor>
      <actor>Natalie Teeger - Traylor Howard</actor>
      <actor>Randy Disher - Jason Gray-Stanford</actor>
      <actor>Trudy Monk - Melora Hardin</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Neven Bell - Hector Elizondo</actor>
      <actor>Stottlemeyer - Ted Levine</actor>
      <actor>Rick Eden - James Purefoy</actor>
      <actor>Molly Evans - Caitlin McGee</actor>
      <actor>Griffin Briggs - Austin Scott</actor>
      <actor>Skyler - Emma Ishta</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504103500 +0500" stop="20260504121000 +0500">
    <title>Jane Austen Wrecked My Life</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Agathe, a shy employee of the Shakespeare \u0026 Co. bookstore.in Paris, dreams of romantic love like in a Jane Austen novel and success as a writer.An invitation to England gives her a chance to change her fate.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Laura Piani</director>
      <actor>Agathe Robinson - Camille Rutherford</actor>
      <actor>Félix - Pablo Pauly</actor>
      <actor>Oliver - Charlie Anson</actor>
      <actor>Chéryl - Annabelle Lengronne</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Liz Crowther</actor>
      <actor>Todd - Alan Fairbairn</actor>
      <actor>Olympia - Lola Peploe</actor>
      <actor>Mona - Alice Butaud</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Roman Angel</actor>
      <actor>Rosemarie - Laurence Pierre</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504121000 +0500" stop="20260504135500 +0500">
    <title>Maid in Manhattan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>New York.Divorcee Marisa Ventura (Jennifer Lopez) raises her son alone.She works as a maid at the luxurious Beresford Hotel in Manhattan.While cleaning the apartment of aristocrat Caroline Lane (Natasha Richardson), the woman tries on her elegant outfit, in which she looks exceptionally nice.Another hotel guest sees her so changed.He is lawyer Christopher Matthew (Ralph Fiennes), running for parliament.He takes Marisa as a person of a similar social status to himself.They go for a walk together and then eat dinner together.The woman cannot bring herself to correct the mistake, especially since she likes Christopher.However, it is not known how the future senator will react to the fact that his chosen one is an ordinary girl from the Bronx... The luxurious Beresford hotel, where the main character of the film works, is in fact the famous Waldorf-Astoria on Park Avenue.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Wayne Wang</director>
      <actor>Marisa Ventura - Jennifer Lopez</actor>
      <actor>Christopher 'Chris' Marshall, N.Y. Assemblyman - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Caroline Lane - Natasha Richardson</actor>
      <actor>Jerry Siegel - Stanley Tucci</actor>
      <actor>Ty Ventura - Tyler Posey</actor>
      <actor>Paula Burns - Frances Conroy</actor>
      <actor>John Bextrum, Personnel Manager - Chris Eigeman</actor>
      <actor>Rachel Hoffberg - Amy Sedaris</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Kehoe, Maid - Marissa Matrone</actor>
      <actor>Veronica Ventura - Priscilla Lopez</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504135500 +0500" stop="20260504154000 +0500">
    <title>Death Of A Comedian</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Argentine actor Juan Debré (Diego Peretti) receives a disturbing diagnosis at the peak of his career.He escapes to Belgium to immerse himself in his own, safe reality.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Beltramino</director>
      <director>Diego Peretti</director>
      <actor>Lena - Malena Villa</actor>
      <actor>Steve Joyce - Chuck Hargrove</actor>
      <actor>Capitán Busch - Heinz K. Krattiger</actor>
      <actor>Head of Security - Carl-Philipp Wengler</actor>
      <actor>Doyle - Eric Jean Bier</actor>
      <actor>Bonnie - Marioska Fabián Nunez</actor>
      <actor>Waiter in Brussels city - Andrés Guillín</actor>
      <actor>Amal - Agustín Matías Kim</actor>
      <actor>Passenger at the tram stop - Elodie Barthels</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504154000 +0500" stop="20260504173000 +0500">
    <title>Sir Alex Ferguson: Never Give In</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The life story of one of the greatest managers in the history of football.Directed by Jason Ferguson, the film conveys a deeply personal portrayal of his father, Sir Alex Ferguson.He grew up in Glasgow in a working-class family.In his youth he played for Scottish clubs, including Rangers.He then moved into the Aberdeen management team and continued to rise through the ranks.Ferguson shares all the details of his life while undergoing rehabilitation after suffering a cerebral hemorrhage.At the same time, he surprises with his excellent memory, devoting most of his attention to the victorious 26 years of managing Manchester United.He lists every trophy, every defeat and every player.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jason Ferguson</director>
      <actor>Self - Eric Cantona</actor>
      <actor>Self - Alex Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Ryan Giggs</actor>
      <actor>Self - Jason Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Mark Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Gordon Strachan</actor>
      <actor>Self - Cathy Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Archie Knox</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504173000 +0500" stop="20260504193500 +0500">
    <title>The Karate Kid</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Teenage Daniel (Ralph Macchio) moves with his mother, Lucille (Randee Heller), from New Jersey to Los Angeles.He becomes friends with his peer Tommy (Rob Garrison).During a beach party, the boy meets a nice blonde, Ali (Elisabeth Shue).The two immediately take a liking to each other, which does not please her ex-boyfriend, Johnny (William Zabka).As an excellent karateka, he easily teaches his rival a lesson.Humiliated, Daniel also decides to start training eastern martial arts to defeat the enemy.Unfortunately, he cannot join the local club because Johnny and his equally unpleasant and brutal friends practice there.One evening, Daniel is attacked by them again.He is saved from trouble by an old man, Mr. Miyagi (Noriyuki "Pat" Morita), who turns out to be a master of eastern martial arts.From then on, the teenager learns the secrets of karate under his watchful eye.The Japanese teaches him not only the fighting style, but also a lot about life... A perfect film for karate lovers.For his role as Master Noriyuki "Pat" Morita, he received an Oscar nomination for Best Supporting Actor and a Golden Globe nomination.Director of photography John G. Avildsen is known as the creator of the legendary "Rocky" from 1976 with Sylvester Stallone.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John G. Avildsen</director>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Kesuke Miyagi - Noriyuki Pat Morita</actor>
      <actor>Ali Mills - Elisabeth Shue</actor>
      <actor>John Kreese Cobra Kai Sensei - Martin Kove</actor>
      <actor>Lucille Larusso - Randee Heller</actor>
      <actor>Johnny Lawrence - William Zabka</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Ron Thomas</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Rob Garrison</actor>
      <actor>Dutch - Chad McQueen</actor>
      <actor>Jimmy - Tony O'Dell</actor>
    </credits><date>1984</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504193500 +0500" stop="20260504211000 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brave Po opens a new chapter in his life - he is to become the spiritual leader of the Valley of Peace.He's trying to get used to his new role.In addition, the voracious bear must find a daredevil who will replace him as the Dragon Warrior.Not everything goes according to plan.This time, China's security is threatened by Chameleon, who wields black magic and can take on any form and take over the abilities of old masters.With the help of a smart vixen and former thief, Zhen, the panda bear must face her.But they need allies to defeat the shape-shifting witch and the sinister army behind her.The time of a merciless fight is inevitably approaching... The voices of the characters include, among others:Marcin Hycnar, Jan Peszek, Wiktor Zborowski and Julia Chatys.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Mitchell</director>
      <director>Stephanie Stine</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504211000 +0500" stop="20260504230000 +0500">
    <title>We're the Millers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Small-time marijuana dealer David Clark tries to help teenagers living in his neighborhood.He is attacked by three homeless punks and robbed of his goods and cash.As a result, he becomes indebted to his supplier, Brad Gurdlinger.To repay the debt, he must import the latest batch of stimulants from Mexico.To conceal himself, he arranges helpers to pretend to be his immediate family going on holiday with him.So David's neighbors go on the road with him: cynical stripper Rose O'Reilly, the drug dealer's would-be client, the dim-witted Kenny Rossmore, and the smart, street-savvy teenager Casey Mathis.A laugh-out-loud action movie full of well-acted episodes and indecent gags.This is another joint project of Jason Sudeikis and Jennifer Aniston, after the comedies "Get Your Ex" and "Horrible Bosses".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rawson Marshall Thurber</director>
      <actor>Rose O'Reilly - Jennifer Aniston</actor>
      <actor>David Clark - Jason Sudeikis</actor>
      <actor>Casey Mathis - Emma Roberts</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Rossmore - Will Poulter</actor>
      <actor>Brad Gurdlinger - Ed Helms</actor>
      <actor>Don Fitzgerald - Nick Offerman</actor>
      <actor>Edie Fitzgerald - Kathryn Hahn</actor>
      <actor>Melissa Fitzgerald - Molly C. Quinn</actor>
      <actor>Pablo Chacon - Tomer Sisley</actor>
      <actor>One-Eye - Matthew Willig</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504230000 +0500" stop="20260505000000 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505000000 +0500" stop="20260505003000 +0500">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greg Russo (Steve Carell) has written a best-selling series of books, and readers identify him with his literary hero nicknamed Rooster.A famous writer comes to the university campus to support his daughter (Charly Clive) who is going through a marital crisis in a difficult moment.Her partner has just left her for a student, which everyone knows perfectly well.The situation is further complicated by scandals involving a woman who are the subject of gossip in the academic community.The father declares help, but his presence quickly reveals old conflicts and uncomfortable topics, instead of bringing the expected solution.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Lawrence</director>
      <director>Matt Tarses</director>
      <actor>Greg Russo - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Walter Mann - John C. McGinley</actor>
      <actor>Cristle - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Maximo Salas</actor>
      <actor>Spooner - Evan Jachelski</actor>
      <actor>George - Xavier Beloved</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505003000 +0500" stop="20260505010500 +0500">
    <title>Comeback 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Valerie Cherish, a once popular television actress, rose to fame as a sitcom star.After many years, he wants to return to the small screen at all costs.He decides to take part in a new reality show.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Patrick King</director>
      <actor>Valerie Cherish - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Jane Benson - Laura Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mark Berman - Damian Young</actor>
      <actor>Billy Stanton - Dan Bucatinsky</actor>
      <actor>Juna Millken - Malin Akerman</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505010500 +0500" stop="20260505024500 +0500">
    <title>Blue Moon</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1943. The legendary lyricist Lorenz Hart (Ethan Hawke), co-author of such hits as "Blue Moon" and "My Funny Valentine", spends the night from March 31 to April 1 in Sardi's bar.In the company of friends, including his muse Elizabeth Weiland (Margaret Qualley), he struggles with wounded pride and shaken self-confidence.At this time, his former long-time collaborator Richard Rodgers (Andrew Scott) celebrates the premiere of his musical entitled"Oklahoma!", which he wrote with Oscar Hammerstein II (Simon Delaney).Two Oscar nominations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard Linklater</director>
      <actor>Lorenz Hart - Ethan Hawke</actor>
      <actor>Elizabeth Weiland - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Eddie - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Richard Rodgers - Andrew Scott</actor>
      <actor>E.B. 'Andy' White - Patrick Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Morty Rifkin - Jonah Lees</actor>
      <actor>Oscar Hammerstein - Simon Delaney</actor>
      <actor>Sven - Giles Surridge</actor>
      <actor>Stevie Sondheim - Cillian Sullivan</actor>
      <actor>Lawrence Langner - Michael James Ford</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505024500 +0500" stop="20260505045000 +0500">
    <title>Eine Million Minuten</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Spouses Vera (Karoline Herfurth) and Wolf (Tom Schilling) Küper, parents of Nina (Pola Friedrichs) and Simon (Piet Levi Busch), have difficulty dividing their time between work and household duties.The bond that united them years ago is weakening.Wolf focuses on his professional career, and Vera, confined to her four walls, is fed up with loneliness and having to replace her children's fathers.The family's world is ruined by the daughter's disastrous medical diagnosis.Wolf recalls that the girl's greatest wish was to spend a million minutes solely on pleasure.The Küpers decide to make her dream come true.Together they set off on a lifelong journey that leads through exotic regions of the world.They get to know new places and foreign cultures, and decide what their future will look like.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christopher Doll</director>
      <actor>Wolf Küper - Tom Schilling</actor>
      <actor>Vera Küper - Karoline Herfurth</actor>
      <actor>Regina Küper - Ulrike Kriener</actor>
      <actor>Nina Küper - Pola Friedrichs</actor>
      <actor>Simon Küper - Piet Levi Busch</actor>
      <actor>Werner Küper - Joachim Król</actor>
      <actor>Bassem Ibn 'Ben' Hamoud - Hassan Akkouch</actor>
      <actor>Claudia Herhenrath - Anneke Kim Sarnau</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Finkelbach - Godehard Giese</actor>
      <actor>Ergotherapeutin - Sara Fuchs</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505045000 +0500" stop="20260505063000 +0500">
    <title>One to One: John &amp; Yoko</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The story of a famous couple of artists, focusing on the One to One charity concert that took place at Madison Square Garden on August 30, 1972.From 1971, John Lennon and Yoko Ono lived in New York, in Greenwich Village, for 18 months.Their then apartment was reconstructed for the film.Private film, photo and music archives of artists and friends were also used, as well as FBI tapes to show their fate and the company they kept in: from Allen Ginsberg to Jerry Rubin and activist AJ Weberman.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kevin Macdonald</director>
      <director>Sam Rice-Edwards</director>
      <actor>Self - John Lennon</actor>
      <actor>Self - Yoko Ono</actor>
      <actor>Themselves - The Plastic Ono Elephants Memory Band</actor>
      <actor>Self - Jerry Rubin</actor>
      <actor>Self - Andy Warhol</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505063000 +0500" stop="20260505082000 +0500">
    <title>Elysium</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 2154. Los Angeles resembles a landfill.People are struggling to survive on a devastated Earth, full of violence and poverty.Rich people live on the Elysium space station.Among the technologies available to them are medical capsules that cure diseases.One day, Max Da Costa, who lives in the slums, is heavily irradiated as a result of an accident at a factory.The dose is lethal.He has five days left.He realizes that only the capsule can save him.So he visits the smuggler Spider, hoping that thanks to him he will get to Elysium.The man promises help on the condition that he will kidnap the wealthy Carlyle for him.The dying Da Costa's body is enhanced with new technology.He soon comes into possession of secret information that could destroy the current order.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Neill Blomkamp</director>
      <actor>Max - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Delacourt - Jodie Foster</actor>
      <actor>Kruger - Sharlto Copley</actor>
      <actor>Frey - Alice Braga</actor>
      <actor>Julio - Diego Luna</actor>
      <actor>Spider - Wagner Moura</actor>
      <actor>John Carlyle - William Fichtner</actor>
      <actor>Drake - Brandon Auret</actor>
      <actor>Crowe - Josh Blacker</actor>
      <actor>Matilda - Emma Tremblay</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Dramat Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505082000 +0500" stop="20260505090000 +0500">
    <title>The Devil Is Busy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The everyday life of the head of security at an abortion clinic in Atlanta.A deeply religious believer, Tracy begins each workday with prayer.Her commitment to defending women's rights does not compromise.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Geeta Gandbhir</director>
      <director>Christalyn Hampton</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505090000 +0500" stop="20260505093000 +0500">
    <title>Monsters vs Aliens: Mutant Pumpkins from Outer Space</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Susan Murphy and a group of friendly monsters undertake another mission.Just before Halloween, a trace of aliens was found in the girl's hometown.Everything looked normal though.Unexpectedly, on the day of the holiday, innocent-looking pumpkin lanterns reveal their true colors.It turns out to be an invasion of aliens who plan to conquer Earth.Susan, called Ginormica, and a team of "freaks of nature" start a fight against mutated pumpkins... In the Polish language version, the characters provided their voices, among others:Barbara Kałużna, Wojciech Paszkowski and Grzegorz Pawlak.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Ramsey</director>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505093000 +0500" stop="20260505095500 +0500">
    <title>Secrets of the Furious Five</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After defeating Tai Lung, Po the panda gains the title of Dragon Warrior.Master Shifu gives the bear another task - to teach kung fu.Enthusiastic bunnies become new adepts of the eastern martial art.In addition to improving his technique, Po must instill in the children the philosophy of kung-fu and character traits such as courage, self-confidence and patience.To achieve the goal, he tells them stories from the past of great warriors - the Crane, the Viper, the Tigress, the Monkey and the Mantis... In the Polish language version, they lent their voices to characters including:Marcin Hycnar (Po) and Jan Peszek (Shifu).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Raman Hui</director>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505095500 +0500" stop="20260505113500 +0500">
    <title>Sarah Bernhardt, la divine</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The beginning of the 20th century.The outstanding French actress Sarah Bernhardt (Sandrine Kiberlain) is considered one of the most important artists of her time and has the status of an international star.Her admirers include Oscar Wilde, Alfons Mucha and Victor Hugo.Her talent and extraordinary charisma, as well as her courage and extravagant lifestyle are widely admired.The actress disrupted social norms and shocked her contemporaries with her unusual preferences and numerous love affairs.She was a declared opponent of anti-Semitism.Fate connected her most closely with the actor Lucien Guitry (Laurent Lafitte) and the painter Louise Abbéma (Amira Casar).Since her fateful fall on stage in 1905 in Rio de Janeiro, Divine Sarah has been struggling with terrible knee pain, which over the years has made it impossible for her to move.In order to be able to perform, after a decade, the actress makes a dramatic decision.Full of passion and inner strength, the artist will forever be remembered in the history of art and culture.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Guillaume Nicloux</director>
      <actor>Sarah Bernhardt - Sandrine Kiberlain</actor>
      <actor>Lucien Guitry - Laurent Lafitte</actor>
      <actor>Louise Abbéma - Amira Casar</actor>
      <actor>Suzanne - Pauline Etienne</actor>
      <actor>Charlotte Lyses - Mathilde Ollivier</actor>
      <actor>Pitou - Laurent Stocker</actor>
      <actor>Maurice Bernhardt - Grégoire Leprince-Ringuet</actor>
      <actor>Georges Clairin - Clément Hervieu-Léger</actor>
      <actor>Samuel Pozzi - Sébastien Pouderoux</actor>
      <actor>Emile Zola - Arthur Igual</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505113500 +0500" stop="20260505130000 +0500">
    <title>A Carpenter Christmas Romance</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Writer Andrea returns to her family farm in Wildwood just before the holidays.She begins an affair with her ex-boyfriend Seth, who was employed in the crew renovating the town after the recent fire.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Helgren</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505130000 +0500" stop="20260505144000 +0500">
    <title>By sleeping with others</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lainey and Jake had only slept together once, but it was the first and most important time in their lives.But then the lovers parted ways.A few years later, they accidentally bump into each other...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Leslye Headland</director>
      <actor>Lainey - Alison Brie</actor>
      <actor>Jake - Jason Sudeikis</actor>
      <actor>R.A. - Jordan Carlos</actor>
      <actor>Hannah - Margarita Levieva</actor>
      <actor>Helmet Kid - Charles Cain</actor>
      <actor>Sam - Adam Brody</actor>
      <actor>Attentive Waiter - Michael Cyril Creighton</actor>
      <actor>SLAA Speaker - Billy Eichner</actor>
      <actor>Xander - Jason Mantzoukas</actor>
      <actor>Thea - Margaret Odette</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505144000 +0500" stop="20260505154500 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E9</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505154500 +0500" stop="20260505173000 +0500">
    <title>Focus</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nicky Spurgeon is a calculating fraud.The model's appearance and ability to keep cool make him a master criminal.He is able to win people over, but he does it to take advantage of them.One day, in a restaurant, he meets a fair-haired beauty, Jess Barrett, whose ambition is to pursue a criminal career.He becomes her mentor.Over time, they both realize that they have much more in common than the relationship of master and disciple.However, they live in a world where there is no place for love.Spurgeon ends this relationship.Three years pass.Nicky is in Buenos Aires, where he works for the owner of a car racing team, Rafael Garrigi.He meets his former lover here.Aware of her strengths, the femme fatale has one goal - to take revenge for the way she was once treated.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Glenn Ficarra</director>
      <director>John Requa</director>
      <actor>Nicky - Will Smith</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Margot Robbie</actor>
      <actor>Farhad - Adrian Martinez</actor>
      <actor>Owens - Gerald McRaney</actor>
      <actor>Garriga - Rodrigo Santoro</actor>
      <actor>Liyuan - BD Wong</actor>
      <actor>Horst - Brennan Brown</actor>
      <actor>McEwen - Robert Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Gordon - Dotan Bonen</actor>
      <actor>Gareth - Griff Furst</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505173000 +0500" stop="20260505194500 +0500">
    <title>The Karate Kid</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sherry Parker (Taraji P. Henson) is offered a job in Beijing.He goes there with his son Dre (Jaden Smith).The boy cannot acclimatize to the new surroundings.For this reason, he often comes into conflict with his school friends.He is also persecuted by them.One day, Dre meets Mr. Han (Jackie Chan), the caretaker of the building where he lives with his mother.The man decides to teach the boy martial arts so that he can defend himself against his peers who bully him.Many hours of training create a unique bond between them, much stronger than ordinary teacher-student relationships.The film's script loosely refers to John G. Avildsen's work from 1984.The production received nominations for the Teen and People's Choice awards, Czarny Repules and the Golden Popcorn award.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Harald Zwart</director>
      <actor>Dre Parker - Jaden Smith</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Sherry Parker - Taraji P. Henson</actor>
      <actor>Meiying - Wenwen Han</actor>
      <actor>Master Li - Rongguang Yu</actor>
      <actor>Meiying's Dad - Zhensu Wu</actor>
      <actor>Meiying's Mom - Zhiheng Wang</actor>
      <actor>Cheng - Zhenwei Wang</actor>
      <actor>Dre's Detroit Friend - Jared Minns</actor>
      <actor>Liang - Shijia Lü</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505194500 +0500" stop="20260505212500 +0500">
    <title>Silver Star</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>African American Billie (Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson) is twenty years old and a tomboy.He comes from a military family and is missing one eye.After serving her prison sentence, she discovers that her separated parents are facing eviction.He decides to prevent this at all costs.The woman decides to rob a bank, but the action ends in failure.As a result, the young criminal takes her client hostage.Pregnant Franny (Grace Van Dien) is eighteen years old and has a head open to crazy ideas.Together they escape and set off on an adventurous journey.At one point, Franny offers Billie an unexpected deal.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ruben Amar</director>
      <director>Lola Bessis</director>
      <actor>Franny - Grace Van Dien</actor>
      <actor>Billie - Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tyrone Sands - Johnath Davis</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Woodman - Getchie Argetsinger</actor>
      <actor>Shonda - Tamara Fruits</actor>
      <actor>Alice - Ekaterina Baker</actor>
      <actor>Dylan - Joey Giambattista</actor>
      <actor>William Bortschstoecker - Josh Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Clark - Amy Tribbey</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Noa Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505212500 +0500" stop="20260505230000 +0500">
    <title>Bastille Day</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>On the eve of Bastille Day, an American thief living in Paris, Michael Mason (Richard Madden), steals a bag containing a teddy bear.Not knowing that there is a bomb hidden inside the toy, he takes the money and documents and throws the rest into a trash bin in a crowded Paris metro station.A few seconds later there is a huge explosion.Four people die.City surveillance footage reveals Michael's face.The police, considering him a terrorist, start searching for him.He is stopped by CIA agent Sean Briar (Idris Elba), who is just trying to find his way back to work after returning from Iraq.He brings the suspect to a secret interrogation room.Michael explains the misunderstanding and convinces that someone else is behind the attack.He and Sean have 24 hours to find the real culprits.The film was shot in 2015 and became even more relevant after the attacks in Paris.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>James Watkins</director>
      <actor>Sean Briar - Idris Elba</actor>
      <actor>Michael Mason - Richard Madden</actor>
      <actor>Zoe - Charlotte Le Bon</actor>
      <actor>Karen Dacre - Kelly Reilly</actor>
      <actor>Victor Gamieux - José Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Rafi Bertrand - Thierry Godard</actor>
      <actor>Yannick Bertrand - Vincent Londez</actor>
      <actor>Jean - Arieh Worthalter</actor>
      <actor>Christophe - Mohamed Makhtoumi</actor>
      <actor>Xavier - Théo Costa-Marini</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505230000 +0500" stop="20260505235500 +0500">
    <title>Heated Rivalry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two ice hockey players, Shane Hollander (Hudson Williams) and Ilya Rozanov (Connor Storrie), are united not only by ambition and the need for competition, but also by a magnetic attraction that neither of them fully understands.What begins as a secret romance between two debutants turns into an extraordinary love journey.Athletes spend eight years chasing fame on the ice while trying to deal with their feelings off it.They must decide whether there is room for something as fragile as love in a world of brutal competition.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Jacob Tierney</director>
      <actor>Shane Hollander - Hudson Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ilya Rozanov - Connor Storrie</actor>
      <actor>Scott Hunter - François Arnaud</actor>
      <actor>Yuna Hollander - Christina Chang</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Marleau - Franco Lo Presti</actor>
      <actor>Hayden Pike - Callan Potter</actor>
      <actor>Svetlana - Ksenia Daniela Kharlamova</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #2 - Shaun Starr</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #1 - Conor McKenna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505235500 +0500" stop="20260506005500 +0500">
    <title>Half Man</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1980s. The life of bullied teenage Niall (Mitchell Robertson) turns upside down when the son of his mother's partner, the fierce and unpredictable Ruben (Stuart Campbell), comes to live with them for a while.Even though they are not related by blood, over time they both become inseparable.However, subsequent events make them move away from each other.Three decades later, Ruben (Richard Gadd) shows up uninvited at Niall's (Jamie Bell) wedding.It soon becomes clear why he reconnected with his long-lost brother.A suggestive story about the fragility of male relationships, brotherhood, betrayal, loyalty and violence.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Ruben - Richard Gadd</actor>
      <actor>Niall - Jamie Bell</actor>
      <actor>Lori - Neve McIntosh</actor>
      <actor>Maura - Marianne McIvor</actor>
      <actor>Alby - Charlie de Melo</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Tim Downie</actor>
      <actor>Ava - Anjli Mohindra</actor>
      <actor>Butch - Tom Andrews</actor>
      <actor>Mona - Amy Manson</actor>
      <actor>Young Ruben - Stuart Campbell</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>