<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503041500 +0500" stop="20260503063500 +0500">
    <title>Kingdom of Heaven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12th century.The young blacksmith Balian (Orlando Bloom) loses his entire family in tragic circumstances.He begins to doubt the existence of God.Then he is visited by the crusader Godfrey of Ibelin (Liam Neeson), who turns out to be his father.He suggests his son learn knightly crafts.One day, Balian kills a priest in a fight.He must escape.Together with Godfrey, he sets off for Jerusalem.On the way, his father is killed by the bishop's men.Prudent King Baldwin IV (Edward Norton) and his advisor Tiberias (Jeremy Irons) strive for a peaceful solution.Thanks to them, there are no hostilities in Jerusalem.They even manage to reach a truce with the leader of the Muslims, Saladin (Ghassan Massoud).However, the ruler's conciliatory policy does not please some greedy and fanatical crusaders.Meanwhile, Balian falls in love with the king's sister, the already married princess Sibyl (Eva Green).The girl does not love her husband, Baron Guy de Lusignan (Marton Csokas).Soon the Crusaders start a war with the Muslims.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Balian - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Sybilla - Eva Green</actor>
      <actor>Tiberias - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Godfrey z Ibelinu - Liam Neeson</actor>
      <actor>Gravedigger - Martin Hancock</actor>
      <actor>Guy de Lusignan - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Reynald de Chatillon - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Stary Strażnik - Tim Barlow</actor>
      <actor>król Baldwin IV - Edward Norton</actor>
      <actor>Saladin - Ghassan Massoud</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503063500 +0500" stop="20260503090000 +0500">
    <title>Man on Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>American John Creasy (Denzel Washington) is a man haunted by nightmares from his past.He is a former assassin who worked for the CIA for many years.Frustrated, he avoids people and seeks solace in alcohol.Creasy comes to Mexico to visit his old friend and colleague, Rayburn (Christopher Walken).The city is currently gripped by a wave of kidnappings for ransom.Rich residents panic and many of them hire security guards to ensure the safety of their children.A friend finds John a job as a bodyguard for ten-year-old Pita Ramos (Dakota Fanning), the daughter of Mexican industrialist Samuel Ramos (Marc Anthony) and his American wife Lisa (Radha Mitchell).At first, Creasy has a hard time coping with the girl's presence.Over time, however, he becomes friends with her.Under its influence, he changes his attitude to life and gives up alcohol.Soon, however, little Pita is kidnapped.The desperate man does everything to save her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tony Scott</director>
      <actor>Creasy - Denzel Washington</actor>
      <actor>Rayburn - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Pita - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Samuel - Marc Anthony</actor>
      <actor>Lisa - Radha Mitchell</actor>
      <actor>Jordan - Mickey Rourke</actor>
      <actor>Manzano - Giancarlo Giannini</actor>
      <actor>Mariana - Rachel Ticotin</actor>
      <actor>Fuentes - Jesús Ochoa</actor>
      <actor>Sister Anna - Angelina Peláez</actor>
    </credits><date>2004</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503090000 +0500" stop="20260503110500 +0500">
    <title>P.S. I Love You</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the death of her husband Gerry (Gerard Butler), Holly (Hilary Swank) falls into a deep depression.On her 30th birthday, a woman receives a mysterious parcel.The cake comes with a tape with a recorded message from... Gerry.He encourages his beloved to go out and have fun with friends.After this event, new letters regularly arrived to the young widow, each ending with a declaration of love.Gerry knew how much his wife would suffer from losing him.In letters written before her death, he encourages her to take on various challenges.Thanks to her extraordinary sense of connection with the deceased, a woman in despair undergoes specific therapy and tries to start her life anew.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard LaGravenese</director>
      <actor>Holly - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Gerry - Gerard Butler</actor>
      <actor>Denise - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Gina Gershon</actor>
      <actor>John - James Marsters</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Kathy Bates</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Harry Connick Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Ciara - Nellie McKay</actor>
      <actor>William - Jeffrey Dean Morgan</actor>
      <actor>George - Christopher Whalen</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503110500 +0500" stop="20260503123500 +0500">
    <title>F+</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A family comedy aimed at teenagers.Ted (Wells Rappaport) and Josh (James Williams Jr.) are best friends and go to the Magnet School for Math and Science together.Ted is a star student, and Josh specializes in creating gadgets that they then use to prank others.After one of such antics, they are suspended.They must be careful because the next time will result in expulsion from school.The situation becomes more complicated when they fail the most important exam.The same fate befell Penny (Lily Jane), Ted's rival.Convinced that something was wrong with the test itself, they team up with a magician and a hacker to try to destroy the results during the school dance and give themselves a chance to improve.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kenny Beaumont</director>
      <actor>Terry Grimes - Randy Couture</actor>
      <actor>Gary Garrie - Tommy Davidson</actor>
      <actor>Principal Sandra Neely - Jennifer Esposito</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Barker - Ettore Ewen</actor>
      <actor>Ted Freeman - Wells Rappaport</actor>
      <actor>Penny Pritchard - Lily Jane</actor>
      <actor>Josh Barker - James Williams Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Gertz Neely - Lily Tricano</actor>
      <actor>The Amazing Chad - Cade Clark</actor>
      <actor>Hannah Freeman - Erin Cline</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503123500 +0500" stop="20260503130000 +0500">
    <title>Scared Shrekless</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Halloween is coming.This year, Shrek's favorite holiday is going to be really scary.Instead of traditional fun, refreshments and tricks, the ogre challenges his friends.Together with Fiona, Donkey, Puss in Boots and other fairy tale characters, he plans to spend the night in Lord Farquaad's haunted castle.The atmosphere of horror is to be fueled by spine-chilling stories.The one who overcomes his fear will win the competition.Biscuits, Donkey, Puss in Boots and Shrek tell dark stories... In the Polish version, the characters are voiced by famous actors, including:Zbigniew Zamachowski (Shrek) and Jerzy Stuhr (Donkey).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gary Trousdale</director>
      <director>Raman Hui</director>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503130000 +0500" stop="20260503152000 +0500">
    <title>War for the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The situation of the mutant monkeys changes with the appearance of a formation led by the Colonel, which seeks to take control of the apes.Meanwhile, Blue Eyes informs his father that he has found a place for their tribe to live.The decision is made to march.Under the cover of darkness, an attack occurs.Caesar's son and wife are killed.Despite the tragedy, the primate leader believes in the success of a peaceful solution.On his own, he searches for the person responsible for the massacre, but falls into the hands of the enemy.He then finds out that his compatriots were forced to work as slaves.People are attacked by a virus that reverses the process of evolution.The final showdown is inevitably approaching.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Reeves</director>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>The Colonel - Woody Harrelson</actor>
      <actor>Bad Ape - Steve Zahn</actor>
      <actor>Maurice - Karin Konoval</actor>
      <actor>Nova - Amiah Miller</actor>
      <actor>Rocket - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Red Donkey - Ty Olsson</actor>
      <actor>Luca - Michael Adamthwaite</actor>
      <actor>Koba - Toby Kebbell</actor>
      <actor>Preacher - Gabriel Chavarria</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503152000 +0500" stop="20260503171500 +0500">
    <title>Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Four high school students, as part of a punishment imposed by the principal, have to clean up the cluttered school basement.The collected items include an old console from the 1990s and the Jumanji game.Intrigued, the teenagers decide to activate the device.In this way, they are drawn into the virtual world.They end up in a dangerous jungle, where, as avatars, they are forced to fight for survival.Spencer becomes a brave adventurer, Fridge turns into a zoologist, Bethany becomes a corpulent paleontology professor who knows his way around maps, and Martha becomes a martial arts expert.On their way, they meet a guide who tells them the purpose of the mission.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Kasdan</director>
      <actor>Spencer - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Fridge - Kevin Hart</actor>
      <actor>Bethany - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Martha - Karen Gillan</actor>
      <actor>Nigel - Rhys Darby</actor>
      <actor>Van Pelt - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Alex - Nick Jonas</actor>
      <actor>Młody Spencer - Alex Wolff</actor>
      <actor>Młody Fridge - Ser'Darius Blain</actor>
      <actor>Młoda Bethany - Madison Iseman</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503171500 +0500" stop="20260503191500 +0500">
    <title>Another Simple Favor</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Emily Nelson (Blake Lively), who was sentenced to 20 years in prison, regains her freedom.She is planning a wedding on the island of Capri, and an old friend becomes her bridesmaid.A crime occurs during the ceremony.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Paul Feig</director>
      <actor>Emily Nelson - Blake Lively</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Smothers - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Miles Smothers - Joshua Satine</actor>
      <actor>Swim Coach - Mitch Salm</actor>
      <actor>Darren - Andrew Rannells</actor>
      <actor>Lulu - Diletta Jayne</actor>
      <actor>Camp Counselor Val - Holmes</actor>
      <actor>Sona - Aparna Nancherla</actor>
      <actor>Stacy - Kelly McCormack</actor>
      <actor>Vicky - Alex Newell</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503191500 +0500" stop="20260503212000 +0500">
    <title>Green Book</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>USA, 1960s. Tony Vallelonga, a simple resident of the Bronx who has a wife and a group of children to support, agrees to accompany, as a chauffeur and bodyguard, a black musician - the luxurious erudite Donald Shirley - on a concert tour across the United States.Not only does he have to defend his protégé from troubles in the Deep South, but he also has to combat prejudiced views.During their journey, they both follow the instructions from the "Green Book" guide for African Americans traveling around the country.It includes, among others:suggestions on where to sleep and eat to avoid unpleasant incidents.The time spent together and overcoming mounting problems cause a surprising, lasting bond to emerge between men from different worlds.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Farrelly</director>
      <actor>Tony Lip - Viggo Mortensen</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Donald Shirley - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Dolores - Linda Cardellini</actor>
      <actor>Johnny Venere - Sebastian Maniscalco</actor>
      <actor>Oleg - Dimiter D. Marinov</actor>
      <actor>George Dyer - the Cellist - Mike Hatton</actor>
      <actor>Record Exec - P.J. Byrne</actor>
      <actor>Gio Loscudo - Joe Cortese</actor>
      <actor>Copa Coat Check Girl - Maggie Nixon</actor>
      <actor>Bobby Rydell - Von Lewis</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503212000 +0500" stop="20260503230000 +0500">
    <title>By sleeping with others</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lainey and Jake had only slept together once, but it was the first and most important time in their lives.But then the lovers parted ways.A few years later, they accidentally bump into each other...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Leslye Headland</director>
      <actor>Lainey - Alison Brie</actor>
      <actor>Jake - Jason Sudeikis</actor>
      <actor>R.A. - Jordan Carlos</actor>
      <actor>Hannah - Margarita Levieva</actor>
      <actor>Helmet Kid - Charles Cain</actor>
      <actor>Sam - Adam Brody</actor>
      <actor>Attentive Waiter - Michael Cyril Creighton</actor>
      <actor>SLAA Speaker - Billy Eichner</actor>
      <actor>Xander - Jason Mantzoukas</actor>
      <actor>Thea - Margaret Odette</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503230000 +0500" stop="20260504003500 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brave Po opens a new chapter in his life - he is to become the spiritual leader of the Valley of Peace.He's trying to get used to his new role.In addition, the voracious bear must find a daredevil who will replace him as the Dragon Warrior.Not everything goes according to plan.This time, China's security is threatened by Chameleon, who wields black magic and can take on any form and take over the abilities of old masters.With the help of a smart vixen and former thief, Zhen, the panda bear must face her.But they need allies to defeat the shape-shifting witch and the sinister army behind her.The time of a merciless fight is inevitably approaching... The voices of the characters include, among others:Marcin Hycnar, Jan Peszek, Wiktor Zborowski and Julia Chatys.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Mitchell</director>
      <director>Stephanie Stine</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504003500 +0500" stop="20260504021000 +0500">
    <title>Laws of Man</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A suspenseful story set in the paranoid climate of the Cold War era.The year is 1963. Two federal marshals are investigating a case in rural Nevada.They are on the trail of a sinister conspiracy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Phil Blattenberger</director>
      <actor>Galen Armstrong - Keith Carradine</actor>
      <actor>Benjamin Bonney - Dermot Mulroney</actor>
      <actor>Sheriff Kutch - Graham Greene</actor>
      <actor>Cassidy Whittaker - Harvey Keitel</actor>
      <actor>Crash Mooncalf - Richard Brake</actor>
      <actor>Tommy Morton - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Don Burgess - Forrie J. Smith</actor>
      <actor>Proprietor Isaac - James Urbaniak</actor>
      <actor>Callie - Kelly Lynn Reiter</actor>
      <actor>Noah Bonney - Greg Kriek</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504021000 +0500" stop="20260504035000 +0500">
    <title>The Killer's Game</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Joe Flood, one of the best contract killers, learns about an incurable disease and places a contract on himself.However, the murderess is targeting his ex-girlfriend.Joe decides to save her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>J.J. Perry</director>
      <actor>Maize Arnaud - Sofia Boutella</actor>
      <actor>Joe Flood - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Angus Mackenzie - Scott Adkins</actor>
      <actor>Zvi Rabinowitz - Ben Kingsley</actor>
      <actor>Radovan - Daniel Bernhardt</actor>
      <actor>Aimee - Antonia Desplat</actor>
      <actor>Emilio 'El Botas' - Marko Zaror</actor>
      <actor>Rory Mckenzie - Drew McIntyre</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504035000 +0500" stop="20260504060000 +0500">
    <title>Monsieur Aznavour</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Paris, 1930s. The son of immigrants takes part in a theater performance.This is how he discovers his vocal talent and decides to become a singer.A breakthrough in his career was his meeting with Edith Piaf.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mehdi Idir</director>
      <director>Grand Corps Malade</director>
      <actor>Charles Aznavour - Tahar Rahim</actor>
      <actor>Pierre Roche - Bastien Bouillon</actor>
      <actor>Edith Piaf - Marie-Julie Baup</actor>
      <actor>Aida Aznavour - Camille Moutawakil</actor>
      <actor>Micheline Rugel - Ella Pellegrini</actor>
      <actor>Knar Aznavourian - Narine Grigoryan</actor>
      <actor>Mischa Aznavourian - Hovnatan Avédikian</actor>
      <actor>Ulla Thorsell - Petra Silander</actor>
      <actor>Raoul Breton - Luc Antoni</actor>
      <actor>Jean-Louis Marquet - Nicolas Chupin</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504060000 +0500" stop="20260504070500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504070500 +0500" stop="20260504090000 +0500">
    <title>Blue Valentine</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dean grew up in a broken home.He never planned to build a lasting relationship until he met Cindy, with whom he fell in love at first sight.When, after a few weeks of dating, it turns out that the girl is expecting another man's child, she makes the difficult decision to get married.The couple tries to create a happy family, but over time they begin to face a serious crisis.The infatuation disappears, and everyday problems make it difficult for them to find understanding.Dean abuses alcohol and does simple physical work, unable to guarantee his wife real stability and support.The couple falls into conflicts more and more often.However, he still tries to rebuild his relationships for the sake of little Frankie.This perfectly portrayed study of the breakdown of a relationship was nominated for the Grand Jury Prize at the Sundance Film Festival.The role of Michelle Williams was nominated for an Oscar and a Golden Globe.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Derek Cianfrance</director>
      <actor>Dean - Ryan Gosling</actor>
      <actor>Cindy - Michelle Williams</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - John Doman</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Mike Vogel</actor>
      <actor>Frankie - Faith Wladyka</actor>
      <actor>Marshall - Marshall Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Gramma - Jen Jones</actor>
      <actor>Glenda - Maryann Plunkett</actor>
      <actor>Jamie - James Benatti</actor>
      <actor>Jo - Barbara Troy</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504090000 +0500" stop="20260504103500 +0500">
    <title>Detective Monk: One last thing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brilliant detective Adrian Monk (Tony Shalhoub) is going through difficult times.The contract to publish his autobiography was canceled, and the coronavirus pandemic intensified his fears and phobias.All this makes the master of deduction start thinking about ending his life and joining his beloved Truda.He is jolted out of his torpor by the tragedy that befalls his stepdaughter Molly (Caitlin McGee).The girl is getting ready to marry journalist Griffin Briggs (Austin Scott).However, her fiancé dies while bungee jumping.Molly is convinced that it was not an accident, but a carefully planned murder.The trail leads to the influential billionaire Rick Eden (James Purefoy).Retired Captain Stottlemeyer (Ted Levine) now works for the rich man as his security chief.Monk is assisted in the investigation by former assistant and now real estate agent Natalie Teeger (Traylor Howard) and Randy Disher (Jason Gray-Stanford), now the New Jersey police commissioner.Continuation of the cult series.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Randy Zisk</director>
      <actor>Adrian Monk - Tony Shalhoub</actor>
      <actor>Natalie Teeger - Traylor Howard</actor>
      <actor>Randy Disher - Jason Gray-Stanford</actor>
      <actor>Trudy Monk - Melora Hardin</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Neven Bell - Hector Elizondo</actor>
      <actor>Stottlemeyer - Ted Levine</actor>
      <actor>Rick Eden - James Purefoy</actor>
      <actor>Molly Evans - Caitlin McGee</actor>
      <actor>Griffin Briggs - Austin Scott</actor>
      <actor>Skyler - Emma Ishta</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504103500 +0500" stop="20260504121000 +0500">
    <title>Jane Austen Wrecked My Life</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Agathe, a shy employee of the Shakespeare \u0026 Co. bookstore.in Paris, dreams of romantic love like in a Jane Austen novel and success as a writer.An invitation to England gives her a chance to change her fate.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Laura Piani</director>
      <actor>Agathe Robinson - Camille Rutherford</actor>
      <actor>Félix - Pablo Pauly</actor>
      <actor>Oliver - Charlie Anson</actor>
      <actor>Chéryl - Annabelle Lengronne</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Liz Crowther</actor>
      <actor>Todd - Alan Fairbairn</actor>
      <actor>Olympia - Lola Peploe</actor>
      <actor>Mona - Alice Butaud</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Roman Angel</actor>
      <actor>Rosemarie - Laurence Pierre</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504121000 +0500" stop="20260504135500 +0500">
    <title>Maid in Manhattan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>New York.Divorcee Marisa Ventura (Jennifer Lopez) raises her son alone.She works as a maid at the luxurious Beresford Hotel in Manhattan.While cleaning the apartment of aristocrat Caroline Lane (Natasha Richardson), the woman tries on her elegant outfit, in which she looks exceptionally nice.Another hotel guest sees her so changed.He is lawyer Christopher Matthew (Ralph Fiennes), running for parliament.He takes Marisa as a person of a similar social status to himself.They go for a walk together and then eat dinner together.The woman cannot bring herself to correct the mistake, especially since she likes Christopher.However, it is not known how the future senator will react to the fact that his chosen one is an ordinary girl from the Bronx... The luxurious Beresford hotel, where the main character of the film works, is in fact the famous Waldorf-Astoria on Park Avenue.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Wayne Wang</director>
      <actor>Marisa Ventura - Jennifer Lopez</actor>
      <actor>Christopher 'Chris' Marshall, N.Y. Assemblyman - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Caroline Lane - Natasha Richardson</actor>
      <actor>Jerry Siegel - Stanley Tucci</actor>
      <actor>Ty Ventura - Tyler Posey</actor>
      <actor>Paula Burns - Frances Conroy</actor>
      <actor>John Bextrum, Personnel Manager - Chris Eigeman</actor>
      <actor>Rachel Hoffberg - Amy Sedaris</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Kehoe, Maid - Marissa Matrone</actor>
      <actor>Veronica Ventura - Priscilla Lopez</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504135500 +0500" stop="20260504154000 +0500">
    <title>Death Of A Comedian</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Argentine actor Juan Debré (Diego Peretti) receives a disturbing diagnosis at the peak of his career.He escapes to Belgium to immerse himself in his own, safe reality.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Beltramino</director>
      <director>Diego Peretti</director>
      <actor>Lena - Malena Villa</actor>
      <actor>Steve Joyce - Chuck Hargrove</actor>
      <actor>Capitán Busch - Heinz K. Krattiger</actor>
      <actor>Head of Security - Carl-Philipp Wengler</actor>
      <actor>Doyle - Eric Jean Bier</actor>
      <actor>Bonnie - Marioska Fabián Nunez</actor>
      <actor>Waiter in Brussels city - Andrés Guillín</actor>
      <actor>Amal - Agustín Matías Kim</actor>
      <actor>Passenger at the tram stop - Elodie Barthels</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504154000 +0500" stop="20260504173000 +0500">
    <title>Sir Alex Ferguson: Never Give In</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The life story of one of the greatest managers in the history of football.Directed by Jason Ferguson, the film conveys a deeply personal portrayal of his father, Sir Alex Ferguson.He grew up in Glasgow in a working-class family.In his youth he played for Scottish clubs, including Rangers.He then moved into the Aberdeen management team and continued to rise through the ranks.Ferguson shares all the details of his life while undergoing rehabilitation after suffering a cerebral hemorrhage.At the same time, he surprises with his excellent memory, devoting most of his attention to the victorious 26 years of managing Manchester United.He lists every trophy, every defeat and every player.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jason Ferguson</director>
      <actor>Self - Eric Cantona</actor>
      <actor>Self - Alex Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Ryan Giggs</actor>
      <actor>Self - Jason Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Mark Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Gordon Strachan</actor>
      <actor>Self - Cathy Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Self - Archie Knox</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504173000 +0500" stop="20260504193500 +0500">
    <title>The Karate Kid</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Teenage Daniel (Ralph Macchio) moves with his mother, Lucille (Randee Heller), from New Jersey to Los Angeles.He becomes friends with his peer Tommy (Rob Garrison).During a beach party, the boy meets a nice blonde, Ali (Elisabeth Shue).The two immediately take a liking to each other, which does not please her ex-boyfriend, Johnny (William Zabka).As an excellent karateka, he easily teaches his rival a lesson.Humiliated, Daniel also decides to start training eastern martial arts to defeat the enemy.Unfortunately, he cannot join the local club because Johnny and his equally unpleasant and brutal friends practice there.One evening, Daniel is attacked by them again.He is saved from trouble by an old man, Mr. Miyagi (Noriyuki "Pat" Morita), who turns out to be a master of eastern martial arts.From then on, the teenager learns the secrets of karate under his watchful eye.The Japanese teaches him not only the fighting style, but also a lot about life... A perfect film for karate lovers.For his role as Master Noriyuki "Pat" Morita, he received an Oscar nomination for Best Supporting Actor and a Golden Globe nomination.Director of photography John G. Avildsen is known as the creator of the legendary "Rocky" from 1976 with Sylvester Stallone.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John G. Avildsen</director>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Kesuke Miyagi - Noriyuki Pat Morita</actor>
      <actor>Ali Mills - Elisabeth Shue</actor>
      <actor>John Kreese Cobra Kai Sensei - Martin Kove</actor>
      <actor>Lucille Larusso - Randee Heller</actor>
      <actor>Johnny Lawrence - William Zabka</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Ron Thomas</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Rob Garrison</actor>
      <actor>Dutch - Chad McQueen</actor>
      <actor>Jimmy - Tony O'Dell</actor>
    </credits><date>1984</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504193500 +0500" stop="20260504211000 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brave Po opens a new chapter in his life - he is to become the spiritual leader of the Valley of Peace.He's trying to get used to his new role.In addition, the voracious bear must find a daredevil who will replace him as the Dragon Warrior.Not everything goes according to plan.This time, China's security is threatened by Chameleon, who wields black magic and can take on any form and take over the abilities of old masters.With the help of a smart vixen and former thief, Zhen, the panda bear must face her.But they need allies to defeat the shape-shifting witch and the sinister army behind her.The time of a merciless fight is inevitably approaching... The voices of the characters include, among others:Marcin Hycnar, Jan Peszek, Wiktor Zborowski and Julia Chatys.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Mitchell</director>
      <director>Stephanie Stine</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504211000 +0500" stop="20260504230000 +0500">
    <title>We're the Millers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Small-time marijuana dealer David Clark tries to help teenagers living in his neighborhood.He is attacked by three homeless punks and robbed of his goods and cash.As a result, he becomes indebted to his supplier, Brad Gurdlinger.To repay the debt, he must import the latest batch of stimulants from Mexico.To conceal himself, he arranges helpers to pretend to be his immediate family going on holiday with him.So David's neighbors go on the road with him: cynical stripper Rose O'Reilly, the drug dealer's would-be client, the dim-witted Kenny Rossmore, and the smart, street-savvy teenager Casey Mathis.A laugh-out-loud action movie full of well-acted episodes and indecent gags.This is another joint project of Jason Sudeikis and Jennifer Aniston, after the comedies "Get Your Ex" and "Horrible Bosses".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rawson Marshall Thurber</director>
      <actor>Rose O'Reilly - Jennifer Aniston</actor>
      <actor>David Clark - Jason Sudeikis</actor>
      <actor>Casey Mathis - Emma Roberts</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Rossmore - Will Poulter</actor>
      <actor>Brad Gurdlinger - Ed Helms</actor>
      <actor>Don Fitzgerald - Nick Offerman</actor>
      <actor>Edie Fitzgerald - Kathryn Hahn</actor>
      <actor>Melissa Fitzgerald - Molly C. Quinn</actor>
      <actor>Pablo Chacon - Tomer Sisley</actor>
      <actor>One-Eye - Matthew Willig</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260504230000 +0500" stop="20260505000000 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>