<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423074500 +0500" stop="20260423090000 +0500">
    <title>Daniel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Daniel Northcott began documenting his life and the world around him at the age of 7, when his father gave him a video camera.He filmed his family and friends, and then the places he traveled to.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Daniel Northcott</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423090000 +0500" stop="20260423104000 +0500">
    <title>The Book of Life</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two powerful magicians bet whether people are pure in heart.La Muerte is the ruler of the World of the Remembered.The dead stay there, remaining in the hearts of their loved ones.Xibalba rules the Land of the Forgotten - a sad place for souls that no one remembers.The magicians are tested by: fashion matador Manolo, who dreams of being a musician, and Joaquin - an athlete and the pride of the city.The boys compete for the affections of Maria, the daughter of the local mayor.However, the beautiful bride is resistant to their advances.Manolo and Joaquin will go on a wonderful journey, during which they will visit extraordinary lands, meet colorful characters and discover the truth about themselves.The project by Guillermo del Toro and Jorge R. Gutierrez was nominated for a Golden Globe in the category of best animated film.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jorge R. Gutiérrez</director>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423104000 +0500" stop="20260423124000 +0500">
    <title>The Fourth Wall</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 1982, war-torn Lebanon.Theater director Georges (Laurent Lafitte), in order to keep his promise to his terminally ill friend, goes to Beirut to implement a risky project.He intends to put "Antigone" on the front line to guarantee a moment of peace for the parties to the conflict.The show will feature actors involved in fighting, belonging to various political and religious factions.Marwan (Simon Abkarian) becomes a guide in an unknown city, who explains the background of the dispute to the foreigner and becomes a link with the locals.Soon Georges faces the brutal realities of war.The plans are also complicated by the feelings he has for one of the actresses, Imane (Manal Issa).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Oelhoffen</director>
      <actor>Georges - Laurent Lafitte</actor>
      <actor>Marwan - Simon Abkarian</actor>
      <actor>Imane - Manal Issa</actor>
      <actor>Sam Akounis - Bernard Bloch</actor>
      <actor>Nakad - Tarek Yaacoub</actor>
      <actor>Charbel - Pio Chihahe</actor>
      <actor>Nabil - Elie Njeim</actor>
      <actor>Yevkine - Dana Mikhail</actor>
      <actor>Khadija - Khitam Al Lahham</actor>
      <actor>Madeleine - Tracy Younes</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423124000 +0500" stop="20260423143500 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn - Part 1</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bella Swan and Edward Cullen are getting married.They spend their honeymoon on a private island in Brazil belonging to the groom's family.Two weeks later, Bella discovers she is pregnant.The fetus is developing at a rapid pace.The couple returns to Forks.It turns out that Bella's condition means great danger to her.The werewolves, led by Sam, want to kill her unborn offspring, who may turn out to be a demon.Jacob defies his pack and decides to protect his lost loved one.The Cullen family prepares for a difficult birth.Edward will have to fight to save the person he loves with all his heart.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Condon</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Jessica Stanley - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Jane - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Aro - Michael Sheen</actor>
      <actor>Emmett Cullen - Kellan Lutz</actor>
      <actor>Rosalie Hale - Nikki Reed</actor>
      <actor>Caius - Jamie Campbell Bower</actor>
      <actor>Irina - Maggie Grace</actor>
    </credits><date>2011</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423143500 +0500" stop="20260423162000 +0500">
    <title>Focus</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nicky Spurgeon is a calculating fraud.The model's appearance and ability to keep cool make him a master criminal.He is able to win people over, but he does it to take advantage of them.One day, in a restaurant, he meets a fair-haired beauty, Jess Barrett, whose ambition is to pursue a criminal career.He becomes her mentor.Over time, they both realize that they have much more in common than the relationship of master and disciple.However, they live in a world where there is no place for love.Spurgeon ends this relationship.Three years pass.Nicky is in Buenos Aires, where he works for the owner of a car racing team, Rafael Garrigi.He meets his former lover here.Aware of her strengths, the femme fatale has one goal - to take revenge for the way she was once treated.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Glenn Ficarra</director>
      <director>John Requa</director>
      <actor>Nicky - Will Smith</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Margot Robbie</actor>
      <actor>Farhad - Adrian Martinez</actor>
      <actor>Owens - Gerald McRaney</actor>
      <actor>Garriga - Rodrigo Santoro</actor>
      <actor>Liyuan - BD Wong</actor>
      <actor>Horst - Brennan Brown</actor>
      <actor>McEwen - Robert Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Gordon - Dotan Bonen</actor>
      <actor>Gareth - Griff Furst</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423162000 +0500" stop="20260423191500 +0500">
    <title>The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Hobbit Frodo Baggins comes into possession of a magical Ring.His relative Bilbo obtained it during his expedition to the Lonely Mountain.This extraordinary gem can give its owner control over the world, which is why its creator - the Lord of Darkness Sauron - will do anything to get it back.The wizard Gandalf knows that the Ring must be destroyed.There is only one way to do this - by throwing him into the fire that burns inside Mount Doom.However, getting there is very difficult.A council is called in Rivendell on this matter.Frodo undertakes a dangerous mission to destroy the jewel.He is accompanied by his friendly hobbits, Sam Gamgee and Pippin and Merry, as well as representatives of other races: the elf Legolas, the dwarf Gimli, people - Aragorn and Boromir - and Gandalf.The ring has a sinister power that is difficult to avoid.It arouses strong desire and influences the psyche, which puts the team to the test.Meanwhile, Sauron sends his troops against her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Frodo Baggins - Elijah Wood</actor>
      <actor>Legolas Greenleaf - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Gandalf - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Galadriel - Cate Blanchett</actor>
      <actor>Sam Gamgee - Sean Astin</actor>
      <actor>Peregrin 'Pippin' Took - Billy Boyd</actor>
      <actor>Saruman - Christopher Lee</actor>
      <actor>Boromir - Sean Bean</actor>
      <actor>Everard Proudfoot - Noel Appleby</actor>
      <actor>Sauron - Sala Baker</actor>
    </credits><date>2001</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423191500 +0500" stop="20260423211500 +0500">
    <title>Alita: Battle Angel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alita (Rosa Salazar), a cyborg girl, wakes up from a coma.It turns out that he doesn't remember who he is or where he is.Doctor Ido (Christoph Waltz) subjected her to a series of tests that revealed that she was a young woman with a unique story.Wanting to protect her, he does not reveal the truth about her past.Alita must adapt to the conditions and rules of life in Scrap City.After some time, he regains his memory thanks to the help of his friend, Hugo (Keean Johnson).Then he realizes that he has incredible fighting skills.She must use them against the power that tries to control her.The film's director is Robert Rodriguez, known from "From Dusk Till Dawn" and "Machete".The script was written by the winner of three Oscars, James Cameron, who considered making "Alita" back in the 1990s. The film was based on the manga.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Rodriguez</director>
      <actor>Alita - Rosa Salazar</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Dyson Ido - Christoph Waltz</actor>
      <actor>Chiren - Jennifer Connelly</actor>
      <actor>Vector - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Zapan - Ed Skrein</actor>
      <actor>Grewishka - Jackie Earle Haley</actor>
      <actor>Hugo - Keean Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tanji - Jorge Lendeborg Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Koyomi - Lana Condor</actor>
      <actor>Nurse Gerhad - Idara Victor</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423211500 +0500" stop="20260423230000 +0500">
    <title>You Gotta Believe</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A group of baseball players are having the most important season of their lives.For one of the boys, the stakes are even higher - the team fights not only for victories, but also for his father's dream to come true.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ty Roberts</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423230000 +0500" stop="20260424002500 +0500">
    <title>The Doll</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rémi did not recover from the breakup.In order to function, he remains in a relationship with the doll Audrey, with whom he lives and shares everyday affairs.One day, a new colleague shows up at his company.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sophie Beaulieu</director>
      <actor>Rémi Allard - Vincent Macaigne</actor>
      <actor>Audrey - Zoé Marchal</actor>
      <actor>Rosy Allard - Marianne Basler</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Cécile De France</actor>
      <actor>Domi - Adele Journeaux</actor>
      <actor>Bernard Allard - Gilbert Melki</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ludovic Thievon</actor>
      <actor>Hervé - Eric Guerin</actor>
      <actor>Renan - Victor Bonnel</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424002500 +0500" stop="20260424013000 +0500">
    <title>The Dark Wizard</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Biography of the legendary climber, BASE jumper and slackliner.Dean Potter specialized in free solo ascents, speed climbing and slacklining without belays.An important element of his activity was crossing the boundaries of style and combining disciplines: climbing, highline and BASE jumping.He was the precursor of free BASE, i.e. solo climbing using a parachute as the only protection.In Yosemite he set speed and free solo records.His activities had a significant impact on setting risk limits, which raised ethical controversies in the community.He died in 2015 in Yosemite Valley.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Mortimer</director>
      <director>Nick Rosen</director>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424013000 +0500" stop="20260424030500 +0500">
    <title>Berlin Nobody</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>American social psychologist Ben Monroe (Eric Bana) moves to Berlin after breaking up with his wife.He gained fame for his research on sects, including a religious group operating in the German capital, and is currently preparing to write another book on this subject.One day, his partner Nina (Sylvia Hoeks) and his old friend, policeman Max Aumann (Stephan Kampwirth), take him to a crime scene where it seems that several people have been ritually committed suicide.Soon, Ben is visited by his 16-year-old daughter, Mazzy (Sadie Sink).She is seduced by a local boy, Martin (Jonas Dassler).He tells her that he is involved in the activities of a pro-ecological non-governmental organization run by the charismatic Hilma (Sophie Rois).The girl allows herself to be drawn into this group, unaware that it is a sect that has chosen her as a victim.When Ben discovers how much danger Mazzy is in, he races against time to save her.The film's script is based on the 2015 novel by Nicholas Hogg."Tokyo", but the setting was moved to Berlin.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jordan Scott</director>
      <actor>Ben Monroe - Eric Bana</actor>
      <actor>Mazzy Monroe - Sadie Sink</actor>
      <actor>Nina - Sylvia Hoeks</actor>
      <actor>Martin - Jonas Dassler</actor>
      <actor>Hilma - Sophie Rois</actor>
      <actor>Max Aumann - Stephan Kampwirth</actor>
      <actor>Sofie Aumann - Justine del Corte</actor>
      <actor>Elsa Aumann - Joone Dankou</actor>
      <actor>Lotte - Lara Feith</actor>
      <actor>Larissa - Sira-Anna Faal</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424030500 +0500" stop="20260424051500 +0500">
    <title>NO</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Animal tamer OJ Haywood (Daniel Kaluuya) and his sister Emerald (Keke Palmer) live on a ranch in southern California where horses are trained for Hollywood film productions.They take over the business of their father, who died in suspicious circumstances.Problems are piling up for them.One day they become witnesses of inexplicable phenomena.Together with a former child star (Steven Yeun), an emcee at a family amusement park, they try to film supernatural incidents to make money by selling sensational materials.Their actions have unforeseen consequences.Director Jordan Peele made his debut in 2017 with the acclaimed thriller "Get Out!", for which he won an Oscar for the script.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jordan Peele</director>
      <actor>OJ Haywood - Daniel Kaluuya</actor>
      <actor>Emerald Haywood - Keke Palmer</actor>
      <actor>Angel Torres - Brandon Perea</actor>
      <actor>Antlers Holst - Michael Wincott</actor>
      <actor>Ricky 'Jupe' Park - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Amber Park - Wrenn Schmidt</actor>
      <actor>Otis Haywood Sr. - Keith David</actor>
      <actor>Ryder Muybridge - Devon Graye</actor>
      <actor>Gordy - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Nessie - Barbie Ferreira</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424051500 +0500" stop="20260424073500 +0500">
    <title>Queer</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Year 1950, Mexico.William Lee (Daniel Craig), a middle-aged American, spends his days almost alone.He contacts several people from a small American community of students and bar owners.The arrival of another student, Eugene Allerton (Drew Starkey), in town makes him realize for the first time that an intimate bond is possible.The men first become friends, then their relationship turns into a romance.As a couple, they go to South America in search of a drug that supposedly gives the power of telepathy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Luca Guadagnino</director>
      <actor>William Lee - Daniel Craig</actor>
      <actor>Karl Steinberg - Daan de Wit</actor>
      <actor>Joe Guidry - Jason Schwartzman</actor>
      <actor>Winston Moor - Henrique Zaga</actor>
      <actor>Tom Williams - Colin Bates</actor>
      <actor>Eugene Allerton - Drew Starkey</actor>
      <actor>Ship Ahoy Bartender - Simon Rizzoni</actor>
      <actor>John Dumé - Drew Droege</actor>
      <actor>Tom Weston - Ariel Schulman</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Andra Ursuta</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424073500 +0500" stop="20260424090000 +0500">
    <title>The Doll</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rémi did not recover from the breakup.In order to function, he remains in a relationship with the doll Audrey, with whom he lives and shares everyday affairs.One day, a new colleague shows up at his company.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sophie Beaulieu</director>
      <actor>Rémi Allard - Vincent Macaigne</actor>
      <actor>Audrey - Zoé Marchal</actor>
      <actor>Rosy Allard - Marianne Basler</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Cécile De France</actor>
      <actor>Domi - Adele Journeaux</actor>
      <actor>Bernard Allard - Gilbert Melki</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ludovic Thievon</actor>
      <actor>Hervé - Eric Guerin</actor>
      <actor>Renan - Victor Bonnel</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424090000 +0500" stop="20260424110000 +0500">
    <title>Everest</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 1996. Rob Hall (Jason Clarke) organizes a commercial expedition to the highest mountain in the world.His brigade includes, among others:Texan Beck Weathers (Josh Brolin) and reporter Jon Krakauer (Michael Kelly).The mountaineers reach the base camp.Over the course of several weeks, they get used to extreme weather conditions and pressure that disregulates the body.Apart from them, other teams are heading to the summit.Hall makes a strategic decision to join Scott Fischer (Jake Gyllenhaal), the head of the Mountain Madness expedition.At the beginning of May, climbers leave the base camp.They struggle with snow storms, bitter cold and lack of oxygen.Extreme conditions put them at the edge of their mental and physical endurance.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Baltasar Kormákur</director>
      <actor>Rob Hall - Jason Clarke</actor>
      <actor>Scott Fischer - Jake Gyllenhaal</actor>
      <actor>Beck Weathers - Josh Brolin</actor>
      <actor>Ang Dorjee - Ang Phula Sherpa</actor>
      <actor>Michael Groom - Thomas M. Wright</actor>
      <actor>Andy 'Harold' Harris - Martin Henderson</actor>
      <actor>Neal Beidleman - Tom Goodman-Hill</actor>
      <actor>Lene Gammelgaard - Charlotte Boving</actor>
      <actor>Lopsang - Pemba Sherpa</actor>
      <actor>Charlotte Fox - Amy Shindler</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Disaster Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424110000 +0500" stop="20260424124500 +0500">
    <title>You Gotta Believe</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A group of baseball players are having the most important season of their lives.For one of the boys, the stakes are even higher - the team fights not only for victories, but also for his father's dream to come true.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ty Roberts</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424124500 +0500" stop="20260424144000 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn - Part 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bella and Edward are already married.However, the young couple did not have time to enjoy each other.The girl quickly became pregnant, but it turned out that it was life-threatening.Edward couldn't watch his beloved suffer and made the dramatic decision to transform her into a vampire.This was the only way he could save Bella from dying during the grueling labor.After the metamorphosis, the young woman improves her skills and learns to control her hunger.Together with her husband, she enjoys watching the rapid development of her extraordinary daughter, Renesmee, who at the age of three months looks like a two-year-old and can show her thoughts through images.The family idyll does not last long.There is a suspicion that the girl is an immortal child whose existence is against the law established by the Volturi.Renesmee and her parents are at risk of death.Edward and his family decide to defend themselves.They summon vampires from all corners of the world and prepare to confront the Volturi.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Condon</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Carlisle Cullen - Peter Facinelli</actor>
      <actor>Esme Cullen - Elizabeth Reaser</actor>
      <actor>Alice Cullen - Ashley Greene</actor>
      <actor>Jasper Hale - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Emmett Cullen - Kellan Lutz</actor>
      <actor>Rosalie Hale - Nikki Reed</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Swan - Billy Burke</actor>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424144000 +0500" stop="20260424151000 +0500">
    <title>Hollywood On Set 23</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E17</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424151000 +0500" stop="20260424164000 +0500">
    <title>Gaslit By My Husband: The Morgan Metzer Story</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Morgan (Jana Kramer) is attacked by a masked assailant.A moment later, her ex-husband appears.His testimony raises concerns - has he come to help her, or is he hiding a dark secret?</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Lee Gabiana</director>
      <actor>Morgan Metzer - Jana Kramer</actor>
      <actor>Rodney Metzer - Austin Nichols</actor>
      <actor>Nicole - Abigail Esmena</actor>
      <actor>Amilia Metzer - Jolie Rae Caussin</actor>
      <actor>Mason Metzer - Maximo Sebastian</actor>
      <actor>Kathy Metzer - Stephanie Cotton</actor>
      <actor>Rod Metzer - Pete Burris</actor>
      <actor>Lindsey - Denise Dal Vera</actor>
      <actor>Richard - J. Barrett Cooper</actor>
      <actor>Therapist - Lee Avant</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424164000 +0500" stop="20260424193500 +0500">
    <title>The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Fellowship of the Ring has been broken.Frodo and Sam continue their journey to Mordor - the only place where the Ring can be destroyed.They manage to capture Gollum, one of the previous owners of the magical gem.Frodo decides to trust him.She makes him her guide.Meanwhile, Gandalf the Gray fights the Balrog, the Demon of Power.After the duel, the wizard is reborn as Gandalf the White.He joins Aragorn, Legolas the elf and Gimli the dwarf as they journey to Rohan.They must warn the local ruler Théoden about the war.It turns out that he can no longer rule.His faith and strength were robbed by a curse cast by Saruman.Merry and Pippin escape from orc captivity to Fangorn - an ancient forest.Treebeard, the shepherd of trees, takes care of them there.Middle-earth is threatened by great danger - Sauron, ruler of Mordor, and the wizard Saruman, lord of Isengard, unite their forces.Troops of wild Uruk-hai are growing in strength.The day of the Battle of Helm's Deep is approaching.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Frodo Baggins - Elijah Wood</actor>
      <actor>Gandalf Szary/Gandalf Biały - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Arwen - Liv Tyler</actor>
      <actor>Aragorn - Viggo Mortensen</actor>
      <actor>Samwise 'Sam' Gamgee - Sean Astin</actor>
      <actor>Galadriel - Cate Blanchett</actor>
      <actor>Gimli/Voice of Treebeard - John Rhys-Davies</actor>
      <actor>Theoden - Bernard Hill</actor>
      <actor>Saruman the White - Christopher Lee</actor>
      <actor>Peregrin 'Pippin' Took - Billy Boyd</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424193500 +0500" stop="20260424211000 +0500">
    <title>Sanctuary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hal Porterfield (Christopher Abbott) orders room service at a posh hotel.Rebecca Marin (Margaret Qualley) shows up at the apartment to interview him for the position of general manager of this chain of facilities.Her questions become more and more personal and lead to a surprising ending.In reality, the woman is a dominatrix who follows the script prepared by Hal.However, the relationship does not follow the script ordered by the client.The woman decides to blackmail the rich man.She claims that she recorded a compromising sex tape with him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zachary Wigon</director>
      <actor>Hal - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Hallway - Francisco Castaneda</actor>
      <actor>Woman in the Hallway - Kathie Young</actor>
      <actor>Older Phil Porterfield - Dominic Defilips</actor>
      <actor>Younger Phil Porterfield - Rene Calvo</actor>
      <actor>Hal's Mother - Danita Battle</actor>
      <actor>Young Hal - Christian Casatelli</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424211000 +0500" stop="20260424230000 +0500">
    <title>Macbeth</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Macbeth returns from his war expedition.The witches predict a great future for him.The man's ambition and lust for power awaken, additionally fueled by his wife.However, his path to the throne will be bloody.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Justin Kurzel</director>
      <actor>Makbet - Michael Fassbender</actor>
      <actor>Lady Makbet - Marion Cotillard</actor>
      <actor>Banquo - Paddy Considine</actor>
      <actor>Fleance - Lochlann Harris</actor>
      <actor>Young Witch - Kayla Fallon</actor>
      <actor>Middle-Aged Witch - Lynn Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Older Witch - Seylan Mhairi Baxter</actor>
      <actor>Child Witch - Amber Rissmann</actor>
      <actor>Young Boy Soldier - Scot Greenan</actor>
      <actor>Macdonwald - Hilton McRae</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260424230000 +0500" stop="20260425003500 +0500">
    <title>Eileen</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1960s, Massachusetts.Eileen Dunlop (Thomasin McKenzie) works as a secretary at a reformatory for teenage boys.She lives with her widowed, alcohol-addicted father (Shea Whigham), a former police chief who suffers from paranoia and emotionally abuses her.The girl feels overwhelmed by anger and a sense of helplessness.He seeks refuge in the world of fantasy.The arrival of a new prison psychologist, the assertive and self-confident Rebecca (Anne Hathaway), causes her suppressed feelings to come to life.It seems that for the first time he has a chance for a real, deep relationship... The film's script is based on the novel by Ottessa Moshfegh.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>William Oldroyd</director>
      <actor>Eileen Dunlop - Thomasin McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Anne Hathaway</actor>
      <actor>Jim Dunlop - Shea Whigham</actor>
      <actor>Lee Polk - Sam Nivola</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Murray - Siobhan Fallon Hogan</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Stevens - Tonye Patano</actor>
      <actor>Intake Guard - William Hill</actor>
      <actor>Randy - Owen Teague</actor>
      <actor>Warden - Peter McRobbie</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Frye - Peter von Berg</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>