<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502041500 +0500" stop="20260502060000 +0500">
    <title>Closer</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>London.Stripper and waitress Alice (Natalie Portman) has a minor accident on the street.Writer Dan (Jude Law) takes her to the hospital.They fall in love with each other almost at first sight and move in together.A few months later, Dan falls in love with talented photographer Anna (Julia Roberts).Although she is not indifferent to the writer, knowing about his relationship with Alice, she does not want to meet him.To take revenge, Dan impersonates her in one of the erotic chat rooms and starts a spicy conversation with doctor Larry (Clive Owen).The first real meeting between Larry and Anna is quite unfortunate, but soon they both fall in love and get married.After some time, the woman meets Dan again and the old fascination is revived.Meanwhile, Larry meets Alice and falls under her spell.Adapted from a play by Patrick Marber.Clive Owen and Natalie Portman received Golden Globe and Oscar nominations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Nichols</director>
      <actor>Alice - Natalie Portman</actor>
      <actor>Dan - Jude Law</actor>
      <actor>Anna - Julia Roberts</actor>
      <actor>Larry - Clive Owen</actor>
      <actor>taksówkarz - Nick Hobbs</actor>
      <actor>Customs Officer - Colin Stinton</actor>
    </credits><date>2004</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502060000 +0500" stop="20260502072500 +0500">
    <title>Some Other Woman</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thanks to his job, Peter Simmons (Tom Felton) has the opportunity to move to a tropical island for a few months.He takes his wife, Eva (Amanda Crew), with him there.The couple feels like they are in paradise and enjoys the charms of this beautiful place.However, duties keep Peter on the island longer, so months turn into years and Eva is forced to abandon her plans.In addition, she begins to be haunted by a mysterious woman, Renata (Ashley Greene), who looks very much like her.When Eva realizes that she is taking over her life, piece by piece, she panics.He's not going to let that happen.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joel David Moore</director>
      <actor>Eve Simmons - Amanda Crew</actor>
      <actor>Peter Simmons - Tom Felton</actor>
      <actor>Renata Cordova - Ashley Greene</actor>
      <actor>Chelsea Ranza - Brooke Lyons</actor>
      <actor>Salvador Ranza - Rick Fox</actor>
      <actor>Caro - Caroline Raynaud</actor>
      <actor>Fisherman - Darvin Ebanks</actor>
      <actor>Mendo - Matt Fox Seales</actor>
      <actor>Abarena - Nasaria Suckoo-Cholette</actor>
      <actor>Psychologist - Samantha Kaine</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502072500 +0500" stop="20260502090000 +0500">
    <title>Bastille Day</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>On the eve of Bastille Day, an American thief living in Paris, Michael Mason (Richard Madden), steals a bag containing a teddy bear.Not knowing that there is a bomb hidden inside the toy, he takes the money and documents and throws the rest into a trash bin in a crowded Paris metro station.A few seconds later there is a huge explosion.Four people die.City surveillance footage reveals Michael's face.The police, considering him a terrorist, start searching for him.He is stopped by CIA agent Sean Briar (Idris Elba), who is just trying to find his way back to work after returning from Iraq.He brings the suspect to a secret interrogation room.Michael explains the misunderstanding and convinces that someone else is behind the attack.He and Sean have 24 hours to find the real culprits.The film was shot in 2015 and became even more relevant after the attacks in Paris.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>James Watkins</director>
      <actor>Sean Briar - Idris Elba</actor>
      <actor>Michael Mason - Richard Madden</actor>
      <actor>Zoe - Charlotte Le Bon</actor>
      <actor>Karen Dacre - Kelly Reilly</actor>
      <actor>Victor Gamieux - José Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Rafi Bertrand - Thierry Godard</actor>
      <actor>Yannick Bertrand - Vincent Londez</actor>
      <actor>Jean - Arieh Worthalter</actor>
      <actor>Christophe - Mohamed Makhtoumi</actor>
      <actor>Xavier - Théo Costa-Marini</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502090000 +0500" stop="20260502101500 +0500">
    <title>Upon Entry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Venezuelan Diego (Alberto Ammann) and Spanish Elena (Bruna Cusí) decide to move to the United States.The couple successfully passed the visa procedure and packed all their belongings.It seems that nothing will stop them from building a new life in the USA soon.At the immigration area at the New York airport, they are asked to talk.Inside the cramped interior, Diego and Elena are subjected to a thorough inspection by border officers.Routine activities turn into a grueling interrogation that lasts several hours.Secrets that they never shared with each other are revealed.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Alejandro Rojas</director>
      <director>Juan Vasquez</director>
      <actor>Diego - Alberto Ammann</actor>
      <actor>Elena - Bruna Cusí</actor>
      <actor>Agent Barrett - Ben Temple</actor>
      <actor>Agent Vásquez - Laura Gómez</actor>
      <actor>Taxista - Laura Bernis</actor>
      <actor>Policia cua - Nuris Blu</actor>
      <actor>Policia sala 1 - David Comrie</actor>
      <actor>Jove - Alicia Durán</actor>
      <actor>Gos policia - Kamyla</actor>
      <actor>Policia finestreta - Colin Morgan</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502101500 +0500" stop="20260502113500 +0500">
    <title>Adult Best Friends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Katie (Katie Corwin) and Delaney (Delaney Buffett), who have known each other since childhood, are best friends.They cannot live without each other, even though each of them is at a different stage of their lives.While the first woman is ready to start a family, which was preceded by accepting the proposal of her boyfriend, John (Mason Gooding), the second one stopped at the college stage and has no intention of growing up.In addition, Delaney does not like her friend's boyfriend because she is convinced that sooner or later their relationship will suffer because of him.Therefore, Katie, who always takes into account her friend's opinion, decides to tell her about the engagement in the most delicate way possible, during a girls' trip together.Unfortunately, nothing goes according to plan during the trip.Katie Corwin and Delaney Buffett, who play the main characters, and who also co-wrote the film's script, are also considered best friends in real life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Delaney Buffett</director>
      <actor>Katie - Katie Corwin</actor>
      <actor>Delaney - Delaney Buffett</actor>
      <actor>John - Mason Gooding</actor>
      <actor>Henry - Zachary Quinto</actor>
      <actor>Roxy - Cazzie David</actor>
      <actor>Mel - Hannah Campbell</actor>
      <actor>Phil - Carmen Christopher</actor>
      <actor>Young Katie - Jolie Natalia Handler</actor>
      <actor>Charlie - Connor Hines</actor>
      <actor>Theo - Alexander Hodge</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502113500 +0500" stop="20260502130000 +0500">
    <title>Fantastic Mr. Fox</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Since his unsuccessful attack on one of the farms, Mr. Fox has been leading a quiet, boring life.Under the influence of his wife, he settled down, gave up working on the border of the law and started writing articles for a local newspaper.However, his instincts do not allow him to sit still for long.Soon, together with his friend Szop, he comes up with a plan to attack three large farms.The friends brilliantly rob Walter Boggis, Franklin Bean and Nathan Bunce.However, people do not remain idle and quickly develop a plan for revenge.Mr. Fox must fight for the life not only of himself and his loved ones, but also of other persecuted creatures.Wes Anderson, responsible for the film, was nominated for an Oscar in 2001 for his screenplay for "Brilliant Clan"."Fantastic Mr. Fox" is his animated debut.The director's credits include the award-winning comedy "The Grand Budapest Hotel."The film received nine Oscar nominations, including:in the following categories: best film, script, music, cinematography and editing.He also won a Golden Globe statuette.The Polish language version was attended by, among others:Grzegorz Wons, Agnieszka Kunikowska, Artur Pontek, Piotr Bajtlik and Krzysztof Szczerbiński.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Wes Anderson</director>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502130000 +0500" stop="20260502151000 +0500">
    <title>Dawn of the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ten years have passed since a virus wiped out almost the entire human race.The metropolises were deserted and civilization came to an end.Another intelligent species took over the world - genetically modified monkeys.They create their own world with a specific hierarchy.Caesar, a human-raised male who led the apes to revolution, is the leader of the pack.He was one of the few who experienced both evil and good from people.He hadn't seen a human for two years and thought the species was extinct.However, he is wrong.One day it turns out that in the ruins of San Francisco there lives a colony of people immune to the virus, led by a former policeman.Confrontation between both sides is inevitable.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Reeves</director>
      <actor>Dreyfus - Gary Oldman</actor>
      <actor>Malcolm - Jason Clarke</actor>
      <actor>Ellie - Keri Russell</actor>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>Koba - Toby Kebbell</actor>
      <actor>Alexander - Kodi Smit-McPhee</actor>
      <actor>Carver - Kirk Acevedo</actor>
      <actor>Blue Eyes - Nick Thurston</actor>
      <actor>Rocket - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Maurice - Karin Konoval</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502151000 +0500" stop="20260502171500 +0500">
    <title>The Karate Kid</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Teenage Daniel (Ralph Macchio) moves with his mother, Lucille (Randee Heller), from New Jersey to Los Angeles.He becomes friends with his peer Tommy (Rob Garrison).During a beach party, the boy meets a nice blonde, Ali (Elisabeth Shue).The two immediately take a liking to each other, which does not please her ex-boyfriend, Johnny (William Zabka).As an excellent karateka, he easily teaches his rival a lesson.Humiliated, Daniel also decides to start training eastern martial arts to defeat the enemy.Unfortunately, he cannot join the local club because Johnny and his equally unpleasant and brutal friends practice there.One evening, Daniel is attacked by them again.He is saved from trouble by an old man, Mr. Miyagi (Noriyuki "Pat" Morita), who turns out to be a master of eastern martial arts.From then on, the teenager learns the secrets of karate under his watchful eye.The Japanese teaches him not only the fighting style, but also a lot about life... A perfect film for karate lovers.For his role as Master Noriyuki "Pat" Morita, he received an Oscar nomination for Best Supporting Actor and a Golden Globe nomination.Director of photography John G. Avildsen is known as the creator of the legendary "Rocky" from 1976 with Sylvester Stallone.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John G. Avildsen</director>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Kesuke Miyagi - Noriyuki Pat Morita</actor>
      <actor>Ali Mills - Elisabeth Shue</actor>
      <actor>John Kreese Cobra Kai Sensei - Martin Kove</actor>
      <actor>Lucille Larusso - Randee Heller</actor>
      <actor>Johnny Lawrence - William Zabka</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Ron Thomas</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Rob Garrison</actor>
      <actor>Dutch - Chad McQueen</actor>
      <actor>Jimmy - Tony O'Dell</actor>
    </credits><date>1984</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502171500 +0500" stop="20260502193000 +0500">
    <title>The Karate Kid</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sherry Parker (Taraji P. Henson) is offered a job in Beijing.He goes there with his son Dre (Jaden Smith).The boy cannot acclimatize to the new surroundings.For this reason, he often comes into conflict with his school friends.He is also persecuted by them.One day, Dre meets Mr. Han (Jackie Chan), the caretaker of the building where he lives with his mother.The man decides to teach the boy martial arts so that he can defend himself against his peers who bully him.Many hours of training create a unique bond between them, much stronger than ordinary teacher-student relationships.The film's script loosely refers to John G. Avildsen's work from 1984.The production received nominations for the Teen and People's Choice awards, Czarny Repules and the Golden Popcorn award.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Harald Zwart</director>
      <actor>Dre Parker - Jaden Smith</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Sherry Parker - Taraji P. Henson</actor>
      <actor>Meiying - Wenwen Han</actor>
      <actor>Master Li - Rongguang Yu</actor>
      <actor>Meiying's Dad - Zhensu Wu</actor>
      <actor>Meiying's Mom - Zhiheng Wang</actor>
      <actor>Cheng - Zhenwei Wang</actor>
      <actor>Dre's Detroit Friend - Jared Minns</actor>
      <actor>Liang - Shijia Lü</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502193000 +0500" stop="20260502210500 +0500">
    <title>Karate Kid: Legends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li Fong's friend needs help.He decided to take part in a karate tournament, but his skills are insufficient.Teacher Han turns to the legendary Daniel LaRusso for help.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Li Fong - Ben Wang</actor>
      <actor>Victor Lipani - Joshua Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Mia Lipani - Sadie Stanley</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Fong - Ming-Na</actor>
      <actor>Alan - Wyatt Oleff</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Aramis Knight</actor>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Young Girl - Olivia Yang Avis</actor>
      <actor>Young Student - Aaron Wang</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502210500 +0500" stop="20260502230000 +0500">
    <title>Vinci 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Cuma receives an offer to participate in a new heist.At first he refuses, but changes his mind when he learns that his old rival, Chudy, is planning a spectacular robbery in Krakow without his participation.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Juliusz Machulski</director>
      <actor>Robert Cumiński Cuma - Robert Więckiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Julian Wolniewicz Szerszeń - Borys Szyc</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Kamilla Baar</actor>
      <actor>komisarz Łukasz Wilk - Marcin Dorociński</actor>
      <actor>paser Chudy - Mirosław Haniszewski</actor>
      <actor>Marcin Kudra - Łukasz Simlat</actor>
      <actor>Jan Bednarek Werbus - Jacek Król</actor>
      <actor>Kazu Tanaka - Masakazu Miyanaga</actor>
      <actor>kurator Zjawińska - Ilona Ostrowska</actor>
      <actor>Helmut - Krzysztof Stelmaszyk</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260502230000 +0500" stop="20260503010000 +0500">
    <title>Another Simple Favor</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Emily Nelson (Blake Lively), who was sentenced to 20 years in prison, regains her freedom.She is planning a wedding on the island of Capri, and an old friend becomes her bridesmaid.A crime occurs during the ceremony.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Paul Feig</director>
      <actor>Emily Nelson - Blake Lively</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Smothers - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Miles Smothers - Joshua Satine</actor>
      <actor>Swim Coach - Mitch Salm</actor>
      <actor>Darren - Andrew Rannells</actor>
      <actor>Lulu - Diletta Jayne</actor>
      <actor>Camp Counselor Val - Holmes</actor>
      <actor>Sona - Aparna Nancherla</actor>
      <actor>Stacy - Kelly McCormack</actor>
      <actor>Vicky - Alex Newell</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503010000 +0500" stop="20260503024000 +0500">
    <title>Anaconda</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Doug (Jack Black) and Griff (Paul Rudd) have been friends since childhood.They have always dreamed of making a remake of their favorite film, the horror film "Anaconda".When both buddies experience a midlife crisis, they decide not to wait any longer and set off together deep into the Amazon to start filming.The situation becomes more complicated when... a real giant anaconda appears on the film set, spreading chaos and destruction around.Despite the deadly threat, the friends decide to take advantage of the predator's presence.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tom Gormican</director>
      <actor>Doug McCallister - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Ronald Griffin Jr. - Paul Rudd</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Trent - Steve Zahn</actor>
      <actor>Claire Simons - Thandie Newton</actor>
      <actor>Ana Almeida - Daniela Melchior</actor>
      <actor>Santiago Braga - Selton Mello</actor>
      <actor>Ice Cube - Ice Cube</actor>
      <actor>Malie - Ione Skye</actor>
      <actor>Joao - Rui Ricardo Diaz</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - John Billingsley</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503024000 +0500" stop="20260503041500 +0500">
    <title>Eileen</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1960s, Massachusetts.Eileen Dunlop (Thomasin McKenzie) works as a secretary at a reformatory for teenage boys.She lives with her widowed, alcohol-addicted father (Shea Whigham), a former police chief who suffers from paranoia and emotionally abuses her.The girl feels overwhelmed by anger and a sense of helplessness.He seeks refuge in the world of fantasy.The arrival of a new prison psychologist, the assertive and self-confident Rebecca (Anne Hathaway), causes her suppressed feelings to come to life.It seems that for the first time he has a chance for a real, deep relationship... The film's script is based on the novel by Ottessa Moshfegh.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>William Oldroyd</director>
      <actor>Eileen Dunlop - Thomasin McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Anne Hathaway</actor>
      <actor>Jim Dunlop - Shea Whigham</actor>
      <actor>Lee Polk - Sam Nivola</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Murray - Siobhan Fallon Hogan</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Stevens - Tonye Patano</actor>
      <actor>Intake Guard - William Hill</actor>
      <actor>Randy - Owen Teague</actor>
      <actor>Warden - Peter McRobbie</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Frye - Peter von Berg</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503041500 +0500" stop="20260503063500 +0500">
    <title>Kingdom of Heaven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12th century.The young blacksmith Balian (Orlando Bloom) loses his entire family in tragic circumstances.He begins to doubt the existence of God.Then he is visited by the crusader Godfrey of Ibelin (Liam Neeson), who turns out to be his father.He suggests his son learn knightly crafts.One day, Balian kills a priest in a fight.He must escape.Together with Godfrey, he sets off for Jerusalem.On the way, his father is killed by the bishop's men.Prudent King Baldwin IV (Edward Norton) and his advisor Tiberias (Jeremy Irons) strive for a peaceful solution.Thanks to them, there are no hostilities in Jerusalem.They even manage to reach a truce with the leader of the Muslims, Saladin (Ghassan Massoud).However, the ruler's conciliatory policy does not please some greedy and fanatical crusaders.Meanwhile, Balian falls in love with the king's sister, the already married princess Sibyl (Eva Green).The girl does not love her husband, Baron Guy de Lusignan (Marton Csokas).Soon the Crusaders start a war with the Muslims.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Balian - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Sybilla - Eva Green</actor>
      <actor>Tiberias - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Godfrey z Ibelinu - Liam Neeson</actor>
      <actor>Gravedigger - Martin Hancock</actor>
      <actor>Guy de Lusignan - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Reynald de Chatillon - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Stary Strażnik - Tim Barlow</actor>
      <actor>król Baldwin IV - Edward Norton</actor>
      <actor>Saladin - Ghassan Massoud</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503063500 +0500" stop="20260503090000 +0500">
    <title>Man on Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>American John Creasy (Denzel Washington) is a man haunted by nightmares from his past.He is a former assassin who worked for the CIA for many years.Frustrated, he avoids people and seeks solace in alcohol.Creasy comes to Mexico to visit his old friend and colleague, Rayburn (Christopher Walken).The city is currently gripped by a wave of kidnappings for ransom.Rich residents panic and many of them hire security guards to ensure the safety of their children.A friend finds John a job as a bodyguard for ten-year-old Pita Ramos (Dakota Fanning), the daughter of Mexican industrialist Samuel Ramos (Marc Anthony) and his American wife Lisa (Radha Mitchell).At first, Creasy has a hard time coping with the girl's presence.Over time, however, he becomes friends with her.Under its influence, he changes his attitude to life and gives up alcohol.Soon, however, little Pita is kidnapped.The desperate man does everything to save her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tony Scott</director>
      <actor>Creasy - Denzel Washington</actor>
      <actor>Rayburn - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Pita - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Samuel - Marc Anthony</actor>
      <actor>Lisa - Radha Mitchell</actor>
      <actor>Jordan - Mickey Rourke</actor>
      <actor>Manzano - Giancarlo Giannini</actor>
      <actor>Mariana - Rachel Ticotin</actor>
      <actor>Fuentes - Jesús Ochoa</actor>
      <actor>Sister Anna - Angelina Peláez</actor>
    </credits><date>2004</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503090000 +0500" stop="20260503110500 +0500">
    <title>P.S. I Love You</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the death of her husband Gerry (Gerard Butler), Holly (Hilary Swank) falls into a deep depression.On her 30th birthday, a woman receives a mysterious parcel.The cake comes with a tape with a recorded message from... Gerry.He encourages his beloved to go out and have fun with friends.After this event, new letters regularly arrived to the young widow, each ending with a declaration of love.Gerry knew how much his wife would suffer from losing him.In letters written before her death, he encourages her to take on various challenges.Thanks to her extraordinary sense of connection with the deceased, a woman in despair undergoes specific therapy and tries to start her life anew.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard LaGravenese</director>
      <actor>Holly - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Gerry - Gerard Butler</actor>
      <actor>Denise - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Gina Gershon</actor>
      <actor>John - James Marsters</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Kathy Bates</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Harry Connick Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Ciara - Nellie McKay</actor>
      <actor>William - Jeffrey Dean Morgan</actor>
      <actor>George - Christopher Whalen</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503110500 +0500" stop="20260503123500 +0500">
    <title>F+</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A family comedy aimed at teenagers.Ted (Wells Rappaport) and Josh (James Williams Jr.) are best friends and go to the Magnet School for Math and Science together.Ted is a star student, and Josh specializes in creating gadgets that they then use to prank others.After one of such antics, they are suspended.They must be careful because the next time will result in expulsion from school.The situation becomes more complicated when they fail the most important exam.The same fate befell Penny (Lily Jane), Ted's rival.Convinced that something was wrong with the test itself, they team up with a magician and a hacker to try to destroy the results during the school dance and give themselves a chance to improve.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kenny Beaumont</director>
      <actor>Terry Grimes - Randy Couture</actor>
      <actor>Gary Garrie - Tommy Davidson</actor>
      <actor>Principal Sandra Neely - Jennifer Esposito</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Barker - Ettore Ewen</actor>
      <actor>Ted Freeman - Wells Rappaport</actor>
      <actor>Penny Pritchard - Lily Jane</actor>
      <actor>Josh Barker - James Williams Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Gertz Neely - Lily Tricano</actor>
      <actor>The Amazing Chad - Cade Clark</actor>
      <actor>Hannah Freeman - Erin Cline</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503123500 +0500" stop="20260503130000 +0500">
    <title>Scared Shrekless</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Halloween is coming.This year, Shrek's favorite holiday is going to be really scary.Instead of traditional fun, refreshments and tricks, the ogre challenges his friends.Together with Fiona, Donkey, Puss in Boots and other fairy tale characters, he plans to spend the night in Lord Farquaad's haunted castle.The atmosphere of horror is to be fueled by spine-chilling stories.The one who overcomes his fear will win the competition.Biscuits, Donkey, Puss in Boots and Shrek tell dark stories... In the Polish version, the characters are voiced by famous actors, including:Zbigniew Zamachowski (Shrek) and Jerzy Stuhr (Donkey).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gary Trousdale</director>
      <director>Raman Hui</director>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503130000 +0500" stop="20260503152000 +0500">
    <title>War for the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The situation of the mutant monkeys changes with the appearance of a formation led by the Colonel, which seeks to take control of the apes.Meanwhile, Blue Eyes informs his father that he has found a place for their tribe to live.The decision is made to march.Under the cover of darkness, an attack occurs.Caesar's son and wife are killed.Despite the tragedy, the primate leader believes in the success of a peaceful solution.On his own, he searches for the person responsible for the massacre, but falls into the hands of the enemy.He then finds out that his compatriots were forced to work as slaves.People are attacked by a virus that reverses the process of evolution.The final showdown is inevitably approaching.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Reeves</director>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>The Colonel - Woody Harrelson</actor>
      <actor>Bad Ape - Steve Zahn</actor>
      <actor>Maurice - Karin Konoval</actor>
      <actor>Nova - Amiah Miller</actor>
      <actor>Rocket - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Red Donkey - Ty Olsson</actor>
      <actor>Luca - Michael Adamthwaite</actor>
      <actor>Koba - Toby Kebbell</actor>
      <actor>Preacher - Gabriel Chavarria</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503152000 +0500" stop="20260503171500 +0500">
    <title>Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Four high school students, as part of a punishment imposed by the principal, have to clean up the cluttered school basement.The collected items include an old console from the 1990s and the Jumanji game.Intrigued, the teenagers decide to activate the device.In this way, they are drawn into the virtual world.They end up in a dangerous jungle, where, as avatars, they are forced to fight for survival.Spencer becomes a brave adventurer, Fridge turns into a zoologist, Bethany becomes a corpulent paleontology professor who knows his way around maps, and Martha becomes a martial arts expert.On their way, they meet a guide who tells them the purpose of the mission.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Kasdan</director>
      <actor>Spencer - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Fridge - Kevin Hart</actor>
      <actor>Bethany - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Martha - Karen Gillan</actor>
      <actor>Nigel - Rhys Darby</actor>
      <actor>Van Pelt - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Alex - Nick Jonas</actor>
      <actor>Młody Spencer - Alex Wolff</actor>
      <actor>Młody Fridge - Ser'Darius Blain</actor>
      <actor>Młoda Bethany - Madison Iseman</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503171500 +0500" stop="20260503191500 +0500">
    <title>Another Simple Favor</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Emily Nelson (Blake Lively), who was sentenced to 20 years in prison, regains her freedom.She is planning a wedding on the island of Capri, and an old friend becomes her bridesmaid.A crime occurs during the ceremony.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Paul Feig</director>
      <actor>Emily Nelson - Blake Lively</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Smothers - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Miles Smothers - Joshua Satine</actor>
      <actor>Swim Coach - Mitch Salm</actor>
      <actor>Darren - Andrew Rannells</actor>
      <actor>Lulu - Diletta Jayne</actor>
      <actor>Camp Counselor Val - Holmes</actor>
      <actor>Sona - Aparna Nancherla</actor>
      <actor>Stacy - Kelly McCormack</actor>
      <actor>Vicky - Alex Newell</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503191500 +0500" stop="20260503212000 +0500">
    <title>Green Book</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>USA, 1960s. Tony Vallelonga, a simple resident of the Bronx who has a wife and a group of children to support, agrees to accompany, as a chauffeur and bodyguard, a black musician - the luxurious erudite Donald Shirley - on a concert tour across the United States.Not only does he have to defend his protégé from troubles in the Deep South, but he also has to combat prejudiced views.During their journey, they both follow the instructions from the "Green Book" guide for African Americans traveling around the country.It includes, among others:suggestions on where to sleep and eat to avoid unpleasant incidents.The time spent together and overcoming mounting problems cause a surprising, lasting bond to emerge between men from different worlds.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Farrelly</director>
      <actor>Tony Lip - Viggo Mortensen</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Donald Shirley - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Dolores - Linda Cardellini</actor>
      <actor>Johnny Venere - Sebastian Maniscalco</actor>
      <actor>Oleg - Dimiter D. Marinov</actor>
      <actor>George Dyer - the Cellist - Mike Hatton</actor>
      <actor>Record Exec - P.J. Byrne</actor>
      <actor>Gio Loscudo - Joe Cortese</actor>
      <actor>Copa Coat Check Girl - Maggie Nixon</actor>
      <actor>Bobby Rydell - Von Lewis</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503212000 +0500" stop="20260503230000 +0500">
    <title>By sleeping with others</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lainey and Jake had only slept together once, but it was the first and most important time in their lives.But then the lovers parted ways.A few years later, they accidentally bump into each other...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Leslye Headland</director>
      <actor>Lainey - Alison Brie</actor>
      <actor>Jake - Jason Sudeikis</actor>
      <actor>R.A. - Jordan Carlos</actor>
      <actor>Hannah - Margarita Levieva</actor>
      <actor>Helmet Kid - Charles Cain</actor>
      <actor>Sam - Adam Brody</actor>
      <actor>Attentive Waiter - Michael Cyril Creighton</actor>
      <actor>SLAA Speaker - Billy Eichner</actor>
      <actor>Xander - Jason Mantzoukas</actor>
      <actor>Thea - Margaret Odette</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260503230000 +0500" stop="20260504003500 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brave Po opens a new chapter in his life - he is to become the spiritual leader of the Valley of Peace.He's trying to get used to his new role.In addition, the voracious bear must find a daredevil who will replace him as the Dragon Warrior.Not everything goes according to plan.This time, China's security is threatened by Chameleon, who wields black magic and can take on any form and take over the abilities of old masters.With the help of a smart vixen and former thief, Zhen, the panda bear must face her.But they need allies to defeat the shape-shifting witch and the sinister army behind her.The time of a merciless fight is inevitably approaching... The voices of the characters include, among others:Marcin Hycnar, Jan Peszek, Wiktor Zborowski and Julia Chatys.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Mitchell</director>
      <director>Stephanie Stine</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>