<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505045000 +0500" stop="20260505063000 +0500">
    <title>One to One: John &amp; Yoko</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The story of a famous couple of artists, focusing on the One to One charity concert that took place at Madison Square Garden on August 30, 1972.From 1971, John Lennon and Yoko Ono lived in New York, in Greenwich Village, for 18 months.Their then apartment was reconstructed for the film.Private film, photo and music archives of artists and friends were also used, as well as FBI tapes to show their fate and the company they kept in: from Allen Ginsberg to Jerry Rubin and activist AJ Weberman.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kevin Macdonald</director>
      <director>Sam Rice-Edwards</director>
      <actor>Self - John Lennon</actor>
      <actor>Self - Yoko Ono</actor>
      <actor>Themselves - The Plastic Ono Elephants Memory Band</actor>
      <actor>Self - Jerry Rubin</actor>
      <actor>Self - Andy Warhol</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505063000 +0500" stop="20260505082000 +0500">
    <title>Elysium</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 2154. Los Angeles resembles a landfill.People are struggling to survive on a devastated Earth, full of violence and poverty.Rich people live on the Elysium space station.Among the technologies available to them are medical capsules that cure diseases.One day, Max Da Costa, who lives in the slums, is heavily irradiated as a result of an accident at a factory.The dose is lethal.He has five days left.He realizes that only the capsule can save him.So he visits the smuggler Spider, hoping that thanks to him he will get to Elysium.The man promises help on the condition that he will kidnap the wealthy Carlyle for him.The dying Da Costa's body is enhanced with new technology.He soon comes into possession of secret information that could destroy the current order.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Neill Blomkamp</director>
      <actor>Max - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Delacourt - Jodie Foster</actor>
      <actor>Kruger - Sharlto Copley</actor>
      <actor>Frey - Alice Braga</actor>
      <actor>Julio - Diego Luna</actor>
      <actor>Spider - Wagner Moura</actor>
      <actor>John Carlyle - William Fichtner</actor>
      <actor>Drake - Brandon Auret</actor>
      <actor>Crowe - Josh Blacker</actor>
      <actor>Matilda - Emma Tremblay</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Dramat Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505082000 +0500" stop="20260505090000 +0500">
    <title>The Devil Is Busy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The everyday life of the head of security at an abortion clinic in Atlanta.A deeply religious believer, Tracy begins each workday with prayer.Her commitment to defending women's rights does not compromise.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Geeta Gandbhir</director>
      <director>Christalyn Hampton</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505090000 +0500" stop="20260505093000 +0500">
    <title>Monsters vs Aliens: Mutant Pumpkins from Outer Space</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Susan Murphy and a group of friendly monsters undertake another mission.Just before Halloween, a trace of aliens was found in the girl's hometown.Everything looked normal though.Unexpectedly, on the day of the holiday, the innocent-looking pumpkin lanterns reveal their true colors.It turns out to be an invasion of aliens who plan to conquer Earth.Susan, called Ginormica, and a team of "freaks of nature" start a fight against mutated pumpkins... In the Polish language version, the characters provided their voices, among others:Barbara Kałużna, Wojciech Paszkowski and Grzegorz Pawlak.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Ramsey</director>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505093000 +0500" stop="20260505095500 +0500">
    <title>Secrets of the Furious Five</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After defeating Tai Lung, Po the panda gains the title of Dragon Warrior.Master Shifu assigns the bear another task - to teach kung fu.Enthusiastic bunnies become new adepts of the eastern martial art.In addition to improving his technique, Po must instill in the children the philosophy of kung-fu and character traits such as courage, self-confidence and patience.To achieve the goal, he tells them stories from the past of great warriors - the Crane, the Viper, the Tigress, the Monkey and the Mantis... In the Polish language version, they lent their voices to characters including:Marcin Hycnar (Po) and Jan Peszek (Shifu).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Raman Hui</director>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505095500 +0500" stop="20260505113500 +0500">
    <title>Sarah Bernhardt, la divine</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The beginning of the 20th century.The outstanding French actress Sarah Bernhardt (Sandrine Kiberlain) is considered one of the most important artists of her time and has the status of an international star.Her admirers include Oscar Wilde, Alfons Mucha and Victor Hugo.Her talent and extraordinary charisma, as well as her courage and extravagant lifestyle are widely admired.The actress disrupted social norms and shocked her contemporaries with her unusual preferences and numerous love affairs.She was a declared opponent of anti-Semitism.Fate connected her most closely with the actor Lucien Guitry (Laurent Lafitte) and the painter Louise Abbéma (Amira Casar).Since her fateful fall on stage in 1905 in Rio de Janeiro, Divine Sarah has been struggling with terrible knee pain, which over the years has made it impossible for her to move.In order to be able to perform, after a decade, the actress makes a dramatic decision.Full of passion and inner strength, the artist will forever be remembered in the history of art and culture.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Guillaume Nicloux</director>
      <actor>Sarah Bernhardt - Sandrine Kiberlain</actor>
      <actor>Lucien Guitry - Laurent Lafitte</actor>
      <actor>Louise Abbéma - Amira Casar</actor>
      <actor>Suzanne - Pauline Etienne</actor>
      <actor>Charlotte Lyses - Mathilde Ollivier</actor>
      <actor>Pitou - Laurent Stocker</actor>
      <actor>Maurice Bernhardt - Grégoire Leprince-Ringuet</actor>
      <actor>Georges Clairin - Clément Hervieu-Léger</actor>
      <actor>Samuel Pozzi - Sébastien Pouderoux</actor>
      <actor>Emile Zola - Arthur Igual</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505113500 +0500" stop="20260505130000 +0500">
    <title>A Carpenter Christmas Romance</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Writer Andrea returns to her family farm in Wildwood just before the holidays.She begins an affair with her ex-boyfriend Seth, who was employed in the crew renovating the town after the recent fire.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Helgren</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505130000 +0500" stop="20260505144000 +0500">
    <title>By sleeping with others</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lainey and Jake had only slept together once, but it was the first and most important time in their lives.But then the lovers parted ways.A few years later, they accidentally bump into each other...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Leslye Headland</director>
      <actor>Lainey - Alison Brie</actor>
      <actor>Jake - Jason Sudeikis</actor>
      <actor>R.A. - Jordan Carlos</actor>
      <actor>Hannah - Margarita Levieva</actor>
      <actor>Helmet Kid - Charles Cain</actor>
      <actor>Sam - Adam Brody</actor>
      <actor>Attentive Waiter - Michael Cyril Creighton</actor>
      <actor>SLAA Speaker - Billy Eichner</actor>
      <actor>Xander - Jason Mantzoukas</actor>
      <actor>Thea - Margaret Odette</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505144000 +0500" stop="20260505154500 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E9</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505154500 +0500" stop="20260505173000 +0500">
    <title>Focus</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nicky Spurgeon is a calculating fraud.The model's appearance and ability to keep cool make him a master criminal.He is able to win people over, but he does it to take advantage of them.One day, in a restaurant, he meets a fair-haired beauty, Jess Barrett, whose ambition is to pursue a criminal career.He becomes her mentor.Over time, they both realize that they have much more in common than the relationship of master and disciple.However, they live in a world where there is no place for love.Spurgeon ends this relationship.Three years pass.Nicky is in Buenos Aires, where he works for the owner of a car racing team, Rafael Garrigi.He meets his former lover here.Aware of her strengths, the femme fatale has one goal - to take revenge for the way she was once treated.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Glenn Ficarra</director>
      <director>John Requa</director>
      <actor>Nicky - Will Smith</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Margot Robbie</actor>
      <actor>Farhad - Adrian Martinez</actor>
      <actor>Owens - Gerald McRaney</actor>
      <actor>Garriga - Rodrigo Santoro</actor>
      <actor>Liyuan - BD Wong</actor>
      <actor>Horst - Brennan Brown</actor>
      <actor>McEwen - Robert Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Gordon - Dotan Bonen</actor>
      <actor>Gareth - Griff Furst</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505173000 +0500" stop="20260505194500 +0500">
    <title>The Karate Kid</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sherry Parker (Taraji P. Henson) is offered a job in Beijing.He goes there with his son Dre (Jaden Smith).The boy cannot acclimatize to the new surroundings.For this reason, he often comes into conflict with his school friends.He is also persecuted by them.One day, Dre meets Mr. Han (Jackie Chan), the caretaker of the building where he lives with his mother.The man decides to teach the boy martial arts so that he can defend himself against his peers who bully him.Many hours of training create a unique bond between them, much stronger than ordinary teacher-student relationships.The film's script loosely refers to John G. Avildsen's work from 1984.The production received nominations for the Teen and People's Choice awards, Czarny Repules and the Golden Popcorn award.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Harald Zwart</director>
      <actor>Dre Parker - Jaden Smith</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Sherry Parker - Taraji P. Henson</actor>
      <actor>Meiying - Wenwen Han</actor>
      <actor>Master Li - Rongguang Yu</actor>
      <actor>Meiying's Dad - Zhensu Wu</actor>
      <actor>Meiying's Mom - Zhiheng Wang</actor>
      <actor>Cheng - Zhenwei Wang</actor>
      <actor>Dre's Detroit Friend - Jared Minns</actor>
      <actor>Liang - Shijia Lü</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505194500 +0500" stop="20260505212500 +0500">
    <title>Silver Star</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>African American Billie (Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson) is twenty years old and a tomboy.He comes from a military family and is missing one eye.After serving her prison sentence, she discovers that her separated parents are facing eviction.He decides to prevent this at all costs.The woman decides to rob a bank, but the action ends in failure.As a result, the young criminal takes her client hostage.Pregnant Franny (Grace Van Dien) is eighteen years old and has a head open to crazy ideas.Together they escape and set off on an adventurous journey.At one point, Franny offers Billie an unexpected deal.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ruben Amar</director>
      <director>Lola Bessis</director>
      <actor>Franny - Grace Van Dien</actor>
      <actor>Billie - Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tyrone Sands - Johnath Davis</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Woodman - Getchie Argetsinger</actor>
      <actor>Shonda - Tamara Fruits</actor>
      <actor>Alice - Ekaterina Baker</actor>
      <actor>Dylan - Joey Giambattista</actor>
      <actor>William Bortschstoecker - Josh Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Clark - Amy Tribbey</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Noa Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505212500 +0500" stop="20260505230000 +0500">
    <title>Bastille Day</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>On the eve of Bastille Day, an American thief living in Paris, Michael Mason (Richard Madden), steals a bag containing a teddy bear.Not knowing that there is a bomb hidden inside the toy, he takes the money and documents and throws the rest into a trash bin in a crowded Paris metro station.A few seconds later there is a huge explosion.Four people die.City surveillance footage reveals Michael's face.The police, considering him a terrorist, start searching for him.He is stopped by CIA agent Sean Briar (Idris Elba), who is just trying to find his way back to work after returning from Iraq.He brings the suspect to a secret interrogation room.Michael explains the misunderstanding and convinces that someone else is behind the attack.He and Sean have 24 hours to find the real culprits.The film was shot in 2015 and became even more relevant after the attacks in Paris.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>James Watkins</director>
      <actor>Sean Briar - Idris Elba</actor>
      <actor>Michael Mason - Richard Madden</actor>
      <actor>Zoe - Charlotte Le Bon</actor>
      <actor>Karen Dacre - Kelly Reilly</actor>
      <actor>Victor Gamieux - José Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Rafi Bertrand - Thierry Godard</actor>
      <actor>Yannick Bertrand - Vincent Londez</actor>
      <actor>Jean - Arieh Worthalter</actor>
      <actor>Christophe - Mohamed Makhtoumi</actor>
      <actor>Xavier - Théo Costa-Marini</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505230000 +0500" stop="20260505235500 +0500">
    <title>Heated Rivalry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two ice hockey players, Shane Hollander (Hudson Williams) and Ilya Rozanov (Connor Storrie), are united not only by ambition and the need for competition, but also by a magnetic attraction that neither of them fully understands.What begins as a secret romance between two debutants turns into an extraordinary love journey.Athletes spend eight years chasing fame on the ice rink while trying to deal with their feelings off it.They must decide whether there is room for something as fragile as love in a world of brutal competition.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Jacob Tierney</director>
      <actor>Shane Hollander - Hudson Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ilya Rozanov - Connor Storrie</actor>
      <actor>Scott Hunter - François Arnaud</actor>
      <actor>Yuna Hollander - Christina Chang</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Marleau - Franco Lo Presti</actor>
      <actor>Hayden Pike - Callan Potter</actor>
      <actor>Svetlana - Ksenia Daniela Kharlamova</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #2 - Shaun Starr</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #1 - Conor McKenna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260505235500 +0500" stop="20260506005500 +0500">
    <title>Half Man</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1980s. The life of bullied teenage Niall (Mitchell Robertson) turns upside down when the son of his mother's partner, the fierce and unpredictable Ruben (Stuart Campbell), comes to live with them for a while.Even though they are not related by blood, over time they both become inseparable.However, subsequent events make them move away from each other.Three decades later, Ruben (Richard Gadd) shows up uninvited at Niall's (Jamie Bell) wedding.It soon becomes clear why he reconnected with his long-lost brother.A suggestive story about the fragility of male relationships, brotherhood, betrayal, loyalty and violence.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Ruben - Richard Gadd</actor>
      <actor>Niall - Jamie Bell</actor>
      <actor>Lori - Neve McIntosh</actor>
      <actor>Maura - Marianne McIvor</actor>
      <actor>Alby - Charlie de Melo</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Tim Downie</actor>
      <actor>Ava - Anjli Mohindra</actor>
      <actor>Butch - Tom Andrews</actor>
      <actor>Mona - Amy Manson</actor>
      <actor>Young Ruben - Stuart Campbell</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506005500 +0500" stop="20260506020500 +0500">
    <title>House of the Dragon 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Rhaenyra the Cruel</sub-title>
    <desc>The second series of the production, the events of which precede the action of "Game of Thrones".After the death of Lucerys Velaryon, the son of Queen Rhaenyra Targaryen (Emma D'Arcy), which was caused by his cousin, Aemond Targaryen (Ewan Mitchell), Westeros finds itself on the brink of a bloody civil war.The Green Council supporting King Aegon (Tom Glynn-Carney) and Queen Rhaenyra's Black Council are fighting for influence.Each side claims the Iron Throne.The dynamic development of events also affects the attitude of Rhaenyra's husband, Daemon (Matt Smith), in life.A man who spends a lot of time in Harrenhal Castle, away from his wife, changes a lot.In addition, the demons of his past begin to haunt him.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Clare Kilner</director>
      <actor>King Aegon II Targaryen - Tom Glynn-Carney</actor>
      <actor>Princess Rhaenys Targaryen - Eve Best</actor>
      <actor>Lord Corlys 'The Sea Snake' Velaryon - Steve Toussaint</actor>
      <actor>Queen Rhaenyra Targaryen - Emma D'Arcy</actor>
      <actor>Prince Daemon Targaryen - Matt Smith</actor>
      <actor>Queen Alicent Hightower - Olivia Cooke</actor>
      <actor>Prince Aemond Targaryen - Ewan Mitchell</actor>
      <actor>Ser Criston Cole - Fabien Frankel</actor>
      <actor>Ser Otto Hightower - Rhys Ifans</actor>
      <actor>Ser Harrold Westerling - Graham McTavish</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Serial Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506020500 +0500" stop="20260506041500 +0500">
    <title>Bastarden</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Year 1755, Denmark.The impoverished Captain Ludvig (Mads Mikkelsen) asks the king for permission to establish a colony on his behalf on the barren moors famous for their infertility.If successful, he expects to be awarded a knighthood and property.The aristocrats are outraged by his arrogance and assume defeat, but he receives consent.From then on, every day for Ludvig and his relatives is spent on hard, physical work beyond their strength, which will allow them to prepare the land for cultivation.They also hire people to help them - two runaway servants: Ann Barbara (Amanda Collin) and her husband.Months pass and the first buildings are built when the ruthless Frederik de Schinkel (Simon Bennebjerg), the land lord, tries to take over the moors.When Ludvig rejects his offer, he decides to destroy it.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nikolaj Arcel</director>
      <actor>Ludvig Kahlen - Mads Mikkelsen</actor>
      <actor>Ann Barbara - Amanda Collin</actor>
      <actor>Frederik De Schinkel - Simon Bennebjerg</actor>
      <actor>Anmai Mus - Melina Hagberg</actor>
      <actor>Edel Helene - Kristine Kujath Thorp</actor>
      <actor>Anton Eklund - Gustav Lindh</actor>
      <actor>Johannes Eriksen - Morten Hee Andersen</actor>
      <actor>Bondo - Thomas W. Gabrielsson</actor>
      <actor>Trappaud - Jacob Lohmann</actor>
      <actor>Hector - Magnus Krepper</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506041500 +0500" stop="20260506064000 +0500">
    <title>Man on Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>American John Creasy (Denzel Washington) is a man haunted by nightmares from his past.He is a former assassin who worked for the CIA for many years.Frustrated, he avoids people and seeks solace in alcohol.Creasy comes to Mexico to visit his old friend and colleague, Rayburn (Christopher Walken).The city is currently gripped by a wave of kidnappings for ransom.Rich residents panic and many of them hire security guards to ensure the safety of their children.A friend finds John a job as a bodyguard for ten-year-old Pita Ramos (Dakota Fanning), the daughter of Mexican industrialist Samuel Ramos (Marc Anthony) and his American wife Lisa (Radha Mitchell).At first, Creasy has a hard time coping with the girl's presence.Over time, however, he becomes friends with her.Under its influence, he changes his attitude to life and gives up alcohol.Soon, however, little Pita is kidnapped.The desperate man does everything to save her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tony Scott</director>
      <actor>Creasy - Denzel Washington</actor>
      <actor>Rayburn - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Pita - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Samuel - Marc Anthony</actor>
      <actor>Lisa - Radha Mitchell</actor>
      <actor>Jordan - Mickey Rourke</actor>
      <actor>Manzano - Giancarlo Giannini</actor>
      <actor>Mariana - Rachel Ticotin</actor>
      <actor>Fuentes - Jesús Ochoa</actor>
      <actor>Sister Anna - Angelina Peláez</actor>
    </credits><date>2004</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506064000 +0500" stop="20260506090000 +0500">
    <title>The Martian</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A mission to the Red Planet is interrupted by a sandstorm.A team of astronauts evacuates to Earth, leaving one of the expedition members, Mark Watney (Matt Damon), on the surface of Mars, believing he is dead.After some time, the seriously injured astronaut regains consciousness.He realizes that his air and food supplies will soon be exhausted.He also cannot count on a rescue mission because he was presumed dead.Despite this, he tries to survive in difficult conditions and notify the inhabitants of Earth that he is alive and waiting for help.Ridley Scott's film is nominated for an Oscar in seven categories, including:as the best film and for the leading role of Matt Damon.Director Ridley Scott, the creator of such cult sci-fi films as "Blade Runner" and the Alien series, was a candidate for the Academy Award four times.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Mark Watney - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Melissa Lewis - Jessica Chastain</actor>
      <actor>Annie Montrose - Kristen Wiig</actor>
      <actor>Teddy Sanders - Jeff Daniels</actor>
      <actor>Rick Martinez - Michael Pena</actor>
      <actor>Mitch Henderson - Sean Bean</actor>
      <actor>Beth Johanssen - Kate Mara</actor>
      <actor>Chris Beck - Sebastian Stan</actor>
      <actor>Alex Vogel - Aksel Hennie</actor>
      <actor>Vincent Kapoor - Chiwetel Ejiofor</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506090000 +0500" stop="20260506102500 +0500">
    <title>A Royal Christmas Ballet</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Former ballet dancer Carrie (Brittany Underwood) is to prepare a performance of "The Nutcracker" on the occasion of a visit from a foreign delegation.While working on the play, she becomes involved in an affair.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Fred Olen Ray</director>
      <actor>Carrie - Brittany Underwood</actor>
      <actor>William - Jonathan Stoddard</actor>
      <actor>Marilyn - Julie Stevens</actor>
      <actor>Medea - Daniela Couso</actor>
      <actor>Jane - Monaye Moyes</actor>
      <actor>Colin - Allen Guy</actor>
      <actor>Audrey - Mary-Kate O'Connell</actor>
      <actor>Victoria - Elizabeth Tobias</actor>
      <actor>Becky - Linda Mesi</actor>
      <actor>Mike - Peter Johnson</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506102500 +0500" stop="20260506120500 +0500">
    <title>Broke</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Former rodeo champion True cannot accept the end of his career.He is surprised by a violent blizzard.He fights for survival.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Carlyle Eubank</director>
      <actor>True Brandywine - Wyatt Russell</actor>
      <actor>Ali - Auden Thornton</actor>
      <actor>George Brandywine - Dennis Quaid</actor>
      <actor>Kathy Brandywine - Mary McDonnell</actor>
      <actor>Caleb Brandywine - Johnny Berchtold</actor>
      <actor>Cliff - Tom Skerritt</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506120500 +0500" stop="20260506134500 +0500">
    <title>Silver Star</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>African American Billie (Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson) is twenty years old and a tomboy.He comes from a military family and is missing one eye.After serving her prison sentence, she discovers that her separated parents are facing eviction.He decides to prevent this at all costs.The woman decides to rob a bank, but the action ends in failure.As a result, the young criminal takes her client hostage.Pregnant Franny (Grace Van Dien) is eighteen years old and has a head open to crazy ideas.Together they escape and set off on an adventurous journey.At one point, Franny offers Billie an unexpected deal.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ruben Amar</director>
      <director>Lola Bessis</director>
      <actor>Franny - Grace Van Dien</actor>
      <actor>Billie - Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tyrone Sands - Johnath Davis</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Woodman - Getchie Argetsinger</actor>
      <actor>Shonda - Tamara Fruits</actor>
      <actor>Alice - Ekaterina Baker</actor>
      <actor>Dylan - Joey Giambattista</actor>
      <actor>William Bortschstoecker - Josh Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Clark - Amy Tribbey</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Noa Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506134500 +0500" stop="20260506154500 +0500">
    <title>Vinci 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Cuma receives an offer to participate in a new heist.At first he refuses, but changes his mind when he learns that his old rival, Chudy, is planning a spectacular robbery in Krakow without his participation.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Juliusz Machulski</director>
      <actor>Robert Cumiński Cuma - Robert Więckiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Julian Wolniewicz Szerszeń - Borys Szyc</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Kamilla Baar</actor>
      <actor>komisarz Łukasz Wilk - Marcin Dorociński</actor>
      <actor>paser Chudy - Mirosław Haniszewski</actor>
      <actor>Marcin Kudra - Łukasz Simlat</actor>
      <actor>Jan Bednarek Werbus - Jacek Król</actor>
      <actor>Kazu Tanaka - Masakazu Miyanaga</actor>
      <actor>kurator Zjawińska - Ilona Ostrowska</actor>
      <actor>Helmut - Krzysztof Stelmaszyk</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506154500 +0500" stop="20260506173000 +0500">
    <title>In short</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2019, on the threshold of the pandemic.Single woman Ellen (Laura Tonke) spends New Year's Eve with her friends.No one knows that she is having an affair with Sebastian (Ronald Zehrfeld), Eva's (Antje Traue) husband.Rolf (Nicholas Ofczarek) and Dina (Pegah Ferydoni) make a perfect couple, unlike Mareike (Annette Frier) and Adam (Trystan Pütter).Maya (Katia Fellin) wants children, Natalie (Jasmin Shakeri) cannot decide.Max (Henning Flüsloh) comes into Ellen's life and he would love her if she let him.Years pass.The woman attends various types of celebrations, birthday parties and casual social gatherings.He learns about events in his friends' lives.The sense of community unites and allows everyone to return to everyday life with positive energy.Remake of the Danish film "A Long Story Briefly".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Dietl</director>
      <actor>Ellen - Laura Tonke</actor>
      <actor>Natalie - Jasmin Shakeri</actor>
      <actor>Mareike - Annette Frier</actor>
      <actor>Rolf - Nicholas Ofczarek</actor>
      <actor>Max - Henning Flüsloh</actor>
      <actor>Adam - Trystan Pütter</actor>
      <actor>Maya - Katia Fellin</actor>
      <actor>Sebastian - Ronald Zehrfeld</actor>
      <actor>Dina - Pegah Ferydoni</actor>
      <actor>Becky - Marlene Tanczik</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506173000 +0500" stop="20260506190500 +0500">
    <title>Karate Kid: Legends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li Fong's friend needs help.He decided to take part in a karate tournament, but his skills are insufficient.Teacher Han turns to the legendary Daniel LaRusso for help.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Li Fong - Ben Wang</actor>
      <actor>Victor Lipani - Joshua Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Mia Lipani - Sadie Stanley</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Fong - Ming-Na</actor>
      <actor>Alan - Wyatt Oleff</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Aramis Knight</actor>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Young Girl - Olivia Yang Avis</actor>
      <actor>Young Student - Aaron Wang</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506190500 +0500" stop="20260506212500 +0500">
    <title>Kingdom of Heaven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12th century.The young blacksmith Balian (Orlando Bloom) loses his entire family in tragic circumstances.He begins to doubt the existence of God.Then he is visited by the crusader Godfrey of Ibelin (Liam Neeson), who turns out to be his father.He suggests his son learn knightly crafts.One day, Balian kills a priest in a fight.He must escape.Together with Godfrey, he sets off for Jerusalem.On the way, his father is killed by the bishop's men.Prudent King Baldwin IV (Edward Norton) and his advisor Tiberias (Jeremy Irons) strive for peaceful solutions.Thanks to them, there are no hostilities in Jerusalem.They even manage to reach a truce with the leader of the Muslims, Saladin (Ghassan Massoud).However, the ruler's conciliatory policy does not please some greedy and fanatical crusaders.Meanwhile, Balian falls in love with the king's sister, the already married princess Sibyl (Eva Green).The girl does not love her husband, Baron Guy de Lusignan (Marton Csokas).Soon the Crusaders start a war with the Muslims.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Balian - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Sybilla - Eva Green</actor>
      <actor>Tiberias - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Godfrey z Ibelinu - Liam Neeson</actor>
      <actor>Gravedigger - Martin Hancock</actor>
      <actor>Guy de Lusignan - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Reynald de Chatillon - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Stary Strażnik - Tim Barlow</actor>
      <actor>król Baldwin IV - Edward Norton</actor>
      <actor>Saladin - Ghassan Massoud</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506212500 +0500" stop="20260506230000 +0500">
    <title>Anaconda</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Doug (Jack Black) and Griff (Paul Rudd) have been friends since childhood.They have always dreamed of making a remake of their favorite film, the horror film "Anaconda".When both buddies experience a midlife crisis, they decide not to wait any longer and set off together deep into the Amazon to start filming.The situation becomes more complicated when... a real giant anaconda appears on the film set, spreading chaos and destruction around.Despite the deadly threat, the friends decide to take advantage of the predator's presence.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tom Gormican</director>
      <actor>Doug McCallister - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Ronald Griffin Jr. - Paul Rudd</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Trent - Steve Zahn</actor>
      <actor>Claire Simons - Thandie Newton</actor>
      <actor>Ana Almeida - Daniela Melchior</actor>
      <actor>Santiago Braga - Selton Mello</actor>
      <actor>Ice Cube - Ice Cube</actor>
      <actor>Malie - Ione Skye</actor>
      <actor>Joao - Rui Ricardo Diaz</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - John Billingsley</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506230000 +0500" stop="20260507003500 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brave Po opens a new chapter in his life - he is to become the spiritual leader of the Valley of Peace.He's trying to get used to his new role.In addition, the voracious bear must find a daredevil who will replace him as the Dragon Warrior.Not everything goes according to plan.This time, China's security is threatened by Chameleon, who wields black magic and can take on any form and take over the abilities of old masters.With the help of a smart vixen and former thief, Zhen, the panda bear must face her.But they need allies to defeat the shape-shifting witch and the sinister army behind her.The time of a merciless fight is inevitably approaching... The voices of the characters include, among others:Marcin Hycnar, Jan Peszek, Wiktor Zborowski and Julia Chatys.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Mitchell</director>
      <director>Stephanie Stine</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>