<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506020500 +0500" stop="20260506041500 +0500">
    <title>Bastarden</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Year 1755, Denmark.The impoverished Captain Ludvig (Mads Mikkelsen) asks the king for permission to establish a colony on his behalf on the barren moors famous for their infertility.If successful, he expects to be awarded a knighthood and property.The aristocrats are outraged by his arrogance and assume defeat, but he receives consent.From then on, every day for Ludvig and his relatives is spent on hard, physical work beyond their strength, which will allow them to prepare the land for cultivation.They also hire people to help them - two runaway servants: Ann Barbara (Amanda Collin) and her husband.Months pass and the first buildings are built when the ruthless Frederik de Schinkel (Simon Bennebjerg), the land lord, tries to take over the moors.When Ludvig rejects his offer, he decides to destroy it.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nikolaj Arcel</director>
      <actor>Ludvig Kahlen - Mads Mikkelsen</actor>
      <actor>Ann Barbara - Amanda Collin</actor>
      <actor>Frederik De Schinkel - Simon Bennebjerg</actor>
      <actor>Anmai Mus - Melina Hagberg</actor>
      <actor>Edel Helene - Kristine Kujath Thorp</actor>
      <actor>Anton Eklund - Gustav Lindh</actor>
      <actor>Johannes Eriksen - Morten Hee Andersen</actor>
      <actor>Bondo - Thomas W. Gabrielsson</actor>
      <actor>Trappaud - Jacob Lohmann</actor>
      <actor>Hector - Magnus Krepper</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506041500 +0500" stop="20260506064000 +0500">
    <title>Man on Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>American John Creasy (Denzel Washington) is a man haunted by nightmares from his past.He is a former assassin who worked for the CIA for many years.Frustrated, he avoids people and seeks solace in alcohol.Creasy comes to Mexico to visit his old friend and colleague, Rayburn (Christopher Walken).The city is currently gripped by a wave of kidnappings for ransom.Rich residents panic and many of them hire security guards to ensure the safety of their children.A friend finds John a job as a bodyguard for ten-year-old Pita Ramos (Dakota Fanning), the daughter of Mexican industrialist Samuel Ramos (Marc Anthony) and his American wife Lisa (Radha Mitchell).At first, Creasy has a hard time coping with the girl's presence.Over time, however, he becomes friends with her.Under its influence, he changes his attitude to life and gives up alcohol.Soon, however, little Pita is kidnapped.The desperate man does everything to save her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tony Scott</director>
      <actor>Creasy - Denzel Washington</actor>
      <actor>Rayburn - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Pita - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Samuel - Marc Anthony</actor>
      <actor>Lisa - Radha Mitchell</actor>
      <actor>Jordan - Mickey Rourke</actor>
      <actor>Manzano - Giancarlo Giannini</actor>
      <actor>Mariana - Rachel Ticotin</actor>
      <actor>Fuentes - Jesús Ochoa</actor>
      <actor>Sister Anna - Angelina Peláez</actor>
    </credits><date>2004</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506064000 +0500" stop="20260506090000 +0500">
    <title>The Martian</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A mission to the Red Planet is interrupted by a sandstorm.A team of astronauts evacuates to Earth, leaving one of the expedition members, Mark Watney (Matt Damon), on the surface of Mars, believing he is dead.After some time, the seriously injured astronaut regains consciousness.He realizes that his air and food supplies will soon be exhausted.He also cannot count on a rescue mission because he was presumed dead.Despite this, he tries to survive in difficult conditions and notify the inhabitants of Earth that he is alive and waiting for help.Ridley Scott's film is nominated for an Oscar in seven categories, including:as the best film and for the leading role of Matt Damon.Director Ridley Scott, the creator of such cult sci-fi films as "Blade Runner" and the Alien series, was a candidate for the Academy Award four times.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Mark Watney - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Melissa Lewis - Jessica Chastain</actor>
      <actor>Annie Montrose - Kristen Wiig</actor>
      <actor>Teddy Sanders - Jeff Daniels</actor>
      <actor>Rick Martinez - Michael Pena</actor>
      <actor>Mitch Henderson - Sean Bean</actor>
      <actor>Beth Johanssen - Kate Mara</actor>
      <actor>Chris Beck - Sebastian Stan</actor>
      <actor>Alex Vogel - Aksel Hennie</actor>
      <actor>Vincent Kapoor - Chiwetel Ejiofor</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506090000 +0500" stop="20260506102500 +0500">
    <title>A Royal Christmas Ballet</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Former ballet dancer Carrie (Brittany Underwood) is to prepare a performance of "The Nutcracker" on the occasion of a visit from a foreign delegation.While working on the play, she becomes involved in an affair.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Fred Olen Ray</director>
      <actor>Carrie - Brittany Underwood</actor>
      <actor>William - Jonathan Stoddard</actor>
      <actor>Marilyn - Julie Stevens</actor>
      <actor>Medea - Daniela Couso</actor>
      <actor>Jane - Monaye Moyes</actor>
      <actor>Colin - Allen Guy</actor>
      <actor>Audrey - Mary-Kate O'Connell</actor>
      <actor>Victoria - Elizabeth Tobias</actor>
      <actor>Becky - Linda Mesi</actor>
      <actor>Mike - Peter Johnson</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506102500 +0500" stop="20260506120500 +0500">
    <title>Broke</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Former rodeo champion True cannot accept the end of his career.He is surprised by a violent blizzard.He fights for survival.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Carlyle Eubank</director>
      <actor>True Brandywine - Wyatt Russell</actor>
      <actor>Ali - Auden Thornton</actor>
      <actor>George Brandywine - Dennis Quaid</actor>
      <actor>Kathy Brandywine - Mary McDonnell</actor>
      <actor>Caleb Brandywine - Johnny Berchtold</actor>
      <actor>Cliff - Tom Skerritt</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506120500 +0500" stop="20260506134500 +0500">
    <title>Silver Star</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>African American Billie (Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson) is twenty years old and a tomboy.He comes from a military family and is missing one eye.After serving her prison sentence, she discovers that her separated parents are facing eviction.He decides to prevent this at all costs.The woman decides to rob a bank, but the action ends in failure.As a result, the young criminal takes her client hostage.Pregnant Franny (Grace Van Dien) is eighteen years old and has a head open to crazy ideas.Together they escape and set off on an adventurous journey.At one point, Franny offers Billie an unexpected deal.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ruben Amar</director>
      <director>Lola Bessis</director>
      <actor>Franny - Grace Van Dien</actor>
      <actor>Billie - Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tyrone Sands - Johnath Davis</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Woodman - Getchie Argetsinger</actor>
      <actor>Shonda - Tamara Fruits</actor>
      <actor>Alice - Ekaterina Baker</actor>
      <actor>Dylan - Joey Giambattista</actor>
      <actor>William Bortschstoecker - Josh Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Clark - Amy Tribbey</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Noa Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506134500 +0500" stop="20260506154500 +0500">
    <title>Vinci 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Cuma receives an offer to participate in a new heist.At first he refuses, but changes his mind when he learns that his old rival, Chudy, is planning a spectacular robbery in Krakow without his participation.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Juliusz Machulski</director>
      <actor>Robert Cumiński Cuma - Robert Więckiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Julian Wolniewicz Szerszeń - Borys Szyc</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Kamilla Baar</actor>
      <actor>komisarz Łukasz Wilk - Marcin Dorociński</actor>
      <actor>paser Chudy - Mirosław Haniszewski</actor>
      <actor>Marcin Kudra - Łukasz Simlat</actor>
      <actor>Jan Bednarek Werbus - Jacek Król</actor>
      <actor>Kazu Tanaka - Masakazu Miyanaga</actor>
      <actor>kurator Zjawińska - Ilona Ostrowska</actor>
      <actor>Helmut - Krzysztof Stelmaszyk</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506154500 +0500" stop="20260506173000 +0500">
    <title>In short</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2019, on the threshold of the pandemic.Single woman Ellen (Laura Tonke) spends New Year's Eve with her friends.No one knows that she is having an affair with Sebastian (Ronald Zehrfeld), Eva's (Antje Traue) husband.Rolf (Nicholas Ofczarek) and Dina (Pegah Ferydoni) make a perfect couple, unlike Mareike (Annette Frier) and Adam (Trystan Pütter).Maya (Katia Fellin) wants children, Natalie (Jasmin Shakeri) cannot decide.Max (Henning Flüsloh) comes into Ellen's life and he would love her if she let him.Years pass.The woman attends various types of celebrations, birthday parties and casual social gatherings.He learns about events in his friends' lives.The sense of community unites and allows everyone to return to everyday life with positive energy.Remake of the Danish film "A Long Story Briefly".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Dietl</director>
      <actor>Ellen - Laura Tonke</actor>
      <actor>Natalie - Jasmin Shakeri</actor>
      <actor>Mareike - Annette Frier</actor>
      <actor>Rolf - Nicholas Ofczarek</actor>
      <actor>Max - Henning Flüsloh</actor>
      <actor>Adam - Trystan Pütter</actor>
      <actor>Maya - Katia Fellin</actor>
      <actor>Sebastian - Ronald Zehrfeld</actor>
      <actor>Dina - Pegah Ferydoni</actor>
      <actor>Becky - Marlene Tanczik</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506173000 +0500" stop="20260506190500 +0500">
    <title>Karate Kid: Legends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li Fong's friend needs help.He decided to take part in a karate tournament, but his skills are insufficient.Teacher Han turns to the legendary Daniel LaRusso for help.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Li Fong - Ben Wang</actor>
      <actor>Victor Lipani - Joshua Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Mia Lipani - Sadie Stanley</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Fong - Ming-Na</actor>
      <actor>Alan - Wyatt Oleff</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Aramis Knight</actor>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Young Girl - Olivia Yang Avis</actor>
      <actor>Young Student - Aaron Wang</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506190500 +0500" stop="20260506212500 +0500">
    <title>Kingdom of Heaven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12th century.The young blacksmith Balian (Orlando Bloom) loses his entire family in tragic circumstances.He begins to doubt the existence of God.Then he is visited by the crusader Godfrey of Ibelin (Liam Neeson), who turns out to be his father.He suggests his son learn knightly crafts.One day, Balian kills a priest in a fight.He must escape.Together with Godfrey, he sets off for Jerusalem.On the way, his father is killed by the bishop's men.Prudent King Baldwin IV (Edward Norton) and his advisor Tiberias (Jeremy Irons) strive for peaceful solutions.Thanks to them, there are no hostilities in Jerusalem.They even manage to reach a truce with the leader of the Muslims, Saladin (Ghassan Massoud).However, the ruler's conciliatory policy does not please some greedy and fanatical crusaders.Meanwhile, Balian falls in love with the king's sister, the already married princess Sibyl (Eva Green).The girl does not love her husband, Baron Guy de Lusignan (Marton Csokas).Soon the Crusaders start a war with the Muslims.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Balian - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Sybilla - Eva Green</actor>
      <actor>Tiberias - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Godfrey z Ibelinu - Liam Neeson</actor>
      <actor>Gravedigger - Martin Hancock</actor>
      <actor>Guy de Lusignan - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Reynald de Chatillon - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Stary Strażnik - Tim Barlow</actor>
      <actor>król Baldwin IV - Edward Norton</actor>
      <actor>Saladin - Ghassan Massoud</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506212500 +0500" stop="20260506230000 +0500">
    <title>Anaconda</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Doug (Jack Black) and Griff (Paul Rudd) have been friends since childhood.They have always dreamed of making a remake of their favorite film, the horror film "Anaconda".When both buddies experience a midlife crisis, they decide not to wait any longer and set off together deep into the Amazon to start filming.The situation becomes more complicated when... a real giant anaconda appears on the film set, spreading chaos and destruction around.Despite the deadly threat, the friends decide to take advantage of the predator's presence.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tom Gormican</director>
      <actor>Doug McCallister - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Ronald Griffin Jr. - Paul Rudd</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Trent - Steve Zahn</actor>
      <actor>Claire Simons - Thandie Newton</actor>
      <actor>Ana Almeida - Daniela Melchior</actor>
      <actor>Santiago Braga - Selton Mello</actor>
      <actor>Ice Cube - Ice Cube</actor>
      <actor>Malie - Ione Skye</actor>
      <actor>Joao - Rui Ricardo Diaz</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - John Billingsley</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260506230000 +0500" stop="20260507003500 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brave Po opens a new chapter in his life - he is to become the spiritual leader of the Valley of Peace.He's trying to get used to his new role.In addition, the voracious bear must find a daredevil who will replace him as the Dragon Warrior.Not everything goes according to plan.This time, China's security is threatened by Chameleon, who wields black magic and can take on any form and take over the abilities of old masters.With the help of a smart vixen and former thief, Zhen, the panda bear must face her.But they need allies to defeat the shape-shifting witch and the sinister army behind her.The time of a merciless fight is inevitably approaching... The voices of the characters include, among others:Marcin Hycnar, Jan Peszek, Wiktor Zborowski and Julia Chatys.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Mitchell</director>
      <director>Stephanie Stine</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507003500 +0500" stop="20260507013500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507013500 +0500" stop="20260507021500 +0500">
    <title>Peacemaker 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Ignorance Is Chris</sub-title>
    <desc>Two years have passed since the last events.Chris Smith (John Cena) considers himself a real hero.However, he must earn the recognition of other heroes.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Christopher Smith - John Cena</actor>
      <actor>Leota Adebayo - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Adrian Chase - Freddie Stroma</actor>
      <actor>Agent Emilia Harcourt - Jennifer Holland</actor>
      <actor>John Economos - Steve Agee</actor>
      <actor>Eagly - Dee Bradley Baker</actor>
      <actor>Clemson Murn - Chukwudi Iwuji</actor>
      <actor>Auggie Smith - Robert Patrick</actor>
      <actor>Detective Sophie Song - Annie Chang</actor>
      <actor>Detective Larry Fitzgibbon - Lochlyn Munro</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Action-Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507021500 +0500" stop="20260507040000 +0500">
    <title>G20</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>During the G20 summit, the leaders of the world's influential countries become the targets of terrorists.US President Danielle Sutton (Viola Davis) miraculously manages to escape the attackers.She must face the enemy alone.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Patricia Riggen</director>
      <actor>President Danielle Sutton - Viola Davis</actor>
      <actor>Derek Sutton - Anthony Anderson</actor>
      <actor>Agent Manny Ruiz - Ramon Rodriguez</actor>
      <actor>Serena Sutton - Marsai Martin</actor>
      <actor>Rutledge - Antony Starr</actor>
      <actor>Prime Minister Oliver Everett - Douglas Hodge</actor>
      <actor>Treasury Secretary Joanna Worth - Elizabeth Marvel</actor>
      <actor>Demetrius Sutton - Christopher Farrar</actor>
      <actor>Elena Romano - Sabrina Impacciatore</actor>
      <actor>Han Min-Seo - MeeWha Alana Lee</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507040000 +0500" stop="20260507053500 +0500">
    <title>Laws of Man</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A suspenseful story set in the paranoid climate of the Cold War era.The year is 1963. Two federal marshals are investigating a case in rural Nevada.They are on the trail of a sinister conspiracy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Phil Blattenberger</director>
      <actor>Galen Armstrong - Keith Carradine</actor>
      <actor>Benjamin Bonney - Dermot Mulroney</actor>
      <actor>Sheriff Kutch - Graham Greene</actor>
      <actor>Cassidy Whittaker - Harvey Keitel</actor>
      <actor>Crash Mooncalf - Richard Brake</actor>
      <actor>Tommy Morton - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Don Burgess - Forrie J. Smith</actor>
      <actor>Proprietor Isaac - James Urbaniak</actor>
      <actor>Callie - Kelly Lynn Reiter</actor>
      <actor>Noah Bonney - Greg Kriek</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507053500 +0500" stop="20260507073000 +0500">
    <title>Blue Valentine</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dean grew up in a broken home.He never planned to build a lasting relationship until he met Cindy, with whom he fell in love at first sight.When, after a few weeks of dating, it turns out that the girl is expecting another man's child, she makes the difficult decision to get married.The couple tries to create a happy family, but over time they begin to face a serious crisis.The infatuation disappears, and everyday problems make it difficult for them to find understanding.Dean abuses alcohol and does simple physical work, unable to guarantee his wife real stability and support.The couple falls into conflicts more and more often.However, he still tries to rebuild his relationships for the sake of little Frankie.This perfectly portrayed study of the breakdown of a relationship was nominated for the Grand Jury Prize at the Sundance Film Festival.The role of Michelle Williams was nominated for an Oscar and a Golden Globe.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Derek Cianfrance</director>
      <actor>Dean - Ryan Gosling</actor>
      <actor>Cindy - Michelle Williams</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - John Doman</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Mike Vogel</actor>
      <actor>Frankie - Faith Wladyka</actor>
      <actor>Marshall - Marshall Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Gramma - Jen Jones</actor>
      <actor>Glenda - Maryann Plunkett</actor>
      <actor>Jamie - James Benatti</actor>
      <actor>Jo - Barbara Troy</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507073000 +0500" stop="20260507090000 +0500">
    <title>It's a Wonderful Knife</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A year ago, teenage Winnie Carruthers (Jane Widdop) had to face a psychopathic murderer, Henry Waters (Justin Long), on Christmas Eve, whose victim was also her best friend.Now it's Christmas again in the town of Angel Falls.Winnie still remembers the tragic events, although her father David (Joel McHale) and other loved ones advise her to leave the difficult past behind.A misunderstood girl on a bridge on Christmas night makes a wish - she would prefer to have never been born.He then finds himself in a nightmarish parallel universe.He discovers that without her, everything could have turned out much worse.No one recognizes her here, she is a stranger even to her family and friends.And what's worse, Henry is still alive and the mayor of Angel Falls.The teenager must regain her former life and face a bloodthirsty murderer.A bloody variation on the famous Christmas classic - "It's a Wonderful Life" by Frank Capra.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tyler MacIntyre</director>
      <actor>Winnie Carruthers - Jane Widdop</actor>
      <actor>David Carruthers - Joel McHale</actor>
      <actor>Henry Waters - Justin Long</actor>
      <actor>Bernie Simon - Jessica McLeod</actor>
      <actor>Gale Prescott - Katharine Isabelle</actor>
      <actor>Jimmy Carruthers - Aiden Howard</actor>
      <actor>Judy Carruthers - Erin Boyes</actor>
      <actor>Buck Waters - Sean Depner</actor>
      <actor>Darla Berlin - Zenia Marshall</actor>
      <actor>Robbie Olenger - Jason Fernandes</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507090000 +0500" stop="20260507101500 +0500">
    <title>Little Emma</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A little girl named Emma was raised by animals.Her life is full of warmth and joy, until one of her friends discovers the unpleasant truth that she was actually adopted and is not part of their family.Devastated, Emma sets out on a journey to find her loved ones.Along the way, he gathers an extraordinary team, including the clumsy inventor Żółwik Bystrzak, the ambitious scientist Edward Wilk and the brave Weasel Sancho.Together they are looking for a mysterious island which, according to legend, is inhabited by tiny people.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Leo Lewis</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507101500 +0500" stop="20260507103500 +0500">
    <title>Book of Dragons</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hiccup, Astrid, Fishlegs and Gobber learn the secrets of the dragons contained in the book.Gobber tells the others the story of Borek the Unlucky, who was the first to describe these unusual creatures.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Steve Hickner</director>
    </credits><date>2011</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507103500 +0500" stop="20260507121000 +0500">
    <title>E Poi Si Vede</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three friends compete for an attractive job at the city hall.Federico relies on his father's connections, Fabrizio feels that he is born for this job, and Luca is always lucky.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Giovanni Calvaruso</director>
      <actor>Senatrice Purpura - Donatella Finocchiaro</actor>
      <actor>Roberta - Ester Pantano</actor>
      <actor>Giampiero Casesa - Domenico Centamore</actor>
      <actor>Fabrizio Caruso - Fabrizio Sansone</actor>
      <actor>Federico Pagano - Federico Sansone</actor>
      <actor>Teresa Pagano - Paola Minaccioni</actor>
      <actor>Prof. De Ruvo - Gino Astorina</actor>
      <actor>Giuseppe Bolignari - Paride Benassai</actor>
      <actor>Giudice - Pierpaolo Benigni</actor>
      <actor>Giuseppe Pagano - Maurizio Bologna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507121000 +0500" stop="20260507141500 +0500">
    <title>P.S. I Love You</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the death of her husband Gerry (Gerard Butler), Holly (Hilary Swank) falls into a deep depression.On her 30th birthday, a woman receives a mysterious parcel.The cake comes with a tape with a recorded message from... Gerry.He encourages his beloved to go out and have fun with friends.After this event, new letters regularly arrived to the young widow, each ending with a declaration of love.Gerry knew how much his wife would suffer from losing him.In letters written before her death, he encourages her to take on various challenges.Thanks to her extraordinary sense of connection with the deceased, a woman in despair undergoes specific therapy and tries to start her life anew.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard LaGravenese</director>
      <actor>Holly - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Gerry - Gerard Butler</actor>
      <actor>Denise - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Gina Gershon</actor>
      <actor>John - James Marsters</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Kathy Bates</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Harry Connick Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Ciara - Nellie McKay</actor>
      <actor>William - Jeffrey Dean Morgan</actor>
      <actor>George - Christopher Whalen</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507141500 +0500" stop="20260507162000 +0500">
    <title>Big Fish</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Edward Bloom (Albert Finney), a brilliant storyteller and favorite of the neighborhood, is dying.His son Will (Billy Crudup) left home long ago, not wanting to live forever in the shadow of his father's fantastic stories.Now she returns to accompany him in his last moments.Listening to Edward's stories again, Will tries to put them together to make sense.The picture that emerges is surprisingly coherent and shows the father's life in a new light.The son realizes who his father really was.Tim Burton, one of the most eccentric creators of American cinema, created a film that captivates with its warmth, fairy-tale atmosphere and surreal poetics.The script is based on the novel "Big Fish: A Story of Mythic Proportions" by Daniel Wallace.We will see Ewan McGregor as young Edward.The atmospheric music received an Oscar nomination.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tim Burton</director>
      <actor>młody Ed Bloom - Ewan McGregor</actor>
      <actor>stary Ed Bloom - Albert Finney</actor>
      <actor>Will Bloom - Billy Crudup</actor>
      <actor>stara Sandra Bloom - Jessica Lange</actor>
      <actor>młoda Sandra Bloom - Alison Lohman</actor>
      <actor>Jenny - Helena Bonham Carter</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Bennett - Robert Guillaume</actor>
      <actor>Josephine - Marion Cotillard</actor>
      <actor>Karl the Giant - Matthew McGrory</actor>
      <actor>Don Price - David Denman</actor>
    </credits><date>2003</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507162000 +0500" stop="20260507175500 +0500">
    <title>Detective Monk: One last thing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brilliant detective Adrian Monk (Tony Shalhoub) is going through difficult times.The contract to publish his autobiography was canceled, and the coronavirus pandemic intensified his fears and phobias.All this makes the master of deduction start thinking about ending his life and joining his beloved Truda.He is jolted out of his torpor by the tragedy that befalls his stepdaughter Molly (Caitlin McGee).The girl is getting ready to marry journalist Griffin Briggs (Austin Scott).However, her fiancé dies while bungee jumping.Molly is convinced that it was not an accident, but a carefully planned murder.The trail leads to the influential billionaire Rick Eden (James Purefoy).Retired Captain Stottlemeyer (Ted Levine) now works for the rich man as his security chief.Monk is assisted in the investigation by former assistant and now real estate agent Natalie Teeger (Traylor Howard) and Randy Disher (Jason Gray-Stanford), now the New Jersey police commissioner.Continuation of the cult series.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Randy Zisk</director>
      <actor>Adrian Monk - Tony Shalhoub</actor>
      <actor>Natalie Teeger - Traylor Howard</actor>
      <actor>Randy Disher - Jason Gray-Stanford</actor>
      <actor>Trudy Monk - Melora Hardin</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Neven Bell - Hector Elizondo</actor>
      <actor>Stottlemeyer - Ted Levine</actor>
      <actor>Rick Eden - James Purefoy</actor>
      <actor>Molly Evans - Caitlin McGee</actor>
      <actor>Griffin Briggs - Austin Scott</actor>
      <actor>Skyler - Emma Ishta</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507175500 +0500" stop="20260507192500 +0500">
    <title>In-laws 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In a recreation center that has already passed its glory days, Wanda (Izabela Kuna) and Tadeusz (Adam Woronowicz) organize their grandson's baptism.At the family celebration, to which they invite Małgorzata (Maja Ostaszewska) and her friend, psychotherapist Grażyna (Magdalena Popławska), the former husband of the first woman, Andrzej (Marcin Dorociński), who comes from Australia with... his son Stanley (Noah Lucewicz), also appears.The atmosphere of the meeting quickly gets out of control, and old conflicts and new romances lead to surprising consequences.The local police must intervene.The third part of the comedy, with a pinch of salt, showing the class struggle.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jakub Michalczuk</director>
      <actor>Małgorzata Wilk - Maja Ostaszewska</actor>
      <actor>Wanda Chrapek - Izabela Kuna</actor>
      <actor>Andrzej Wilk - Marcin Dorociński</actor>
      <actor>Tadeusz Chrapek - Adam Woronowicz</actor>
      <actor>Grażyna Zięcina - Magdalena Popławska</actor>
      <actor>Marek Vajs - Wojciech Mecwaldowski</actor>
      <actor>Weronika Chrapek-Wilk - Katarzyna Chojnacka</actor>
      <actor>Łukasz Wilk - Ignacy Martusewicz</actor>
      <actor>ojciec Wandy - Joachim Lamża</actor>
      <actor>Danuta - Ewa Konstancja Bułhak</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507192500 +0500" stop="20260507210000 +0500">
    <title>One of Them Days</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dreux (Keke Palmer) and Alyssa (SZA) are like lovebirds, they have been friends for years and share an apartment.Their everyday lives suddenly turn upside down when they discover that Alyssa's boyfriend has squandered all their savings - money that was supposed to be used to pay the rent.The girls face a real challenge: in an atmosphere full of funny adventures, they must quickly find a way to get the missing amount and avoid eviction.It quickly turns out that they will be forced to take truly unusual actions to not only save their home, but also put their friendship to the test.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Lawrence Lamont</director>
      <actor>Dreux - Keke Palmer</actor>
      <actor>Alyssa - SZA</actor>
      <actor>Bethany - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>The Buyer - Lil Rel Howery</actor>
      <actor>Ruby - Janelle James</actor>
      <actor>Mama Ruth - Vanessa Bell Calloway</actor>
      <actor>Lucky - Katt Williams</actor>
      <actor>Maniac - Patrick Cage</actor>
      <actor>Shayla - Gabrielle Dennis</actor>
      <actor>King Lolo - Amin Joseph</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507210000 +0500" stop="20260507230000 +0500">
    <title>Another Simple Favor</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Emily Nelson (Blake Lively), who was sentenced to 20 years in prison, regains her freedom.She is planning a wedding on the island of Capri, and an old friend becomes her bridesmaid.A crime occurs during the ceremony.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Paul Feig</director>
      <actor>Emily Nelson - Blake Lively</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Smothers - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Miles Smothers - Joshua Satine</actor>
      <actor>Swim Coach - Mitch Salm</actor>
      <actor>Darren - Andrew Rannells</actor>
      <actor>Lulu - Diletta Jayne</actor>
      <actor>Camp Counselor Val - Holmes</actor>
      <actor>Sona - Aparna Nancherla</actor>
      <actor>Stacy - Kelly McCormack</actor>
      <actor>Vicky - Alex Newell</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260507230000 +0500" stop="20260508005500 +0500">
    <title>Welcome to Marwen</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Mark Hogancamp (Steve Carell) is an illustrator, known primarily for his World War II graphics.However, he hides quite an original preference.He is fascinated by women's shoes.At home, she has a large collection of high heels, sandals, flip-flops and many other shoes.His secret is revealed unexpectedly and causes great emotions.He is attacked by a group of neo-Nazis.The injuries are so severe that they result in loss of not only memory, but also the ability to speak and move.His artistic career is ruined.The man starts therapy, hoping to regain his former shape.However, he struggles with enormous trauma and mental problems.He finally manages to find a new passion.He constructs a village in the garden, which he names Marwen.Its inhabitants, the dolls, are modeled on real people from his life.It turns out that the mockup helps him deal with panic attacks.However, he still cannot forget his experiences.Meanwhile, a new neighbor, Nicol (Leslie Mann), moves in next door.The film is inspired by the true story of artist Mark Hogancamp.The town he built is located in Kingston.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Zemeckis</director>
      <actor>Mark Hogancamp - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Captain Topf - Falk Hentschel</actor>
      <actor>Lieutenant Benz - Matt O'Leary</actor>
      <actor>Rudolph - Nikolai Witschl</actor>
      <actor>Stefan - Patrick Roccas</actor>
      <actor>Werner - Alexander Lowe</actor>
      <actor>Carlala - Eiza González</actor>
      <actor>Suzette - Leslie Zemeckis</actor>
      <actor>Roberta - Merritt Wever</actor>
      <actor>Anna - Gwendoline Christie</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>