<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422024000 +0500" stop="20260422043500 +0500">
    <title>Assassin's Creed</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Recidivist Callum Lynch sentenced to death is not executed.After a fake execution, he ends up in a secret laboratory.There he meets Rikkin and his daughter Sofia.Scientists have a mysterious device that allows them to access the records of ancestors' actions stored in their genes.The criminal is to connect with the consciousness of Aguilar from Spain, who lived during the Great Inquisition and obtained the Apple of Eden, which provides control over emotions.By using this item, you can supposedly eliminate aggression in people.The daredevil travels to the Middle Ages.He discovers that he is a descendant of a member of the Assassin secret society.Over time, he learns what a big mistake he made when he trusted Sofia and her father.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Justin Kurzel</director>
      <actor>Cal Lynch - Michael Fassbender</actor>
      <actor>Sofia - Marion Cotillard</actor>
      <actor>Rikkin - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Joseph Lynch - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Ellen Kaye - Charlotte Rampling</actor>
      <actor>Moussa - Michael K. Williams</actor>
      <actor>McGowan - Denis Ménochet</actor>
      <actor>Maria - Ariane Labed</actor>
      <actor>Sultan Muhammad XII - Khalid Abdalla</actor>
      <actor>Cal's Mother - Essie Davis</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422043500 +0500" stop="20260422071500 +0500">
    <title>Kinds of Kindness</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three seemingly unrelated stories.Emma Stone, Jesse Plemons and Willem Dafoe play various roles.A corporate manager (Jesse Plemons) lives under the dictates of an eccentric boss (Willem Dafoe).She puts his well-being above her own and doesn't question any outlandish demands.Stripped of his dignity, he tries to free himself from total control.A policeman (Jesse Plemons) misses his wife (Emma Stone) - a biologist who disappeared during a research expedition.A woman who survived the disaster returns, but her marriage is put to the test.The husband becomes paranoid and is not sure if this is the same beloved he once married.The heroes of the last story are members of a sect who are looking for a person with the power to resurrect the dead.The work of Yórgos Lánthimos - the director of "Poor Things" which won four Oscars.For his performance, Jesse Plemons was awarded the Palme d'Or at Cannes.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Yorgos Lanthimos</director>
      <actor>Rita - Emma Stone</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Jesse Plemons</actor>
      <actor>Raymond - Willem Dafoe</actor>
      <actor>Vivian - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Sarah - Hong Chau</actor>
      <actor>Collectibles Appraise Man 1 - Joe Alwyn</actor>
      <actor>Will - Mamoudou Athie</actor>
      <actor>Anna - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Young Woman Driver - Susan Elle</actor>
      <actor>Susan - Krystal Alayne Chambers</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422071500 +0500" stop="20260422090000 +0500">
    <title>Andrea Bocelli: Because I Believe</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Silhouette of a famous opera singer.The camera follows Andrea Bocelli not only behind the scenes, but also off stage to show his private life - among his family and closest friends.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Cosima Spender</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422090000 +0500" stop="20260422110000 +0500">
    <title>BlackBerry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1996. Mike and Doug, friends from their youth, run a small technology company.They create a revolutionary product, but they cannot sell it.They attract the attention of Jim, who offers to help them.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Johnson</director>
      <actor>Mike - Jay Baruchel</actor>
      <actor>Jim - Glenn Howerton</actor>
      <actor>Doug - Matt Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Jasmine - Kelly Van der Burg</actor>
      <actor>Young Businessman #1 - Gregory Ambrose Calderone</actor>
      <actor>Shelly - Laura Cilevitz</actor>
      <actor>Rick Brock - Martin Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Callaghan Drummond - James Elliot Miniou</actor>
      <actor>Derek - Fuad Musayev</actor>
      <actor>Ethan - Ethan Eng</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422110000 +0500" stop="20260422124000 +0500">
    <title>The Glassworker</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vincent Oliver, the son of renowned glassmaker Tomasz, is preparing for his first exhibition when he finds a letter from his childhood friend, Alliz Amano, whom he has always loved.He recalls how - raised by a pacifist father - he saw her for the first time.Alliz arrives in Vincent's city, Waterfront, with her parent, Colonel Amano.They become a couple.Meanwhile, a war breaks out and both he and his rival for the girl's favor, Malik, join the army.Tomasz is forced to produce glass rectifiers for the army.Some time later, the girl's father dies without any news at the front.When Malik returns to town with him, Alliz rewards him with a kiss, which Vincent witnesses.Devastated, he sabotages the production of rectifiers, but this leads to tragedy.The anime-inspired production with an anti-war message is the first Pakistani film made using the hand-animated technique.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Usman Riaz</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422124000 +0500" stop="20260422144000 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: Eclipse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After a painful separation, Bella and her lover can enjoy each other's company again.The teenager wants to be transformed into an immortal being, which will allow them to be united forever.Before that, however, he has to take care of more mundane matters - pass his high school leaving exams and get into college.In addition, he is worried about his friend Jacob.It turns out that soon he and Edward will have to join forces to ensure the safety of the girl who has won their hearts.The relative peace of all the bloodsuckers and werewolves of Forks is disturbed by disturbing news from Seattle.It turns out that mysterious murders are taking place there.People are being killed by a pack of vampires, spreading fear and destruction around.The gang is recruiting new members.It is headed by Riley.He was chosen as the leader by the vengeful Victoria, who is seeking Bella's life.Thanks to Alice's visions and the Cullens' vigilance, they manage to protect her.Enemy races unite in the face of danger.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Slade</director>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Victoria - Bryce Dallas Howard</actor>
      <actor>Riley - Xavier Samuel</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Carlisle Cullen - Peter Facinelli</actor>
      <actor>Jessica Stanley - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Mike - Michael Welch</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422144000 +0500" stop="20260422163000 +0500">
    <title>Death Of A Comedian</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Argentine actor Juan Debré (Diego Peretti) receives a disturbing diagnosis at the peak of his career.He escapes to Belgium to immerse himself in his own, safe reality.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Beltramino</director>
      <director>Diego Peretti</director>
      <actor>Lena - Malena Villa</actor>
      <actor>Steve Joyce - Chuck Hargrove</actor>
      <actor>Capitán Busch - Heinz K. Krattiger</actor>
      <actor>Head of Security - Carl-Philipp Wengler</actor>
      <actor>Doyle - Eric Jean Bier</actor>
      <actor>Bonnie - Marioska Fabián Nunez</actor>
      <actor>Waiter in Brussels city - Andrés Guillín</actor>
      <actor>Amal - Agustín Matías Kim</actor>
      <actor>Passenger at the tram stop - Elodie Barthels</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422163000 +0500" stop="20260422191000 +0500">
    <title>The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The hobbit Bilbo (Martin Freeman), Gandalf (Ian McKellen) and the dwarves led by Thorin (Richard Armitage) continue their dangerous journey.The goal of their expedition is to regain Erebor - the kingdom of the dwarves, which is currently occupied by the dragon Smaug (Benedict Cumberbatch).The travelers meet the bear warrior Beorn (Mikael Persbrandt), giant spiders inhabiting Mirkwood, the Wood Elves and their master, King Thranduil (Lee Pace), his son Legolas (Orlando Bloom), and the elf Tauriel (Evangeline Lilly).Thanks to an archer called Bard (Luke Evans), they get to Lake Town.When they reach the Lonely Mountain, they will come face to face with their greatest danger.The second part of the trilogy based on the novel by J.R.R.Tolkien.The film starred, among others: Ian McKellen ("Gods and Monsters"), Martin Freeman ("Fargo", "Sherlock") and Richard Armitage ("Versa", "Epicenter").The film, made on a grand scale, received three Oscar nominations, including for best special effects.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Thorin - Richard Armitage</actor>
      <actor>Gandalf - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Bilbo - Martin Freeman</actor>
      <actor>Balin - Ken Stott</actor>
      <actor>Dwalin - Graham McTavish</actor>
      <actor>Bifur - William Kircher</actor>
      <actor>Bofur - James Nesbitt</actor>
      <actor>Bombur - Stephen Hunter</actor>
      <actor>Fili - Dean O'Gorman</actor>
      <actor>Kili - Aidan Turner</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422191000 +0500" stop="20260422210500 +0500">
    <title>The Idea of You</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Solene (Anne Hathaway) is the owner of an art gallery.One day, a divorced woman accompanies her daughter to a concert and meets her musical idol - the singer of the boy band Hayes Campbell (Nicholas Galitzine), about whom teenagers fantasize.Despite the significant age difference, they both feel that they have a lot in common.They start an affair.Paparazzi make their romantic moments miserable.The revelation of a young musician's relationship with a middle-aged single mother turns out to be a media sensation.An unusual love story with a script based on the novel by Robinne Lee.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Showalter</director>
      <actor>Solene - Anne Hathaway</actor>
      <actor>Hayes - Nicholas Galitzine</actor>
      <actor>Izzy - Ella Rubin</actor>
      <actor>Tracy - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Eva - Perry Mattfeld</actor>
      <actor>Zeke - Jordan Aaron Hall</actor>
      <actor>Georgia - Mathilda Gianopoulos</actor>
      <actor>Claire - Meg Millidge</actor>
      <actor>Jeremy - Cheech Manohar</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422210500 +0500" stop="20260422230000 +0500">
    <title>Soul On Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nine-year-old John O'Leary suffers burns to almost his entire body.He struggles with pain and limitations.However, he wins love and makes his dreams come true.He inspires others by showing how to live life to the fullest.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sean McNamara</director>
      <actor>John O'Leary - Joel Courtney</actor>
      <actor>Denny O'Leary - John Corbett</actor>
      <actor>Susan O'Leary - Stephanie Szostak</actor>
      <actor>Beth O'Leary - Masey McLain</actor>
      <actor>Nurse Roy - DeVon Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Jack Buck - William H. Macy</actor>
      <actor>Young John - James McCracken</actor>
      <actor>Amy O'Leary - Stella Bratcher</actor>
      <actor>Susie O'Leary - Lucy Panozzo</actor>
      <actor>Jim O'Leary - Mikey Cestone</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260422230000 +0500" stop="20260423004500 +0500">
    <title>Blue Moon</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1943. The legendary lyricist Lorenz Hart (Ethan Hawke), co-author of such hits as "Blue Moon" and "My Funny Valentine", spends the night from March 31 to April 1 in Sardi's bar.In the company of friends, including his muse Elizabeth Weiland (Margaret Qualley), he struggles with wounded pride and shaken self-confidence.At this time, his former long-time collaborator Richard Rodgers (Andrew Scott) celebrates the premiere of his musical entitled"Oklahoma!", which he wrote with Oscar Hammerstein II (Simon Delaney).Two Oscar nominations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard Linklater</director>
      <actor>Lorenz Hart - Ethan Hawke</actor>
      <actor>Elizabeth Weiland - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Eddie - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Richard Rodgers - Andrew Scott</actor>
      <actor>E.B. 'Andy' White - Patrick Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Morty Rifkin - Jonah Lees</actor>
      <actor>Oscar Hammerstein - Simon Delaney</actor>
      <actor>Sven - Giles Surridge</actor>
      <actor>Stevie Sondheim - Cillian Sullivan</actor>
      <actor>Lawrence Langner - Michael James Ford</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423004500 +0500" stop="20260423014500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423014500 +0500" stop="20260423022500 +0500">
    <title>Peacemaker 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Need I Say Door</sub-title>
    <desc>Two years have passed since the last events.Chris Smith (John Cena) considers himself a real hero.However, he must earn the recognition of other heroes.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Christopher Smith - John Cena</actor>
      <actor>Leota Adebayo - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Adrian Chase - Freddie Stroma</actor>
      <actor>Agent Emilia Harcourt - Jennifer Holland</actor>
      <actor>John Economos - Steve Agee</actor>
      <actor>Eagly - Dee Bradley Baker</actor>
      <actor>Clemson Murn - Chukwudi Iwuji</actor>
      <actor>Auggie Smith - Robert Patrick</actor>
      <actor>Detective Sophie Song - Annie Chang</actor>
      <actor>Detective Larry Fitzgibbon - Lochlyn Munro</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Action-Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423022500 +0500" stop="20260423045000 +0500">
    <title>Man on Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>American John Creasy (Denzel Washington) is a man haunted by nightmares from his past.He is a former assassin who worked for the CIA for many years.Frustrated, he avoids people and seeks solace in alcohol.Creasy comes to Mexico to visit his old friend and colleague, Rayburn (Christopher Walken).The city is currently gripped by a wave of kidnappings for ransom.Rich residents panic and many of them hire security guards to ensure the safety of their children.A friend finds John a job as a bodyguard for ten-year-old Pita Ramos (Dakota Fanning), the daughter of Mexican industrialist Samuel Ramos (Marc Anthony) and his American wife Lisa (Radha Mitchell).At first, Creasy has a hard time coping with the girl's presence.Over time, however, he becomes friends with her.Under its influence, he changes his attitude to life and gives up alcohol.Soon, however, little Pita is kidnapped.The desperate man does everything to save her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tony Scott</director>
      <actor>Creasy - Denzel Washington</actor>
      <actor>Rayburn - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Pita - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Samuel - Marc Anthony</actor>
      <actor>Lisa - Radha Mitchell</actor>
      <actor>Jordan - Mickey Rourke</actor>
      <actor>Manzano - Giancarlo Giannini</actor>
      <actor>Mariana - Rachel Ticotin</actor>
      <actor>Fuentes - Jesús Ochoa</actor>
      <actor>Sister Anna - Angelina Peláez</actor>
    </credits><date>2004</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423045000 +0500" stop="20260423060500 +0500">
    <title>One, two, three... You're in the game</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Salem, Massachusetts, a town marked by a history of witch hunts.Jonah (Benjamin Evan Ainsworth) and his older brother Marcus (Asa Butterfield) come across an abandoned cabin while biking through the forest.They find a diary and a knife with a mysterious inscription on its blade.When read to her, it evokes a demon that forces young people to participate in macabre versions of children's games - from hide and seek to tag.The brothers, their sister Billy (Natalia Dyer) and her friends take part in the bloody showdown.They discover that this competition from hell cannot be won.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Eren Celeboglu</director>
      <director>Ari Costa</director>
      <actor>Marcus Fletcher - Asa Butterfield</actor>
      <actor>Billie Fletcher - Natalia Dyer</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Fletcher - Benjamin Evan Ainsworth</actor>
      <actor>Sophie Fletcher - Laurel Marsden</actor>
      <actor>Kathy Fletcher - Annabeth Gish</actor>
      <actor>Joanna Good - Marina Stephenson Kerr</actor>
      <actor>Pete - Kolton Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Bob - Erik Athavale</actor>
      <actor>Nick - Matthew Lupu</actor>
      <actor>Pilar - Sydney Sabiston</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423060500 +0500" stop="20260423074500 +0500">
    <title>Blue Moon</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1943. The legendary lyricist Lorenz Hart (Ethan Hawke), co-author of such hits as "Blue Moon" and "My Funny Valentine", spends the night from March 31 to April 1 in Sardi's bar.In the company of friends, including his muse Elizabeth Weiland (Margaret Qualley), he struggles with wounded pride and shaken self-confidence.At this time, his former long-time collaborator Richard Rodgers (Andrew Scott) celebrates the premiere of his musical entitled"Oklahoma!", which he wrote with Oscar Hammerstein II (Simon Delaney).Two Oscar nominations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard Linklater</director>
      <actor>Lorenz Hart - Ethan Hawke</actor>
      <actor>Elizabeth Weiland - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Eddie - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Richard Rodgers - Andrew Scott</actor>
      <actor>E.B. 'Andy' White - Patrick Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Morty Rifkin - Jonah Lees</actor>
      <actor>Oscar Hammerstein - Simon Delaney</actor>
      <actor>Sven - Giles Surridge</actor>
      <actor>Stevie Sondheim - Cillian Sullivan</actor>
      <actor>Lawrence Langner - Michael James Ford</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423074500 +0500" stop="20260423090000 +0500">
    <title>Daniel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Daniel Northcott began documenting his life and the world around him at the age of 7, when his father gave him a video camera.He filmed his family and friends, and then the places he traveled to.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Daniel Northcott</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423090000 +0500" stop="20260423104000 +0500">
    <title>The Book of Life</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two powerful magicians bet whether people are pure in heart.La Muerte is the ruler of the World of the Remembered.The dead stay there, remaining in the hearts of their loved ones.Xibalba rules the Land of the Forgotten - a sad place for souls that no one remembers.The magicians are tested by: fashion matador Manolo, who dreams of being a musician, and Joaquin - an athlete and the pride of the city.The boys compete for the affections of Maria, the daughter of the local mayor.However, the beautiful bride is resistant to their advances.Manolo and Joaquin will go on a wonderful journey during which they will visit extraordinary lands, meet colorful characters and discover the truth about themselves.The project by Guillermo del Toro and Jorge R. Gutierrez was nominated for a Golden Globe in the category of best animated film.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jorge R. Gutiérrez</director>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423104000 +0500" stop="20260423124000 +0500">
    <title>The Fourth Wall</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 1982, war-torn Lebanon.Theater director Georges (Laurent Lafitte), in order to keep his promise to his terminally ill friend, goes to Beirut to implement a risky project.He intends to put "Antigone" on the front line to guarantee a moment of peace for the parties to the conflict.The show will feature actors involved in fighting, belonging to various political and religious factions.Marwan (Simon Abkarian) becomes a guide in an unknown city, who explains the background of the dispute to the foreigner and becomes a link with the locals.Soon Georges faces the brutal realities of war.The plans are also complicated by the feelings he has for one of the actresses, Imane (Manal Issa).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Oelhoffen</director>
      <actor>Georges - Laurent Lafitte</actor>
      <actor>Marwan - Simon Abkarian</actor>
      <actor>Imane - Manal Issa</actor>
      <actor>Sam Akounis - Bernard Bloch</actor>
      <actor>Nakad - Tarek Yaacoub</actor>
      <actor>Charbel - Pio Chihahe</actor>
      <actor>Nabil - Elie Njeim</actor>
      <actor>Yevkine - Dana Mikhail</actor>
      <actor>Khadija - Khitam Al Lahham</actor>
      <actor>Madeleine - Tracy Younes</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423124000 +0500" stop="20260423143500 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn - Part 1</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bella Swan and Edward Cullen are getting married.They spend their honeymoon on a private island in Brazil belonging to the groom's family.Two weeks later, Bella discovers she is pregnant.The fetus is developing at a rapid pace.The couple returns to Forks.It turns out that Bella's condition means great danger to her.The werewolves, led by Sam, want to kill her unborn offspring, who may turn out to be a demon.Jacob defies his pack and decides to protect his lost loved one.The Cullen family prepares for a difficult birth.Edward will have to fight to save the person he loves with all his heart.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Condon</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Jessica Stanley - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Jane - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Aro - Michael Sheen</actor>
      <actor>Emmett Cullen - Kellan Lutz</actor>
      <actor>Rosalie Hale - Nikki Reed</actor>
      <actor>Caius - Jamie Campbell Bower</actor>
      <actor>Irina - Maggie Grace</actor>
    </credits><date>2011</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423143500 +0500" stop="20260423162000 +0500">
    <title>Focus</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nicky Spurgeon is a calculating fraud.The model's appearance and ability to keep cool make him a master criminal.He is able to win people over, but he does it to take advantage of them.One day, in a restaurant, he meets a fair-haired beauty, Jess Barrett, whose ambition is to pursue a criminal career.He becomes her mentor.Over time, they both realize that they have much more in common than the relationship of master and disciple.However, they live in a world where there is no place for love.Spurgeon ends this relationship.Three years pass.Nicky is in Buenos Aires, where he works for the owner of a car racing team, Rafael Garrigi.He meets his former lover here.Aware of her strengths, the femme fatale has one goal - to take revenge for the way she was once treated.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Glenn Ficarra</director>
      <director>John Requa</director>
      <actor>Nicky - Will Smith</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Margot Robbie</actor>
      <actor>Farhad - Adrian Martinez</actor>
      <actor>Owens - Gerald McRaney</actor>
      <actor>Garriga - Rodrigo Santoro</actor>
      <actor>Liyuan - BD Wong</actor>
      <actor>Horst - Brennan Brown</actor>
      <actor>McEwen - Robert Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Gordon - Dotan Bonen</actor>
      <actor>Gareth - Griff Furst</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423162000 +0500" stop="20260423191500 +0500">
    <title>The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Hobbit Frodo Baggins comes into possession of a magical Ring.His relative Bilbo obtained it during his expedition to the Lonely Mountain.This extraordinary gem can give its owner control over the world, which is why its creator - the Lord of Darkness Sauron - will do anything to get it back.The wizard Gandalf knows that the Ring must be destroyed.There is only one way to do this - by throwing him into the fire that burns inside Mount Doom.However, getting there is very difficult.A council is called in Rivendell on this matter.Frodo undertakes a dangerous mission to destroy the jewel.He is accompanied by his friendly hobbits, Sam Gamgee and Pippin and Merry, as well as representatives of other races: the elf Legolas, the dwarf Gimli, people - Aragorn and Boromir - and Gandalf.The ring has a sinister power that is difficult to avoid.It arouses strong desire and influences the psyche, which puts the team to the test.Meanwhile, Sauron sends his troops against her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Frodo Baggins - Elijah Wood</actor>
      <actor>Legolas Greenleaf - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Gandalf - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Galadriel - Cate Blanchett</actor>
      <actor>Sam Gamgee - Sean Astin</actor>
      <actor>Peregrin 'Pippin' Took - Billy Boyd</actor>
      <actor>Saruman - Christopher Lee</actor>
      <actor>Boromir - Sean Bean</actor>
      <actor>Everard Proudfoot - Noel Appleby</actor>
      <actor>Sauron - Sala Baker</actor>
    </credits><date>2001</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423191500 +0500" stop="20260423211500 +0500">
    <title>Alita: Battle Angel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alita (Rosa Salazar), a cyborg girl, wakes up from a coma.It turns out that he doesn't remember who he is or where he is.Doctor Ido (Christoph Waltz) subjected her to a series of tests that revealed that she was a young woman with a unique story.Wanting to protect her, he does not reveal the truth about her past.Alita must adapt to the conditions and rules of life in Scrap City.After some time, he regains his memory thanks to the help of his friend, Hugo (Keean Johnson).Then he realizes that he has incredible fighting skills.She must use them against the power that tries to control her.The film's director is Robert Rodriguez, known from "From Dusk Till Dawn" and "Machete".The script was written by the winner of three Oscars, James Cameron, who considered making "Alita" back in the 1990s. The film was based on the manga.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Rodriguez</director>
      <actor>Alita - Rosa Salazar</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Dyson Ido - Christoph Waltz</actor>
      <actor>Chiren - Jennifer Connelly</actor>
      <actor>Vector - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Zapan - Ed Skrein</actor>
      <actor>Grewishka - Jackie Earle Haley</actor>
      <actor>Hugo - Keean Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tanji - Jorge Lendeborg Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Koyomi - Lana Condor</actor>
      <actor>Nurse Gerhad - Idara Victor</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423211500 +0500" stop="20260423230000 +0500">
    <title>You Gotta Believe</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A group of baseball players are having the most important season of their lives.For one of the boys, the stakes are even higher - the team fights not only for victories, but also for his father's dream to come true.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ty Roberts</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260423230000 +0500" stop="20260424002500 +0500">
    <title>The Doll</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rémi did not recover from the breakup.In order to function, he remains in a relationship with the doll Audrey, with whom he lives and shares everyday affairs.One day, a new colleague shows up at his company.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sophie Beaulieu</director>
      <actor>Rémi Allard - Vincent Macaigne</actor>
      <actor>Audrey - Zoé Marchal</actor>
      <actor>Rosy Allard - Marianne Basler</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Cécile De France</actor>
      <actor>Domi - Adele Journeaux</actor>
      <actor>Bernard Allard - Gilbert Melki</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ludovic Thievon</actor>
      <actor>Hervé - Eric Guerin</actor>
      <actor>Renan - Victor Bonnel</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>