<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423080500 +0500" stop="20260423090000 +0500">
    <title>An Update on Our Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The filmmakers discuss the topic of vlogging by families.They tell the story of Myka and James Stauffer, who gave an adopted boy to an orphanage when he was diagnosed with autism.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Rachel Mason</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423090000 +0500" stop="20260423102000 +0500">
    <title>The Pirates! Band of Misfits</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A certain inept captain of a pirate ship firmly believes that he will soon become the terror of the seas and oceans.Unfortunately, for now, these ambitious plans have no chance of being implemented, and his subsequent crazy ideas end in failure.The buccaneer, who wants to prove his bravery at all costs, intends to defeat his greatest enemies - Black Bellamy and Cutlass Liz - in the competition for the title of Pirate of the Year.His faithful, although slightly crazy crew will help him achieve his goal.The captain and his companions face quite a challenge.What stands in their way is, among others:young Charles Darwin and the privateers of the cruel Queen Victoria.An adventurous family film directed by Peter Lord, who received his third Oscar nomination for this picture.The plot of the film was taken from a series of books by Gideon Defoe.In the Polish language version, the voices of the characters were provided by, among others:Waldemar Barwiński, Grzegorz Kwiecień, Karol Wróblewski and Izabella Bukowska.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Lord</director>
      <director>Jeff Newitt</director>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423102000 +0500" stop="20260423115500 +0500">
    <title>The Best Christmas Pageant Ever</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Herdman clan has a bad reputation in the town.Unruly siblings steal and bully their peers.Wherever he appears, he causes chaos and goes completely unpunished.Meanwhile, the residents, under the direction of the newly elected organizer, Grace (Judy Greer), are preparing for the annual Christmas nativity play.To everyone's surprise, Gladys Herdman (Kynlee Heiman) and her relatives want to appear in the show.Grace casts a girl as Mary, which complicates preparations for the play and causes widespread dissatisfaction.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Dallas Jenkins</director>
      <actor>Grace - Judy Greer</actor>
      <actor>Self - Narrator - Lauren Graham</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Grady - Elizabeth Tabish</actor>
      <actor>Reverend Hopkins - Kirk B.R. Woller</actor>
      <actor>First-grade teacher - Vanessa Benavente</actor>
      <actor>Bob - Pete Holmes</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Thomas - Stephanie Sy</actor>
      <actor>Gladys Herdman - Kynlee Heiman</actor>
      <actor>Imogene Herdman - Beatrice Schneider</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Molly Belle Wright</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423115500 +0500" stop="20260423131000 +0500">
    <title>Little Emma</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A little girl named Emma was raised by animals.Her life is full of warmth and joy, until one of her friends discovers the unpleasant truth that she was actually adopted and is not part of their family.Devastated, Emma sets out on a journey to find her loved ones.Along the way, he gathers an extraordinary team, including the clumsy inventor Żółwik Bystrzak, the ambitious scientist Edward Wilk and the brave Weasel Sancho.Together they are looking for a mysterious island which, according to legend, is inhabited by tiny people.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Leo Lewis</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423131000 +0500" stop="20260423145500 +0500">
    <title>Wolfgang (extraordinari)</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the sudden death of his mother, nine-year-old Wolfgang (Jordi Catalán), an exceptionally gifted boy with features on the autism spectrum, is forced to live with his father, Carles (Miki Esparbé), whom he has never met before.An orderly nine-year-old who strives for perfection cannot stand his father's chaotic lifestyle.He wants to escape to Paris to study at the Grimald Academy and become the best pianist in the world.When Carles discovers his plan, he must make the most important decision in his life: follow his dream of an acting career or sacrifice his plans and become the father Wolfgang really needs.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Ruiz Caldera</director>
      <actor>Carlos - Miki Esparbé</actor>
      <actor>Matilde - Angels Gonyalons</actor>
      <actor>Paco - Berto Romero</actor>
      <actor>Mia - Anna Castillo</actor>
      <actor>Ingrid - Nausicaa Bonnín</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Ruth Llopis</actor>
      <actor>Juana - Montse Alcoverro</actor>
      <actor>Director Serie - Dafnis Balduz</actor>
      <actor>Directora de Casting - Reichel Delgado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423145500 +0500" stop="20260423162000 +0500">
    <title>The Addams Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Gomez and Morticia Addams are looking for a safe place to live and raise their children.Therefore, they move to a dark, abandoned mansion in New Jersey.The estate is surrounded by swamps and hidden on top of a mountain amidst thick fog.13 years have passed.Gomez teaches the family's traditional saber fighting to Pugslay's son.Meanwhile, Morticia must face daughter Wednesday's questions about life outside the mansion gates.Soon, TV star Margaux Needler appears in the area and starts building a modern housing estate.Her plans are hindered by the fact that the Addams residence does not fit the modernist vision of the theme park.The woman decides to get rid of the strange family.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Conrad Vernon</director>
      <director>Greg Tiernan</director>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423162000 +0500" stop="20260423171000 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Exit Event</sub-title>
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Alec Berg</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423171000 +0500" stop="20260423190000 +0500">
    <title>Completement cramé</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A widowed, wealthy Englishman, Andrew Blake (John Malkovich), goes to France, the homeland of his beloved wife.When he arrives at the stately mansion with a suitcase, to his surprise he is not mistaken for a guest, but a candidate for a butler.To stay as long as possible in the place where he met the love of his life years ago, he accepts a job offer and does not reveal the real destination of his trip to anyone.He meets the owner of the historic mansion, the widow Nathalie Beauvillier (Fanny Ardant), the housekeeper and cook Odile (Émilie Dequenne), the maid Manon (Eugénie Anselin) and the estate manager Philippe.Over time, he becomes friends with the residents and helps them look at their lives from a different perspective.Thanks to this, he also finds his lost joy and motivation to act.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gilles Legardinier</director>
      <actor>Andrew Blake - John Malkovich</actor>
      <actor>Nathalie Beauvillier - Fanny Ardant</actor>
      <actor>Odile - Émilie Dequenne</actor>
      <actor>Magnier - Philippe Bas</actor>
      <actor>Manon - Eugenie Anselin</actor>
      <actor>Mme Berliner - Christel Henon</actor>
      <actor>Passer-by - Daniel Kovacs</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423190000 +0500" stop="20260423204500 +0500">
    <title>Tempete</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Zoe (Carmen Kassovitz) grew up surrounded by horses in her parents' (Mélanie Laurent and Pio Marmai) racing stable.This is her place on earth.He dreams of one day becoming a jockey like his father.When a new foal is born, the girl is the first to notice its potential to become a champion.The family's life changes one tragic night, when a scared mare accidentally injures Zoe.The teenager, overcome with despair, completely breaks down.Thanks to the support of her parents and the help of the stable boy (Kacey Mottet Klein), who has an extraordinary gift for communicating with horses, Zoe decides to overcome adversity and regain what seemed lost.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christian Duguay</director>
      <actor>Marie - Mélanie Laurent</actor>
      <actor>Philippe - Pio Marmai</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Carmen Kassovitz</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Charlie Paulet</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - June Benard</actor>
      <actor>Monsieur Cooper - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Madame Cooper - Carole Bouquet</actor>
      <actor>Sébastien - Kacey Mottet Klein</actor>
      <actor>Haddid - Atmen Kelif</actor>
      <actor>Éric - Antoine Cholet</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423204500 +0500" stop="20260423223000 +0500">
    <title>You're Cordially Invited</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A booking error causes two weddings to take place in one place at the same time.Both families face the challenge of having to share space.However, they have no intention of letting anything stop them from organizing a special ceremony for their loved one.Jim (Will Ferrell), the father of Jenni (Geraldine Viswanathan), who is getting ready to marry, and Margot (Reese Witherspoon), sister of the second bride, Neve (Meredith Hagner), try to keep their cool in a difficult situation, but they are still fighting a desperate duel.A comedy directed by Nicholas Stoller, the creator of "Neighbors".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Jim - Will Ferrell</actor>
      <actor>Margot - Reese Witherspoon</actor>
      <actor>Jenni - Geraldine Viswanathan</actor>
      <actor>Neve - Meredith Hagner</actor>
      <actor>Dixon - Jimmy Tatro</actor>
      <actor>Oliver - Stony Blyden</actor>
      <actor>Gwyneth - Leanne Morgan</actor>
      <actor>Colton - Rory Scovel</actor>
      <actor>Heather - Keyla Monterroso Mejia</actor>
      <actor>Kelly - Ramona Young</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423223000 +0500" stop="20260423235500 +0500">
    <title>Infinitely Polar Bear</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1970s, Boston.Cam Stuart (Mark Ruffalo) suffers from bipolar disorder.Due to his illness, he had to be hospitalized and lost his job.One day, his wife, nurse Maggie (Zoe Saldana), accepts a scholarship to New York University.The MBA degree obtained there will help her find a well-paid job, thanks to which she will provide for her family and take care of her children's education.While staying in another city, her husband has to take care of his daughters - adolescent Amelia (Imogene Wolodarsky) and Faith (Ashley Aufderheide).He faces an exceptionally difficult task.Girls are often embarrassed by the behavior of their father, who keeps coming up with various unusual ideas.However, they help him face everyday challenges.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Maya Forbes</director>
      <actor>Cam Stuart - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Maggie Stuart - Zoe Saldana</actor>
      <actor>Faith Stuart - Ashley Aufderheide</actor>
      <actor>Pauline Stuart - Beth Dixon</actor>
      <actor>Amelia Stuart - Imogene Wolodarsky</actor>
      <actor>Kim - Nekhebet Kum Juch</actor>
      <actor>Thurgood - Manoah Angelo</actor>
      <actor>Gaga - Muriel Gould</actor>
      <actor>Ruth-Ann - Tod Randolph</actor>
      <actor>Murray Stuart - Keir Dullea</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423235500 +0500" stop="20260424014500 +0500">
    <title>Ghostlight</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Grieving construction worker Dan (Keith Kupferer) joins a local theater group working on a production of Romeo and Juliet.There are changes in his life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kelly O'Sullivan</director>
      <director>Alex Thompson</director>
      <actor>Dan - Keith Kupferer</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Tara Mallen</actor>
      <actor>Rita - Dolly De Leon</actor>
      <actor>Lanora - Hanna Dworkin</actor>
      <actor>Daisy - Katherine Kupferer</actor>
      <actor>Greg - Dexter Zollicoffer</actor>
      <actor>Jonah - H.B. Ward</actor>
      <actor>Lucian - Tommy Rivera-Vega</actor>
      <actor>Moira - Alma Washington</actor>
      <actor>Mikey - Matthew C. Yee</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424014500 +0500" stop="20260424022500 +0500">
    <title>Heated Rivalry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two ice hockey players, Shane Hollander (Hudson Williams) and Ilya Rozanov (Connor Storrie), are united not only by ambition and the need for competition, but also by a magnetic attraction that neither of them fully understands.What begins as a secret romance between two debutants turns into an extraordinary love journey.Athletes spend eight years chasing fame on the ice rink while trying to deal with their feelings off it.They must decide whether there is room for something as fragile as love in a world of brutal competition.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Jacob Tierney</director>
      <actor>Shane Hollander - Hudson Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ilya Rozanov - Connor Storrie</actor>
      <actor>Scott Hunter - François Arnaud</actor>
      <actor>Yuna Hollander - Christina Chang</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Marleau - Franco Lo Presti</actor>
      <actor>Hayden Pike - Callan Potter</actor>
      <actor>Svetlana - Ksenia Daniela Kharlamova</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #2 - Shaun Starr</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #1 - Conor McKenna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424022500 +0500" stop="20260424032000 +0500">
    <title>The dragon's bloodline</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Black Queen</sub-title>
    <desc>The history of House Targaryen.Its leader, Viserys I (Paddy Considine), ruler of the Seven Kingdoms, decides to break with tradition.The king appoints his daughter, Princess Rhaenyra (Milly Alcock and Emma D'Arcy), as heir to the Iron Throne.This step leads to the initiation of a conflict within the family, called the Dance of Dragons.After the ruler's death, the fratricidal fight breaks out with renewed force.Also taking part in it are:Rhaenyra's brother, Aegon (Tom Glynn-Carney), and Alicent Hightower (Emily Carey and Olivia Cooke), the second wife of Viserys I. The events told in the series precede the action of "Game of Thrones" by 200 years.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Greg Yaitanes</director>
      <actor>King Viserys Targaryen - Paddy Considine</actor>
      <actor>Prince Daemon Targaryen - Matt Smith</actor>
      <actor>Lord Corlys Velaryon - Steve Toussaint</actor>
      <actor>Princess Rhaenys Velaryon - Eve Best</actor>
      <actor>Otto Hightower - Rhys Ifans</actor>
      <actor>Mysaria - Sonoya Mizuno</actor>
      <actor>Ser Criston Cole - Fabien Frankel</actor>
      <actor>Ser Harwin 'Breakbones' Strong - Ryan Corr</actor>
      <actor>Lord Jason Lannister - Jefferson Hall</actor>
      <actor>Grand Maester Mellos - David Horovitch</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Serial Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424032000 +0500" stop="20260424040000 +0500">
    <title>Peacemaker 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Need I Say Door</sub-title>
    <desc>Two years have passed since the last events.Chris Smith (John Cena) considers himself a real hero.However, he must earn the recognition of other heroes.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Christopher Smith - John Cena</actor>
      <actor>Leota Adebayo - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Adrian Chase - Freddie Stroma</actor>
      <actor>Agent Emilia Harcourt - Jennifer Holland</actor>
      <actor>John Economos - Steve Agee</actor>
      <actor>Eagly - Dee Bradley Baker</actor>
      <actor>Clemson Murn - Chukwudi Iwuji</actor>
      <actor>Auggie Smith - Robert Patrick</actor>
      <actor>Detective Sophie Song - Annie Chang</actor>
      <actor>Detective Larry Fitzgibbon - Lochlyn Munro</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Action-Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424040000 +0500" stop="20260424054500 +0500">
    <title>Good Guy With A Gun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the violent death of his father, teenage Will (Beck Nolan) and his mother, Tessa Greenwood (Tiffany Bedwell), move to a small town in Illinois.There is a house they inherited from an ancestor, which the woman intends to sell.There, Will meets boys his own age and quickly becomes friends with them.The new friends are fascinated by the weapons each of them has and spend time practicing their shooting skills.Will begins to share their passion, which even worsens his already not good relationship with his mother, complicates the mourning for his father, and even puts the boy's life in danger.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John Mossman</director>
      <actor>Duke - Dan Waller</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - Ian Barford</actor>
      <actor>Auggie - Morgan Allen</actor>
      <actor>Donelle - Liv Shine</actor>
      <actor>Tom Greenwood - Joe Swanberg</actor>
      <actor>Officer Osborne - John LaFlamboy</actor>
      <actor>Philip - David Pasquesi</actor>
      <actor>Anna - Jennifer Jelsema</actor>
      <actor>Marilyn - Elizabeth Laidlaw</actor>
      <actor>Noreen - Skye Shrum</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424054500 +0500" stop="20260424072500 +0500">
    <title>La extorsión</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Experienced airline pilot Alejandro Petrossián (Guillermo Francella) does not want to retire yet, although he is approaching that age.He begins to be blackmailed by the secret services, which threaten him with revealing the bad results of his hearing tests, which would result in the immediate end of his career.Alejandro has to carry several suitcases on subsequent flights from Buenos Aires to Madrid.Although he is not allowed to ask any questions, the pilot is intrigued by the contents of the briefcases, which causes him to plunge into the world of intrigue and corruption, which endangers both the life of the man himself and his loved ones.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Martino Zaidelis</director>
      <actor>Alejandro Petrossián - Guillermo Francella</actor>
      <actor>Saavedra - Pablo Rago</actor>
      <actor>Carolina Guerrero - Andrea Frigerio</actor>
      <actor>Porchietto - Alberto Ajaka</actor>
      <actor>Fernando Marconi - Guillermo Arengo</actor>
      <actor>Mario Aldana - Carlos Portaluppi</actor>
      <actor>Rita Tirabosco - Mónica Villa</actor>
      <actor>Andrés Sadik - Juan Lo Sasso</actor>
      <actor>Cristaldo - Joselo Bella</actor>
      <actor>Beltramino - Osvaldo Djeredjian</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424072500 +0500" stop="20260424090000 +0500">
    <title>Infinitely Polar Bear</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1970s, Boston.Cam Stuart (Mark Ruffalo) suffers from bipolar disorder.Due to his illness, he had to be hospitalized and lost his job.One day, his wife, nurse Maggie (Zoe Saldana), accepts a scholarship to New York University.The MBA degree obtained there will help her find a well-paid job, thanks to which she will provide for her family and take care of her children's education.While staying in another city, her husband has to take care of his daughters - adolescent Amelia (Imogene Wolodarsky) and Faith (Ashley Aufderheide).He faces an exceptionally difficult task.Girls are often embarrassed by the behavior of their father, who keeps coming up with various unusual ideas.However, they help him face everyday challenges.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Maya Forbes</director>
      <actor>Cam Stuart - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Maggie Stuart - Zoe Saldana</actor>
      <actor>Faith Stuart - Ashley Aufderheide</actor>
      <actor>Pauline Stuart - Beth Dixon</actor>
      <actor>Amelia Stuart - Imogene Wolodarsky</actor>
      <actor>Kim - Nekhebet Kum Juch</actor>
      <actor>Thurgood - Manoah Angelo</actor>
      <actor>Gaga - Muriel Gould</actor>
      <actor>Ruth-Ann - Tod Randolph</actor>
      <actor>Murray Stuart - Keir Dullea</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424090000 +0500" stop="20260424104500 +0500">
    <title>Tempete</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Zoe (Carmen Kassovitz) grew up surrounded by horses in her parents' (Mélanie Laurent and Pio Marmai) racing stable.This is her place on earth.He dreams of one day becoming a jockey like his father.When a new foal is born, the girl is the first to notice its potential to become a champion.The family's life changes one tragic night, when a scared mare accidentally injures Zoe.The teenager, overcome with despair, completely breaks down.Thanks to the support of her parents and the help of the stable boy (Kacey Mottet Klein), who has an extraordinary gift for communicating with horses, Zoe decides to overcome adversity and regain what seemed lost.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christian Duguay</director>
      <actor>Marie - Mélanie Laurent</actor>
      <actor>Philippe - Pio Marmai</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Carmen Kassovitz</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Charlie Paulet</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - June Benard</actor>
      <actor>Monsieur Cooper - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Madame Cooper - Carole Bouquet</actor>
      <actor>Sébastien - Kacey Mottet Klein</actor>
      <actor>Haddid - Atmen Kelif</actor>
      <actor>Éric - Antoine Cholet</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424104500 +0500" stop="20260424123000 +0500">
    <title>You're Cordially Invited</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A booking error causes two weddings to take place in one place at the same time.Both families face the challenge of having to share space.However, they have no intention of letting anything stop them from organizing a special ceremony for their loved one.Jim (Will Ferrell), the father of Jenni (Geraldine Viswanathan), who is getting ready to marry, and Margot (Reese Witherspoon), sister of the second bride, Neve (Meredith Hagner), try to keep their cool in a difficult situation, but they are still fighting a desperate duel.A comedy directed by Nicholas Stoller, the creator of "Neighbors".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Jim - Will Ferrell</actor>
      <actor>Margot - Reese Witherspoon</actor>
      <actor>Jenni - Geraldine Viswanathan</actor>
      <actor>Neve - Meredith Hagner</actor>
      <actor>Dixon - Jimmy Tatro</actor>
      <actor>Oliver - Stony Blyden</actor>
      <actor>Gwyneth - Leanne Morgan</actor>
      <actor>Colton - Rory Scovel</actor>
      <actor>Heather - Keyla Monterroso Mejia</actor>
      <actor>Kelly - Ramona Young</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424123000 +0500" stop="20260424142000 +0500">
    <title>The Last Vermeer</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Netherlands after World War II.The accountability of Nazi criminals and their accomplices continues.A Jew, Joseph Piller (Claes Bang), who fought in the resistance movement, is to deal with the case of stolen works of art.He accuses the eccentric painter Han van Meegeren (Guy Pearce) of collaboration, who hosted Germans at his home for hedonistic parties and sold them valuable paintings.The artist faces a death sentence.However, he claims that he traded in fakes he created.His exquisitely crafted fakes are indistinguishable from the originals.Although the evidence points to van Meegeren's guilt, and accepting his version would make the brilliant forger a national hero, Piller begins to believe him.Together with her assistant (Vicky Krieps), she tries to prove his innocence, putting her career and good name on the line.Based on facts, the extraordinary story of a Dutch painter and one of the best art forgers in history.It was based on the biography of Han van Meegeren by Jonathan Lopez.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Dan Friedkin</director>
      <actor>Han Van Meegeren - Guy Pearce</actor>
      <actor>Joseph Piller - Claes Bang</actor>
      <actor>Minna Holmberg - Vicky Krieps</actor>
      <actor>Esper Dekker - Roland Moller</actor>
      <actor>Alex De Klerks - August Diehl</actor>
      <actor>Bernard Bakker - Karl Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Maarten Wooning - Andrew Havill</actor>
      <actor>Chief Judge - Paul Bentall</actor>
      <actor>Cootje Henning - Olivia Grant</actor>
      <actor>Dirk Hannema - Adrian Scarborough</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424142000 +0500" stop="20260424163000 +0500">
    <title>Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1926. A slightly lost, nice Englishman, Newt Scamander, returns from an international research expedition, during which he had to find and describe as many species of fantastic animals as possible.He is carrying a mysterious suitcase with unknown contents.On the way he stops in New York.America is different from his homeland.It is forbidden to possess or transport magical creatures.Newt gets into trouble when it comes to light that his briefcase contains creatures considered dangerous.A researcher who is aware of their uniqueness does everything to ensure that they do not become extinct.Due to his inattention, several peculiar specimens find their way into the real world.Even more chaos is caused by a powerful force that threatens people's lives.Mr. Graves tries to erase the memories of people who witness her actions.The Muggle Jakub becomes involved in the course of events.Scamander must control the situation as quickly as possible and discover the source of the problem.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Yates</director>
      <actor>Newt - Eddie Redmayne</actor>
      <actor>Tina - Katherine Waterston</actor>
      <actor>Queenie - Alison Sudol</actor>
      <actor>Graves - Colin Farrell</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Kowalski - Dan Fogler</actor>
      <actor>Customs Official - Sam Redford</actor>
      <actor>Customs Official - Scott Goldman</actor>
      <actor>Witness - Tim Bentinck</actor>
      <actor>Reporter - Tristan Tait</actor>
      <actor>Photographer 2 - Tom Clarke Hill</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424163000 +0500" stop="20260424170000 +0500">
    <title>Veep</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Fundraiser</sub-title>
    <desc>Washington.Former senator Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) is nominated for Vice President of the United States.She quickly discovers that the new job is not what she dreamed of, but everything she feared.The woman, together with her closest colleagues: Gary (Tony Hale), her office manager Amy (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike (Matt Walsh), ambitious political assistant Dan (Reid Scott), young White House liaison officer Jonah (Timothy C. Simons) and assistant Sue (Sufe Bradshaw), wants to do something significant in politics without getting involved in suspicious games and deals.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Armando Iannucci</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer, Chief of Staff  - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Sue  - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Carson Larchspein - Ken Bulcroft</actor>
      <actor>Selina's Secret Service - Justin Doescher</actor>
      <actor>Secret Service Agent In Charge  - Marcus LaRon</actor>
      <actor>VP Bullpen staffer 'Helen' - Jennifer McCormick</actor>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424170000 +0500" stop="20260424172500 +0500">
    <title>Veep</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Frozen Yoghurt</sub-title>
    <desc>Washington.Former senator Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) is nominated for Vice President of the United States.She quickly discovers that the new job is not what she dreamed of, but everything she feared.The woman, together with her closest colleagues: Gary (Tony Hale), her office manager Amy (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike (Matt Walsh), ambitious political assistant Dan (Reid Scott), young White House liaison officer Jonah (Timothy C. Simons) and assistant Sue (Sufe Bradshaw), wants to do something significant in politics without getting involved in suspicious games and deals.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Armando Iannucci</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer, Chief of Staff  - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Sue  - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Carson Larchspein - Ken Bulcroft</actor>
      <actor>Selina's Secret Service - Justin Doescher</actor>
      <actor>Secret Service Agent In Charge  - Marcus LaRon</actor>
      <actor>VP Bullpen staffer 'Helen' - Jennifer McCormick</actor>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424172500 +0500" stop="20260424191500 +0500">
    <title>Arrival</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Spaceships land in twelve different places on Earth.No one knows why the aliens chose these locations.The American military is trying to solve the mystery.For this purpose, the soldiers build a camp next to one of the mysterious objects.A talented linguist, Dr. Louise Banks, is called there.Together with Colonel G.T.Weber and physicist Ian Donnelly tries to find out what the real intentions of aliens are and determine whether humanity is in danger from them.Soon, Louise is sent to a spaceship to talk to representatives of an alien civilization.He must unravel the rules of the newcomers' language.He realizes that time plays a key role in the mysterious message.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>Louise Banks - Amy Adams</actor>
      <actor>Ian Donnelly - Jeremy Renner</actor>
      <actor>Colonel Weber - Forest Whitaker</actor>
      <actor>Agent Halpern - Michael Stuhlbarg</actor>
      <actor>Captain Marks - Mark O'Brien</actor>
      <actor>General Shang - Tzi Ma</actor>
      <actor>8-Year-Old-Hannah - Abigail Pniowsky</actor>
      <actor>12-Year-Old-Hannah - Julia Scarlett Dan</actor>
      <actor>6-Year-Old-Hannah - Jadyn Malone</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Kettler - Frank Schorpion</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424191500 +0500" stop="20260424203500 +0500">
    <title>A Picture Of Her</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Beth (Rhiannon Fish) works as first mate on a fishing vessel.He goes ashore for a while to take care of his aunt (Samantha Ferris), who has broken her leg.During her daily shopping, photographer Jake (Tyler Hynes) secretly takes a photo of her choosing flowers.A freelancer sends a photo of a stranger to a newspaper under a pseudonym.Some time later, Beth and Jake meet in person.They both turn out to be dog lovers, and over time they discover that they have a lot in common.The lovers' relationship is getting closer.Then Beth's photo appears on the cover of a magazine and goes viral, making her very popular.The woman wants to find the author, meanwhile Jake does not have the courage to confess the truth.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Robinson</director>
      <director>Michael Robison</director>
      <actor>Jake - Tyler Hynes</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Rhiannon Fish</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Dody - Samantha Ferris</actor>
      <actor>Captain Mark - Robert Wisden</actor>
      <actor>Candace - Alison Araya</actor>
      <actor>Janice - Aadila Dosani</actor>
      <actor>Richie Rosebrook - Gavin Langelo</actor>
      <actor>Jaypeg - Seth Whittaker</actor>
      <actor>Cool Rocker - Mark James</actor>
      <actor>Date Woman - Felicia Chiappetta</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424203500 +0500" stop="20260424223000 +0500">
    <title>Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Four high school students, as part of a punishment imposed by the principal, have to clean up the cluttered school basement.The collected items include an old console from the 1990s and the Jumanji game.Intrigued, the teenagers decide to activate the device.In this way, they are drawn into the virtual world.They end up in a dangerous jungle, where, as avatars, they are forced to fight for survival.Spencer becomes a brave adventurer, Fridge turns into a zoologist, Bethany becomes a corpulent paleontology professor who knows his way around maps, and Martha becomes a martial arts expert.On their way, they meet a guide who tells them the purpose of the mission.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Kasdan</director>
      <actor>Spencer - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Fridge - Kevin Hart</actor>
      <actor>Bethany - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Martha - Karen Gillan</actor>
      <actor>Nigel - Rhys Darby</actor>
      <actor>Van Pelt - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Alex - Nick Jonas</actor>
      <actor>Młody Spencer - Alex Wolff</actor>
      <actor>Młody Fridge - Ser'Darius Blain</actor>
      <actor>Młoda Bethany - Madison Iseman</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260424223000 +0500" stop="20260425000000 +0500">
    <title>The Addams Family 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Morticia and Gomez are distraught that their children are growing up so fast.Wednesday and Pugsley increasingly prefer to spend time alone rather than devote it to their parents.Morticia is downright distraught that her children even neglect meals together.To reconnect with her offspring, Gomez comes up with a great idea.He even forces Wednesday, Pugsley, Uncle Fester and the rest of the gang into a haunted camper to go with them on their last, completely miserable family vacation.Traveling across America is full of adventures.During this time, the family will face many complications.She organizes a barrel race in Niagara Falls, visits the Headless Horseman's hometown, causes a massive explosion in the Grand Canyon, and finally causes a collective panic attack during a girls' talent competition.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Greg Tiernan</director>
      <director>Conrad Vernon</director>
      <director>Laura Brousseau</director>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>