<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505033000 +0500" stop="20260505050500 +0500">
    <title>Killer Heat</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greece.American Nick Bali (Joseph Gordon-Levitt) is hired to investigate the circumstances of the death of young shipping magnate Leo Vardakis (Richard Madden) in Crete.The deceased's sister-in-law, Penelope Vardakis (Shailene Woodley), does not believe the official police report.A private detective discovers that sunny landscapes hide many dark secrets and anyone can be a suspect.He discovers further facts about the rich and influential Vardakis family, as well as the brothers' complicated relationship.Adaptation of the story "The Jealousy Man" by Jo Nesbo.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Philippe Lacôte</director>
      <actor>Nick Bali - Joseph Gordon-Levitt</actor>
      <actor>Penelope Vardakis - Shailene Woodley</actor>
      <actor>Elias 'Leonidas' - Richard Madden</actor>
      <actor>Audrey - Clare Holman</actor>
      <actor>Georges Mensah - Babou Ceesay</actor>
      <actor>Monique - Abbey Lee</actor>
      <actor>Victoria - Eleni Vergeti</actor>
      <actor>Yannis - Emmanouil Gavridakis</actor>
      <actor>Governor - Dimitris Topalidis</actor>
      <actor>Christopher - Christos Efthimiou</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505050500 +0500" stop="20260505071500 +0500">
    <title>NO</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Animal tamer OJ Haywood (Daniel Kaluuya) and his sister Emerald (Keke Palmer) live on a ranch in southern California where horses are trained for Hollywood film productions.They take over the business of their father, who died in suspicious circumstances.Problems are piling up for them.One day they become witnesses of inexplicable phenomena.Together with a former child star (Steven Yeun), an emcee at a family amusement park, they try to film supernatural incidents to make money by selling sensational materials.Their actions have unforeseen consequences.Director Jordan Peele made his debut in 2017 with the acclaimed thriller "Get Out!", for which he won an Oscar for the script.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jordan Peele</director>
      <actor>OJ Haywood - Daniel Kaluuya</actor>
      <actor>Emerald Haywood - Keke Palmer</actor>
      <actor>Angel Torres - Brandon Perea</actor>
      <actor>Antlers Holst - Michael Wincott</actor>
      <actor>Ricky 'Jupe' Park - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Amber Park - Wrenn Schmidt</actor>
      <actor>Otis Haywood Sr. - Keith David</actor>
      <actor>Ryder Muybridge - Devon Graye</actor>
      <actor>Gordy - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Nessie - Barbie Ferreira</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505071500 +0500" stop="20260505090000 +0500">
    <title>Your Monster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Actress Laura (Melissa Barrera) was supposed to become a star of the stage and live happily with the director of the show, Jacob (Edmund Donovan), but her beloved dumped her and took the role away.The devastated woman returns to her family home, where she spends all day in a bathrobe and crying.Her wailing gets on the nerves of the monster (Tommy Dewey), who has been living in the closet for years.The monster gives Laura two weeks to move out and threatens bloody revenge.Over time, however, an extraordinary bond develops between them, which helps Laura open her heart and follow her dreams.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Caroline Lindy</director>
      <actor>Laura Franco - Melissa Barrera</actor>
      <actor>Monster - Tommy Dewey</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Sullivan - Edmund Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Mazie Silverberg - Kayla Foster</actor>
      <actor>Jackie Dennon - Meghann Fahy</actor>
      <actor>Don McBride - Ikechukwu Ufomadu</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Megan Haley</actor>
      <actor>Will - Brandon Victor Dixon</actor>
      <actor>Scotty - Taylor Trensch</actor>
      <actor>Ellyn - Lana Young</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505090000 +0500" stop="20260505103500 +0500">
    <title>The Glassworker</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vincent Oliver, the son of renowned glassmaker Tomasz, is preparing for his first exhibition when he finds a letter from his childhood friend, Alliz Amano, whom he has always loved.He recalls how - raised by a pacifist father - he saw her for the first time.Alliz arrives in Vincent's city, Waterfront, with her parent, Colonel Amano.They become a couple.Meanwhile, a war breaks out and both he and his rival for the girl's favor, Malik, join the army.Tomasz is forced to produce glass rectifiers for the army.Some time later, the girl's father dies without any news at the front.When Malik returns to town with him, Alliz rewards him with a kiss, which Vincent witnesses.Devastated, he sabotages the production of rectifiers, but this leads to tragedy.The anime-inspired production with an anti-war message is the first Pakistani film made using the hand-animated technique.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Usman Riaz</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505103500 +0500" stop="20260505121000 +0500">
    <title>Verano en diciembre</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Four generations of women meet in Madrid at a convention organized by Teresa.She is accompanied by four daughters in their thirties, a granddaughter and her 95-year-old mother-in-law, who suffers from dementia.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Carolina África</director>
      <actor>Teresa - Carmen Machi</actor>
      <actor>Carmen - Bárbara Lennie</actor>
      <actor>Paloma - Vicky Luengo</actor>
      <actor>Martina - Lola Cordón</actor>
      <actor>Alicia - Beatriz Grimaldos</actor>
      <actor>Zoe - Vega Bosque</actor>
      <actor>Don Ramón - Antonio Resines</actor>
      <actor>Noelia - Irene Escolar</actor>
      <actor>Rodrigo - Nacho Fresneda</actor>
      <actor>Mujer de Rodrigo - Silvia Marsó</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505121000 +0500" stop="20260505140000 +0500">
    <title>Oscar's Eye</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nine-year-old Oscar cannot speak.Because of this, he is rejected and bullied by his peers.However, he becomes friends with the owner of the workshop, Eric, with whom he shares a common passion - photography.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jay Silverman</director>
      <actor>Eric Conway - Beau Bridges</actor>
      <actor>Evelyn Kennedy - Jessica Parker Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Frank Flynn - Bruce Davison</actor>
      <actor>Victor Kennedy - Scotty Tovar</actor>
      <actor>Oscar Kennedy - Miguel Gabriel</actor>
      <actor>Dermot Flynn - Ross Partridge</actor>
      <actor>Manny - Jorge Pallo</actor>
      <actor>Tony - Ayinde Howell</actor>
      <actor>Jim - Bob Bledsoe</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Ezekiel Bridges</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505140000 +0500" stop="20260505154500 +0500">
    <title>Frieda's Case</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 1904. A seamstress accused of a crime becomes the center of a trial that exposes the injustices of the legal system.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Maria Brendle</director>
      <actor>Frieda Keller - Julia Buchmann</actor>
      <actor>Walter Gmür - Stefan Merki</actor>
      <actor>Erna Gmür - Rachel Braunschweig</actor>
      <actor>Gesine - Marlene Tanczik</actor>
      <actor>Arnold Janggen - Max Simonischek</actor>
      <actor>Bertha - Liliane Amuat</actor>
      <actor>Frau Hartmann - Bigna Körner</actor>
      <actor>Landjäger Schönenberger - Aaron Hitz</actor>
      <actor>Arbeiterin - Ramona Saluz</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505154500 +0500" stop="20260505161000 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Shutdown</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Becky Martin</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505161000 +0500" stop="20260505164000 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">First Response</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Armando Iannucci</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505164000 +0500" stop="20260505181500 +0500">
    <title>Tripped Up</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lizzy (Leah Lewis) has always dreamed of becoming a chef.However, participating in a culinary reality show and later working in a New York restaurant became a source of frustration for her.A cooking enthusiast is one step away from giving up her greatest passion.The last chance to stay in the catering industry is to participate in a culinary festival.Together with her friends, Mary (Ashley Moore), Kai (Ariel Winter) and Taylor (Sasha Fox), she sets off on an adventure.If she fails, she is ready to look for another path in life.Unfortunately, the team has been plagued by bad luck since the beginning of the expedition.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Shruti Ganguly</director>
      <actor>Lizzy - Leah Lewis</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Ashley Moore</actor>
      <actor>Kai - Ariel Winter</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Sasha Fox</actor>
      <actor>Patty - Vanessa L. Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ashley - Jo Ellen Pellman</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Danny Kornfeld</actor>
      <actor>Jose - Gil Perez-Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Missy - Judy Gold</actor>
      <actor>Lotus - Justin Guarini</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505181500 +0500" stop="20260505202500 +0500">
    <title>Little women</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The times of the Civil War.In the absence of their father, who is serving in the military away from the family, the four March sisters from Orchard House are cared for by their mother alone.Marmee wants them to find their own path and helps them enter adulthood.Each of them has a different personality.The oldest Meg dreams of becoming an actress.Family-oriented and warm, Beth has a talent for playing the piano.Jo, an aspiring writer, pursues her goal with her characteristic energy and tenacity.Amy, a bit smart, wants to become a painter.Despite their own problems, the girls are not indifferent to other people's suffering.Young women will get to know the taste of first loves and disappointments.Fate subjects them to tests, after which their lives will never be the same again.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Greta Gerwig</director>
      <actor>Jo March - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Meg March - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Amy March - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Beth March - Eliza Scanlen</actor>
      <actor>Marmee March - Laura Dern</actor>
      <actor>Theodore 'Laurie' Laurence - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Dashwood - Tracy Letts</actor>
      <actor>Father March - Bob Odenkirk</actor>
      <actor>John Brooke - James Norton</actor>
      <actor>Friedrich Bhaer - Louis Garrel</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505202500 +0500" stop="20260505223000 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: New Moon</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bella Swan (Kristen Stewart) celebrates her 18th birthday.The passing moments make her realize that she will one day grow old, while her boyfriend Edward Cullen (Robert Pattinson), who is a vampire, will always physically remain young.Despite this, the girl agrees to come to the party organized by the Cullen family.During her birthday party, Bella accidentally cuts her finger.At the sight of blood, one of the members of the vampire clan, Jasper (Jackson Rathbone), cannot stop feeling hungry.Unable to control himself, he attacks the girl.Edward saves his beloved, but decides not to put her in danger anymore.For her sake, he decides to leave the area.Before leaving, he tells Bella that he doesn't feel anything for her anymore.A lonely and betrayed teenager falls into depression.Only her acquaintance with a handsome Indian, Jacob Black (Taylor Lautner), helps her regain her balance.The boy falls in love with Bella, but hides his greatest secret from her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Weitz</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Alice Cullen - Ashley Greene</actor>
      <actor>Jasper Hale - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Swan - Billy Burke</actor>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505223000 +0500" stop="20260506000500 +0500">
    <title>Sanctuary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hal Porterfield (Christopher Abbott) orders room service at a posh hotel.Rebecca Marin (Margaret Qualley) shows up at the apartment to interview him for the position of general manager of this chain of facilities.Her questions become more and more personal and lead to a surprising ending.In reality, the woman is a dominatrix who follows the script prepared by Hal.However, the relationship does not follow the script ordered by the client.The woman decides to blackmail the rich man.She claims that she recorded a compromising sex tape with him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zachary Wigon</director>
      <actor>Hal - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Hallway - Francisco Castaneda</actor>
      <actor>Woman in the Hallway - Kathie Young</actor>
      <actor>Older Phil Porterfield - Dominic Defilips</actor>
      <actor>Younger Phil Porterfield - Rene Calvo</actor>
      <actor>Hal's Mother - Danita Battle</actor>
      <actor>Young Hal - Christian Casatelli</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506000500 +0500" stop="20260506015500 +0500">
    <title>Assassin's Creed</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Recidivist Callum Lynch sentenced to death is not executed.After a fake execution, he ends up in a secret laboratory.There he meets Rikkin and his daughter Sofia.Scientists have a mysterious device that allows them to access the records of ancestors' actions stored in their genes.The criminal is to connect with the consciousness of Aguilar from Spain, who lived during the Great Inquisition and obtained the Apple of Eden, which provides control over emotions.By using this item, you can supposedly eliminate aggression in people.The daredevil travels to the Middle Ages.He discovers that he is a descendant of a member of the Assassin secret society.Over time, he learns what a big mistake he made when he trusted Sofia and her father.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Justin Kurzel</director>
      <actor>Cal Lynch - Michael Fassbender</actor>
      <actor>Sofia - Marion Cotillard</actor>
      <actor>Rikkin - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Joseph Lynch - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Ellen Kaye - Charlotte Rampling</actor>
      <actor>Moussa - Michael K. Williams</actor>
      <actor>McGowan - Denis Ménochet</actor>
      <actor>Maria - Ariane Labed</actor>
      <actor>Sultan Muhammad XII - Khalid Abdalla</actor>
      <actor>Cal's Mother - Essie Davis</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506015500 +0500" stop="20260506035500 +0500">
    <title>The Alto Knights</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1957. Former friends from their teenage years, Frank Costello (Robert De Niro) and Vito Genovese (Robert De Niro), are now the most famous New York bosses, fighting for control of the city streets.When one day the first of them becomes the target of a failed assassination attempt by his rival, he decides it's time to step aside.He informs Vita about this, but he - a man paranoid about losing power - does not believe him.Soon he orders another attack.His victim is Albert Anastazja (Michael Rispoli), appointed by Frank as his successor.This event makes Costell realize that if he does not stop his rival, he will again attempt to kill both him and his loved ones.The conflict between two former friends and now rivals escalates, leading to a dramatic climax.A film inspired by real events.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Barry Levinson</director>
      <actor>Frank Costello - Robert De Niro</actor>
      <actor>Bobbie Costello - Debra Messing</actor>
      <actor>Anna Genovese - Kathrine Narducci</actor>
      <actor>Vincent Gigante - Cosmo Jarvis</actor>
      <actor>Albert Anastasia - Michael Rispoli</actor>
      <actor>Tony Bender - Robert Uricola</actor>
      <actor>Richie Boiardo - Frank Piccirillo</actor>
      <actor>George Wolf - Matt Servitto</actor>
      <actor>Joe Bonanno - Louis Mustillo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy Lucchese - Anthony J. Gallo</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Gangster Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506035500 +0500" stop="20260506053500 +0500">
    <title>Kneecap</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>2010. Liam (Mo Chara) and Naoise (Móglaí Bap) live in west Belfast.Growing up, they learned to speak Irish from the other's father, Arl (Michael Fassbender), who faked his own death to avoid repression from the British authorities and is now disillusioned with his son's hedonistic lifestyle.One night, Liam is arrested for drug possession.During interrogation, he refuses to speak English.So the police call in a translator, JJ Ó Dochartaigh (DJ Próvai), a music teacher at an Irish-speaking school.He helps Liam avoid charges and takes his notes with him.When at home he realizes that the lyrics are in Irish, he convinces the boy and his friend to start a hip-hop band, claiming that music would be a way to introduce the native language to the young generation.Liam names the group Kneecap.When the trio starts giving concerts, it turns out that crowds come to them.However, the musicians immediately begin to fall victim to sharp attacks from both the media and the extreme republican organization RRAD.Inspired by true events, the story of the creation of a popular Irish band.The main roles in the film were played by musicians who formed the group in reality.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rich Peppiatt</director>
      <actor>Naoise - Móglaí Bap</actor>
      <actor>Liam - Mo Chara</actor>
      <actor>JJ - DJ Próvai</actor>
      <actor>Detective Ellis - Josie Walker</actor>
      <actor>Caitlin - Fionnuala Flaherty</actor>
      <actor>Georgia - Jessica Reynolds</actor>
      <actor>Doyle - Adam Best</actor>
      <actor>Dolores - Simone Kirby</actor>
      <actor>Arló Ó Cairealláin - Michael Fassbender</actor>
      <actor>Sean - Matthew Sharpe</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506053500 +0500" stop="20260506072500 +0500">
    <title>Life</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Research carried out by a six-person team of cosmonauts is underway on the International Space Station.The crew makes a breakthrough discovery - they manage to observe the first evidence of life on Mars.However, the astronauts discover that the form of life they have found is unexpectedly intelligent, and at the same time dangerous.Behind the camera, Swedish director Daniel Espinosa, and on screen, among others:Oscar candidate Jake Gyllenhaal, Golden Globe nominees Rebecca Ferguson and Ryan Reynolds, and Hiroyuki Sanada - winner of the award granted by the Japanese Film Academy.The advantage of the production are its spectacular special effects.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Daniel Espinosa</director>
      <actor>David Jordan - Jake Gyllenhaal</actor>
      <actor>Sho Murakami - Hiroyuki Sanada</actor>
      <actor>Rory Adams - Ryan Reynolds</actor>
      <actor>Miranda North - Rebecca Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Ekaterina Golovkina - Olga Dihovichnaya</actor>
      <actor>Hugh Derry - Ariyon Bakare</actor>
      <actor>Student 2 - Jesus Del Orden</actor>
      <actor>Student 1 - Allen McLean</actor>
      <actor>Student 3 - Leila Grace</actor>
      <actor>Student 4 - Mari Gvelesiani</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506072500 +0500" stop="20260506090000 +0500">
    <title>Sanctuary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hal Porterfield (Christopher Abbott) orders room service at a posh hotel.Rebecca Marin (Margaret Qualley) shows up at the apartment to interview him for the position of general manager of this chain of facilities.Her questions become more and more personal and lead to a surprising ending.In reality, the woman is a dominatrix who follows the script prepared by Hal.However, the relationship does not follow the script ordered by the client.The woman decides to blackmail the rich man.She claims that she recorded a compromising sex tape with him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zachary Wigon</director>
      <actor>Hal - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Hallway - Francisco Castaneda</actor>
      <actor>Woman in the Hallway - Kathie Young</actor>
      <actor>Older Phil Porterfield - Dominic Defilips</actor>
      <actor>Younger Phil Porterfield - Rene Calvo</actor>
      <actor>Hal's Mother - Danita Battle</actor>
      <actor>Young Hal - Christian Casatelli</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506090000 +0500" stop="20260506103000 +0500">
    <title>Tripped Up</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lizzy (Leah Lewis) has always dreamed of becoming a chef.However, participating in a culinary reality show and later working in a New York restaurant became a source of frustration for her.A cooking enthusiast is one step away from giving up her greatest passion.The last chance to stay in the catering industry is to participate in a culinary festival.Together with her friends, Mary (Ashley Moore), Kai (Ariel Winter) and Taylor (Sasha Fox), she sets off on an adventure.If she fails, she is ready to look for another path in life.Unfortunately, the team has been plagued by bad luck since the beginning of the expedition.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Shruti Ganguly</director>
      <actor>Lizzy - Leah Lewis</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Ashley Moore</actor>
      <actor>Kai - Ariel Winter</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Sasha Fox</actor>
      <actor>Patty - Vanessa L. Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ashley - Jo Ellen Pellman</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Danny Kornfeld</actor>
      <actor>Jose - Gil Perez-Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Missy - Judy Gold</actor>
      <actor>Lotus - Justin Guarini</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506103000 +0500" stop="20260506124000 +0500">
    <title>Little women</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The times of the Civil War.In the absence of their father, who is serving in the military away from the family, the four March sisters from Orchard House are cared for by their mother alone.Marmee wants them to find their own path and helps them enter adulthood.Each of them has a different personality.The oldest Meg dreams of becoming an actress.Family-oriented and warm, Beth has a talent for playing the piano.Jo, an aspiring writer, pursues her goal with her characteristic energy and tenacity.Amy, a bit smart, wants to become a painter.Despite their own problems, the girls are not indifferent to other people's suffering.Young women will get to know the taste of first loves and disappointments.Fate subjects them to tests, after which their lives will never be the same again.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Greta Gerwig</director>
      <actor>Jo March - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Meg March - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Amy March - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Beth March - Eliza Scanlen</actor>
      <actor>Marmee March - Laura Dern</actor>
      <actor>Theodore 'Laurie' Laurence - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Dashwood - Tracy Letts</actor>
      <actor>Father March - Bob Odenkirk</actor>
      <actor>John Brooke - James Norton</actor>
      <actor>Friedrich Bhaer - Louis Garrel</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506124000 +0500" stop="20260506145000 +0500">
    <title>Spider-Man: Homecoming</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Young Peter Parker is fascinated by the Avengers team.He has the opportunity to experience an amazing adventure alongside his idols and unrivaled role models.After all, the teenager must return home and try to get used to his uninteresting everyday life as an ordinary mortal.He still lives with his good Aunt May, goes to college, and hangs out with friends.At the same time, he remains under the watchful care of Tony Stark, i.e. Iron Man - his mentor and greatest authority.He also tries to fight the pessimistic thoughts that plague him, that no one appreciates his activities, which bring so much benefit to society.Everything changes when it turns out that a new enemy is waiting for the superhero.One day, a dangerous Vulture appears on the boy's path.Peter must stand up for what he loves most.Not only are the lives of his loved ones at risk, but also those of other New York residents.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jon Watts</director>
      <actor>Peter Parker - Tom Holland</actor>
      <actor>Adrian Toomes - Michael Keaton</actor>
      <actor>Tony Stark - Robert Downey Jr.</actor>
      <actor>May Parker - Marisa Tomei</actor>
      <actor>Happy Hogan - Jon Favreau</actor>
      <actor>Pepper Potts - Gwyneth Paltrow</actor>
      <actor>Michelle - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Aaron Davis - Donald Glover</actor>
      <actor>Ned - Jacob Batalon</actor>
      <actor>Liz - Laura Harrier</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506145000 +0500" stop="20260506151500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Running</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tim Kirkby</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506151500 +0500" stop="20260506154500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">D.C</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tim Kirkby</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506154500 +0500" stop="20260506170000 +0500">
    <title>Living Large</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12-year-old Ben sings in a rock band and loves cooking.A real revolution comes in the boy's life when he decides to lose excess weight.Unfortunately, maintaining discipline is not easy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kristina Dufková</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506170000 +0500" stop="20260506184500 +0500">
    <title>Summer School, 2001</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kien returns to Cheb in the Czech Republic, where his relatives run a stall at the market.His appearance changes the family's life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Duzan Duong</director>
      <actor>Kien - Duong Bui</actor>
      <actor>Nudista - Pablo Maldonado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506184500 +0500" stop="20260506203000 +0500">
    <title>Wolfgang (extraordinari)</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the sudden death of his mother, nine-year-old Wolfgang (Jordi Catalán), an exceptionally gifted boy with features on the autism spectrum, is forced to live with his father, Carles (Miki Esparbé), whom he has never met before.An orderly nine-year-old who strives for perfection cannot stand his father's chaotic lifestyle.He wants to escape to Paris to study at the Grimald Academy and become the best pianist in the world.When Carles discovers his plan, he must make the most important decision in his life: follow his dream of an acting career or sacrifice his plans and become the father Wolfgang really needs.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Ruiz Caldera</director>
      <actor>Carlos - Miki Esparbé</actor>
      <actor>Matilde - Angels Gonyalons</actor>
      <actor>Paco - Berto Romero</actor>
      <actor>Mia - Anna Castillo</actor>
      <actor>Ingrid - Nausicaa Bonnín</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Ruth Llopis</actor>
      <actor>Juana - Montse Alcoverro</actor>
      <actor>Director Serie - Dafnis Balduz</actor>
      <actor>Directora de Casting - Reichel Delgado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506203000 +0500" stop="20260506223000 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: Eclipse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After a painful separation, Bella and her lover can enjoy each other's company again.The teenager wants to be transformed into an immortal being, which will allow them to be united forever.Before that, however, he has to take care of more mundane matters - pass his high school leaving exams and get into college.In addition, he is worried about his friend Jacob.It turns out that soon he and Edward will have to join forces to ensure the safety of the girl who has won their hearts.The relative peace of all the bloodsuckers and werewolves of Forks is disturbed by disturbing news from Seattle.It turns out that mysterious murders are taking place there.People are being killed by a pack of vampires, spreading fear and destruction around.The gang is recruiting new members.It is headed by Riley.He was chosen as the leader by the vengeful Victoria, who is seeking Bella's life.Thanks to Alice's visions and the Cullens' vigilance, they manage to protect her.Enemy races unite in the face of danger.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Slade</director>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Victoria - Bryce Dallas Howard</actor>
      <actor>Riley - Xavier Samuel</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Carlisle Cullen - Peter Facinelli</actor>
      <actor>Jessica Stanley - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Mike - Michael Welch</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506223000 +0500" stop="20260506232500 +0500">
    <title>The Tourist</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">In the dew of Lethe's flood</sub-title>
    <desc>A man (Jamie Dornan) traveling through the wilderness has an accident.His car is rammed by a tanker and he barely escapes with his life.When he wakes up injured in the hospital, he doesn't remember anything.He doesn't know what happened or who he is.He tries to use all the meetings with people and the clues he receives to discover his identity and past.He must do this before his enemies find him.A suspenseful, full of mysteries story of a man who faces amnesia and a dark past.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Sweeney</director>
      <actor>The Man - Jamie Dornan</actor>
      <actor>Helen Chambers - Danielle Macdonald</actor>
      <actor>Luci - Shalom Brune-Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Ólafur Darri Ólafsson</actor>
      <actor>Ralph - Danny Adcock</actor>
      <actor>Detective Inspector Lachlan Rogers - Damon Herriman</actor>
      <actor>Sergeant Rodney Lammon - Kamil Ellis</actor>
      <actor>Marko - Damien Strouthos</actor>
      <actor>Ethan Krum - Greg Larsen</actor>
      <actor>Lena Pascal - Victoria Haralabidou</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506232500 +0500" stop="20260507002000 +0500">
    <title>The Tourist</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Waiting for the Sun</sub-title>
    <desc>A man (Jamie Dornan) traveling through the wilderness has an accident.His car is rammed by a tanker and he barely escapes with his life.When he wakes up injured in the hospital, he doesn't remember anything.He doesn't know what happened or who he is.He tries to use all the meetings with people and the clues he receives to discover his identity and past.He must do this before his enemies find him.A suspenseful, full of mysteries story of a man who faces amnesia and a dark past.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Sweeney</director>
      <actor>The Man - Jamie Dornan</actor>
      <actor>Helen Chambers - Danielle Macdonald</actor>
      <actor>Luci - Shalom Brune-Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Ólafur Darri Ólafsson</actor>
      <actor>Ralph - Danny Adcock</actor>
      <actor>Detective Inspector Lachlan Rogers - Damon Herriman</actor>
      <actor>Sergeant Rodney Lammon - Kamil Ellis</actor>
      <actor>Marko - Damien Strouthos</actor>
      <actor>Ethan Krum - Greg Larsen</actor>
      <actor>Lena Pascal - Victoria Haralabidou</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>