<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422030000 +0500" stop="20260422042500 +0500">
    <title>Hell of a Summer</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>24-year-old Jason Hochberg, together with his co-workers, is supposed to take care of the youth camp participants.A serial killer appears in the area.Other staff members become the psychopath's target.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Billy Bryk</director>
      <director>Finn Wolfhard</director>
      <actor>John - Adam Pally</actor>
      <actor>Kathy - Rosebud Baker</actor>
      <actor>Jason Hochberg - Fred Hechinger</actor>
      <actor>Maggie Hochberg - Susan Coyne</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Billy Bryk</actor>
      <actor>Chris - Finn Wolfhard</actor>
      <actor>Mike - D'Pharaoh Woon-A-Tai</actor>
      <actor>Claire - Abby Quinn</actor>
      <actor>Shannon - Krista Nazaire</actor>
      <actor>Ezra - Matthew Finlan</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422042500 +0500" stop="20260422070500 +0500">
    <title>Blade Runner 2049</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The future, a world dominated by machines created to perform various dangerous tasks.Hunter Rick Deckard was tasked with tracking down and then eliminating the androids from Los Angeles three decades ago.Now the roles are reversed and he is the one who has to hide.At the same time, a new blade runner enters the game.Officer K from a special police unit tracks down humanoid robots hiding in society.When he returns home, his computer-generated companion, Joi, is always waiting for him.During the next task, the investigator comes across a shocking discovery proving that replicators can reproduce, which was previously considered impossible.Officer K's superior, Lieutenant Joshi, fears that the discovery will shock society and lead to war.So he orders the matter to be hushed up.Intrigued, K begins a private investigation.The help of the experienced Deckard turns out to be indispensable.Finding it is a difficult task in itself.Moreover, his enemies are hot on his heels.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>'K' - Ryan Gosling</actor>
      <actor>Rick Deckard - Harrison Ford</actor>
      <actor>Joi - Ana de Armas</actor>
      <actor>Luv - Sylvia Hoeks</actor>
      <actor>Lieutenant Joshi - Robin Wright</actor>
      <actor>Sapper Morton - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Interviewer - Mark Arnold</actor>
      <actor>Angry Old Lady - Vilma Szécsi</actor>
      <actor>Nandez - Wood Harris</actor>
      <actor>Coco - David Dastmalchian</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422070500 +0500" stop="20260422090000 +0500">
    <title>Towards the sun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2057. People are increasingly concerned about what is happening to the Sun.It seems to be losing power, and the Earth dependent on it is gradually becoming covered with ice.Scientists are sending an expedition towards the Sun whose task is to place a powerful nuclear charge on its surface.Experts predict that such an explosion will stimulate the star's activity and thus save the world from destruction.After some time, however, it turns out that a similar mission had already taken place seven years earlier, but then none of the crew managed to return to Earth.This time, eight people are sent into space, commanded by the experienced Captain Kaneda.The Icarus II board includes, among others:Cassie, Capa, Corazon and Mace.It quickly turns out that someone is making every effort to prevent the expedition members from reaching their goal.Soon, one of the pilots makes a fatal mistake and deprives the crew of oxygen supplies.In addition, unexpectedly, the ship begins to receive warning signals from its predecessor.The situation is becoming more and more dramatic.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Danny Boyle</director>
      <actor>Kaneda - Hiroyuki Sanada</actor>
      <actor>Cassie - Rose Byrne</actor>
      <actor>Corazon - Michelle Yeoh</actor>
      <actor>Mace - Chris Evans</actor>
      <actor>Capa - Cillian Murphy</actor>
      <actor>Searle - Cliff Curtis</actor>
      <actor>Harvey - Troy Garity</actor>
      <actor>Pinbacker - Mark Strong</actor>
      <actor>Trey - Benedict Wong</actor>
      <actor>Icarus - Chipo Chung</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422090000 +0500" stop="20260422104500 +0500">
    <title>The Huntsman: Winter's War</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Many years before Snow White's birth, Queen Ravenna (Charlize Theron) observes the actions of her sister, Freya (Emily Blunt), who is in love with a man named Andrew.Soon their daughter is born.Shortly thereafter, the child is murdered.At the same time, Freya discovers that she has the power to control ice.The woman leaves Ravenna's lands with a broken heart.He creates his own kingdom and an army of deadly hunters.There is only one rule in their ranks: never to love.It is broken by two warriors - Eric (Chris Hemsworth) and Sara (Jessica Chastain).Freya decides to separate them.Seven years later, after Ravenna's death, Snow White decides to get rid of the evil queen's mirror, moving it to the sanctuary.Some time later, William informs Eric that the soldiers who were responsible for the expedition have gone missing.The hunter suspects Freya - the mirror could significantly increase her power.He agrees to complete the mission, with the help of the dwarves.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Cedric Nicolas-Troyan</director>
      <actor>The Huntsman - Chris Hemsworth</actor>
      <actor>Ravenna - Charlize Theron</actor>
      <actor>Sara - Jessica Chastain</actor>
      <actor>Queen Freya - Emily Blunt</actor>
      <actor>Nion - Nick Frost</actor>
      <actor>Gryff - Rob Brydon</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Bromwyn - Sheridan Smith</actor>
      <actor>Doreena - Alexandra Roach</actor>
      <actor>Tull - Sope Dirisu</actor>
      <actor>Leifr - Sam Hazeldine</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422104500 +0500" stop="20260422122000 +0500">
    <title>Detective Monk: One last thing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brilliant detective Adrian Monk (Tony Shalhoub) is going through difficult times.The contract to publish his autobiography was canceled, and the coronavirus pandemic intensified his fears and phobias.All this makes the master of deduction start thinking about ending his life and joining his beloved Truda.He is jolted out of his torpor by the tragedy that befalls his stepdaughter Molly (Caitlin McGee).The girl is getting ready to marry journalist Griffin Briggs (Austin Scott).However, her fiancé dies while bungee jumping.Molly is convinced that it was not an accident, but a carefully planned murder.The trail leads to the influential billionaire Rick Eden (James Purefoy).Retired Captain Stottlemeyer (Ted Levine) now works for the rich man as his security chief.Monk is assisted in the investigation by former assistant and now real estate agent Natalie Teeger (Traylor Howard) and Randy Disher (Jason Gray-Stanford), now the New Jersey police commissioner.Continuation of the cult series.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Randy Zisk</director>
      <actor>Adrian Monk - Tony Shalhoub</actor>
      <actor>Natalie Teeger - Traylor Howard</actor>
      <actor>Randy Disher - Jason Gray-Stanford</actor>
      <actor>Trudy Monk - Melora Hardin</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Neven Bell - Hector Elizondo</actor>
      <actor>Stottlemeyer - Ted Levine</actor>
      <actor>Rick Eden - James Purefoy</actor>
      <actor>Molly Evans - Caitlin McGee</actor>
      <actor>Griffin Briggs - Austin Scott</actor>
      <actor>Skyler - Emma Ishta</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422122000 +0500" stop="20260422141500 +0500">
    <title>Hitch</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alex Hitchens experienced heartbreak years ago.He decided that he would never fall in love again, but at the same time he decided to serve other men and share with them his knowledge about women's nature.Since then, he has been involved in a rather unusual profession - advising on how to seduce girls.He prides himself on the fact that he can turn every client into a reliable, self-confident pickup artist.Makes every effort to maintain anonymity.Despite this, he easily obtains subsequent lucrative orders.Hitchens' new client is a humble accountant named Albert, who has fallen in love with the beautiful heiress of a fortune, Allegra Cole.She feels that she has no chance because of her overweight and shyness.Alex meets journalist Sara, who is supposed to interview Allegra.He falls in love with her at first sight.It turns out that in this case his methods fail.As he gradually gains Sara's affection, she discovers his shameful secret...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Andy Tennant</director>
      <actor>Alex Hitch Hitchens - Will Smith</actor>
      <actor>Albert - Kevin James</actor>
      <actor>Allegra Cole - Amber Valletta</actor>
      <actor>Sara - Eva Mendes</actor>
      <actor>Casey - Julie Ann Emery</actor>
      <actor>Cressida - Robinne Lee</actor>
      <actor>Geoff - Nathan Lee Graham</actor>
      <actor>Max - Adam Arkin</actor>
      <actor>Ben - Michael Rapaport</actor>
      <actor>Vance - Jeffrey Donovan</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422141500 +0500" stop="20260422154500 +0500">
    <title>Trolls</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Trolls are cheerful, singing and fabulously colorful creatures that live in a colorful forest.None of them have any idea what the world around them is like.Poppy displays their positive attitude the most.Her carefreeness and joy is shared by everyone, except Mruk.The troll believes that his brethren are in danger.These words come true when the village of nice creatures is found by their greatest enemies, the Bergens.All of Poppy's friends are kidnapped and she must set out to rescue them.She is accompanied by Mruk, who is reluctant to leave his house.In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others: Magdalena Wasylik, Piotr Bajtlik, Ewa Konstancja Bułhak and Bartosz Obuchowicz.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Mitchell</director>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422154500 +0500" stop="20260422171000 +0500">
    <title>Trolls World Tour</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Poppy lives a peaceful life in her colorful and singing kingdom.One day he learns that beyond his borders there are other lands inhabited by trolls.Each of them has different rhythms.Just as she loves pop, the creatures inhabiting distant lands prefer rock, funk, techno, country and classical music.The curious queen, together with Mruk and other friends, sets off on a journey to meet and unite her kin.She will have to face the rebellious Barb, who wants to ensure that only rock rules in all lands.The continuation of the 2016 hit sticks to a proven recipe for success - a joyful, extremely colorful animation packed with great hits, showing the unifying power of music and the need for tolerance.The pandemic made the film go down in cinema history as the first high-budget production that went straight to VOD services, without a cinema premiere.In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others:Magdalena Wasylik (Poppy), Piotr Bajtlik (Mruk) and Monika Węgiel-Jarocińska (Barb).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Walt Dohrn</director>
      <director>David P. Smith</director>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422171000 +0500" stop="20260422174000 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">RussFest</sub-title>
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Ross</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422174000 +0500" stop="20260422193000 +0500">
    <title>Esperando a Dalí</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Barcelona, ​​1974, a period of intense opposition to Franco's dictatorship.Brothers Fernando (Ivan Massagué), a chef, and Alberto (Pol López), an activist, must hide from the authorities.They find shelter in Cadaqués, a picturesque seaside village that is also the home of the famous artist Salvador Dalí (Gal Soler).In this setting, the brothers meet Lola (Clara Ponsot), who helps them find work.Fernando, influenced by Dalí's works and his infatuation with women, finds a passion for creating unique dishes.The man's ambitions grow, especially when Jules (José Garcia), Lola's eccentric father, dreams of organizing a dinner for Dalí himself.Despite the difficulties, Fernando creates a culinary masterpiece that inspires a revolution in the world of taste, which leads to the creation of the famous Surreal restaurant.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Pujol</director>
      <actor>Jules - José Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Fernando - Ivan Massagué</actor>
      <actor>Lola - Clara Ponsot</actor>
      <actor>Alberto - Pol López</actor>
      <actor>François - Nicolas Cazalé</actor>
      <actor>Luis - Alberto Lozano</actor>
      <actor>Lesya - Varvara Borodina</actor>
      <actor>Tonet - Francesc Ferrer</actor>
      <actor>Gala - Vicky Pena</actor>
      <actor>Teniente Garrido - Paco Tous</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422193000 +0500" stop="20260422205500 +0500">
    <title>The Pirates! Band of Misfits</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A certain inept captain of a pirate ship firmly believes that he will soon become the terror of the seas and oceans.Unfortunately, for now, these ambitious plans have no chance of being implemented, and his subsequent crazy ideas end in failure.The buccaneer, who wants to prove his bravery at all costs, intends to defeat his greatest enemies - Black Bellamy and Cutlass Liz - in the competition for the title of Pirate of the Year.His faithful, although slightly crazy crew will help him achieve his goal.The captain and his companions face quite a challenge.What stands in their way is, among others:young Charles Darwin and the privateers of the cruel Queen Victoria.An adventurous family film directed by Peter Lord, who received his third Oscar nomination for this picture.The plot of the film was taken from a series of books by Gideon Defoe.In the Polish language version, the voices of the characters were provided by, among others:Waldemar Barwiński, Grzegorz Kwiecień, Karol Wróblewski and Izabella Bukowska.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Lord</director>
      <director>Jeff Newitt</director>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422205500 +0500" stop="20260422223000 +0500">
    <title>The Best Christmas Pageant Ever</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Herdman clan has a bad reputation in the town.Unruly siblings steal and bully their peers.Wherever he appears, he causes chaos and goes completely unpunished.Meanwhile, the residents, under the direction of the newly elected organizer, Grace (Judy Greer), are preparing for the annual Christmas nativity play.To everyone's surprise, Gladys Herdman (Kynlee Heiman) and her relatives want to appear in the show.Grace casts a girl as Mary, which complicates preparations for the play and causes widespread dissatisfaction.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Dallas Jenkins</director>
      <actor>Grace - Judy Greer</actor>
      <actor>Self - Narrator - Lauren Graham</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Grady - Elizabeth Tabish</actor>
      <actor>Reverend Hopkins - Kirk B.R. Woller</actor>
      <actor>First-grade teacher - Vanessa Benavente</actor>
      <actor>Bob - Pete Holmes</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Thomas - Stephanie Sy</actor>
      <actor>Gladys Herdman - Kynlee Heiman</actor>
      <actor>Imogene Herdman - Beatrice Schneider</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Molly Belle Wright</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422223000 +0500" stop="20260422232500 +0500">
    <title>Tokyo Vice 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The War at Home</sub-title>
    <desc>Tokyo, 1990s.Young journalist Jake Adelstein (Ansel Elgort) must face the consequences of his actions.After he was beaten by Yakuza men, he felt that he was not untouchable.However, although he realizes that he cannot count on help from law enforcement officers or the media, and that his life and that of his loved ones are in danger, he does not intend to give up.He wants to continue investigating police corruption.The only one who helps him is his mentor and friend, former detective Hiroto Katagiri (Ken Watanabe).Perhaps, however, the journalist will also be able to count on the cooperation of Shoko Nagata (Miki Maya), a detective - like him - determined to destroy the Yakuza.The second series of an excellent series based on the reports of journalist Jake Anderson.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Eva Sorhaug</director>
      <actor>Taro - Koshi Uehara</actor>
      <actor>Masahito Ohno - Takayuki Suzuki</actor>
      <actor>Paul Luthold - Jonathan Whittaker</actor>
      <actor>Jason Oki - Aoi Takeya</actor>
      <actor>Airport Patron - Jim Chad</actor>
      <actor>American Embassy Guest - David Atkinson</actor>
      <actor>Ruri - Yukina Tsuchiya</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #2 - Paula Berwanger</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #1 - Ruby Young</actor>
      <actor>FBI Agent - Steve Wiley</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260422232500 +0500" stop="20260423002000 +0500">
    <title>Tokyo Vice 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Noble Path</sub-title>
    <desc>Tokyo, 1990s.Young journalist Jake Adelstein (Ansel Elgort) must face the consequences of his actions.After he was beaten by Yakuza men, he felt that he was not untouchable.However, although he realizes that he cannot count on help from law enforcement officers or the media, and that his life and that of his loved ones are in danger, he does not intend to give up.He wants to continue investigating police corruption.The only one who helps him is his mentor and friend, former detective Hiroto Katagiri (Ken Watanabe).Perhaps, however, the journalist will also be able to count on the cooperation of Shoko Nagata (Miki Maya), a detective - like him - determined to destroy the Yakuza.The second series of an excellent series based on the reports of journalist Jake Anderson.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Eva Sorhaug</director>
      <actor>Taro - Koshi Uehara</actor>
      <actor>Masahito Ohno - Takayuki Suzuki</actor>
      <actor>Paul Luthold - Jonathan Whittaker</actor>
      <actor>Jason Oki - Aoi Takeya</actor>
      <actor>Airport Patron - Jim Chad</actor>
      <actor>American Embassy Guest - David Atkinson</actor>
      <actor>Ruri - Yukina Tsuchiya</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #2 - Paula Berwanger</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #1 - Ruby Young</actor>
      <actor>FBI Agent - Steve Wiley</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423002000 +0500" stop="20260423014500 +0500">
    <title>Queen Of Bones</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1930s.Teenage twins Lillian (Julia Butters) and Samuel (Jacob Tremblay) live in rural Oregon.They are half-orphans because their mother died during childbirth.The father, religious fanatic Malcolm (Martin Freeman), treats his children harshly.Ida (Taylor Schilling), who may become the teenagers' stepmother in the future, also shows no sympathy for them.Meanwhile, one day, Lillian and Samuel find a book of pagan spells in their mother's trunk.They come to the conclusion that using them will help them free themselves from the influence of adults and gain power not only over their lives, but also their surroundings.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Budreau</director>
      <actor>Lily - Julia Butters</actor>
      <actor>Sam - Jacob Tremblay</actor>
      <actor>Malcolm - Martin Freeman</actor>
      <actor>Ida May - Taylor Schilling</actor>
      <actor>Fredrik P Jensen - Christopher Heyerdahl</actor>
      <actor>Agnis - Clare Coulter</actor>
      <actor>Arvin - Kyle Breitkopf</actor>
      <actor>Studs - Will Coombs</actor>
      <actor>The Priest - Martin Julien</actor>
      <actor>Henry - Adam Moryto</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423014500 +0500" stop="20260423032000 +0500">
    <title>Clerks 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After Randal and Dante's store catches fire, the friends must find another job.They still cannot come to terms with the loss of the premises, but they have no money to rebuild it.They get a job in a fast food restaurant.Soon, Dante decides to leave with his fiancée to another state.Things get complicated when it turns out that the manager of the place is pregnant.Meanwhile, Dante's bachelor party is approaching.Randall plans to organize a party whose main attraction will be a stripper.However, an unfortunate mistake occurs and things get out of control.Sequel to Kevin Smith's debut film.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kevin Smith</director>
      <actor>Dante - Brian O'Halloran</actor>
      <actor>Randal - Jeff Anderson</actor>
      <actor>Becky - Rosario Dawson</actor>
      <actor>Jay - Jason Mewes</actor>
      <actor>Gawking Guy - Ben Affleck</actor>
      <actor>Lance Dowds - Jason Lee</actor>
      <actor>Silent Bob - Kevin Smith</actor>
      <actor>Teen #1 - Jake Richardson</actor>
      <actor>Teen #2 - Ethan Suplee</actor>
      <actor>Emma  - Jennifer Schwalbach Smith</actor>
    </credits><date>2006</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423032000 +0500" stop="20260423045500 +0500">
    <title>Sellers 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Randall (Jeff Anderson) has a heart attack.He goes to hospital.A sudden illness makes him take stock of his life.While looking for a new goal, he comes up with the idea of ​​making a film about the Quick Stop store.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kevin Smith</director>
      <actor>Dante - Brian O'Halloran</actor>
      <actor>Randal - Jeff Anderson</actor>
      <actor>Hot Goalie - Vincent Pereira</actor>
      <actor>Jay - Jason Mewes</actor>
      <actor>Silent Bob - Kevin Smith</actor>
      <actor>Hockey Player - Michael Zapcic</actor>
      <actor>Hockey Player - Bryan Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Hockey Player - Walter Flanagan</actor>
      <actor>Hockey Player - Ming Chen</actor>
      <actor>Hockey Player - Ernie O'Donnell</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423045500 +0500" stop="20260423063000 +0500">
    <title>Det andet offer</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A routine procedure in the hospital unexpectedly ends in a tragedy that destroys the professional and personal life of Alexandra's neurologist.The doctor faces guilt and the consequences of her mistakes.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zinnini Elkington</director>
      <actor>Alex - Özlem Saglanmak</actor>
      <actor>Camilla - Trine Dyrholm</actor>
      <actor>Aida - Iman Meskini</actor>
      <actor>Karl - Anders Matthesen</actor>
      <actor>Emilie - Mathilde Arcel</actor>
      <actor>Trine - Anne Sofie Wanstrup</actor>
      <actor>Oliver - Jacob Spang Olsen</actor>
      <actor>Ragnar - Anders Hove</actor>
      <actor>Anders - Morten Hee Andersen</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423063000 +0500" stop="20260423080500 +0500">
    <title>Walk Hard: The Dewey Cox Story</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rock star Dewey Cox (John C. Reilly) seems to have done it all.The musician sold millions of records, won the hearts of hundreds of women, and his friends included such giants as Elvis and members of The Beatles.The artist's life consists primarily of performances in front of the audience and crazy, alcohol-infused parties.Cox does not shy away from various types of stimulants, and he cannot stay in a relationship with one woman for long.However, the most important thing for him is music, thanks to which he turned from a simple boy from the province into one of the world's greatest rock icons.Twice nominated for the Golden Globe (Best Actor and Best Original Song), a crazy parody of films about famous musicians inspired by the biographies of such musical personalities as Johnny Cash and Roy Orbison.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Kasdan</director>
      <actor>Dewey Cox - John C. Reilly</actor>
      <actor>Pa Cox - Raymond J. Barry</actor>
      <actor>Ma Cox - Margo Martindale</actor>
      <actor>Edith - Kristen Wiig</actor>
      <actor>Sam - Tim Meadows</actor>
      <actor>Theo - Chris Parnell</actor>
      <actor>Dave - Matt Besser</actor>
      <actor>Schwartzberg - David Krumholtz</actor>
      <actor>Stage Manager - Nat Faxon</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Musical Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423080500 +0500" stop="20260423090000 +0500">
    <title>An Update on Our Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The filmmakers discuss the topic of vlogging by families.They tell the story of Myka and James Stauffer, who gave an adopted boy to an orphanage when he was diagnosed with autism.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Rachel Mason</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423090000 +0500" stop="20260423102000 +0500">
    <title>The Pirates! Band of Misfits</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A certain inept captain of a pirate ship firmly believes that he will soon become the terror of the seas and oceans.Unfortunately, for now, these ambitious plans have no chance of being implemented, and his subsequent crazy ideas end in failure.The buccaneer, who wants to prove his bravery at all costs, intends to defeat his greatest enemies - Black Bellamy and Cutlass Liz - in the competition for the title of Pirate of the Year.His faithful, although slightly crazy crew will help him achieve his goal.The captain and his companions face quite a challenge.What stands in their way is, among others:young Charles Darwin and the privateers of the cruel Queen Victoria.An adventurous family film directed by Peter Lord, who received his third Oscar nomination for this picture.The plot of the film was taken from a series of books by Gideon Defoe.In the Polish language version, the voices of the characters were provided by, among others:Waldemar Barwiński, Grzegorz Kwiecień, Karol Wróblewski and Izabella Bukowska.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Lord</director>
      <director>Jeff Newitt</director>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423102000 +0500" stop="20260423115500 +0500">
    <title>The Best Christmas Pageant Ever</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Herdman clan has a bad reputation in the town.Unruly siblings steal and bully their peers.Wherever he appears, he causes chaos and goes completely unpunished.Meanwhile, the residents, under the direction of the newly elected organizer, Grace (Judy Greer), are preparing for the annual Christmas nativity play.To everyone's surprise, Gladys Herdman (Kynlee Heiman) and her relatives want to appear in the show.Grace casts a girl as Mary, which complicates preparations for the play and causes widespread dissatisfaction.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Dallas Jenkins</director>
      <actor>Grace - Judy Greer</actor>
      <actor>Self - Narrator - Lauren Graham</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Grady - Elizabeth Tabish</actor>
      <actor>Reverend Hopkins - Kirk B.R. Woller</actor>
      <actor>First-grade teacher - Vanessa Benavente</actor>
      <actor>Bob - Pete Holmes</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Thomas - Stephanie Sy</actor>
      <actor>Gladys Herdman - Kynlee Heiman</actor>
      <actor>Imogene Herdman - Beatrice Schneider</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Molly Belle Wright</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423115500 +0500" stop="20260423131000 +0500">
    <title>Little Emma</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A little girl named Emma was raised by animals.Her life is full of warmth and joy, until one of her friends discovers the unpleasant truth that she was actually adopted and is not part of their family.Devastated, Emma sets out on a journey to find her loved ones.Along the way, he gathers an extraordinary team, including the clumsy inventor Żółwik Bystrzak, the ambitious scientist Edward Wilk and the brave Weasel Sancho.Together they are looking for a mysterious island which, according to legend, is inhabited by tiny people.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Leo Lewis</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423131000 +0500" stop="20260423145500 +0500">
    <title>Wolfgang (extraordinari)</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the sudden death of his mother, nine-year-old Wolfgang (Jordi Catalán), an exceptionally gifted boy with features on the autism spectrum, is forced to live with his father, Carles (Miki Esparbé), whom he has never met before.An orderly nine-year-old who strives for perfection cannot stand his father's chaotic lifestyle.He wants to escape to Paris to study at the Grimald Academy and become the best pianist in the world.When Carles discovers his plan, he must make the most important decision in his life: follow his dream of an acting career or sacrifice his plans and become the father Wolfgang really needs.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Ruiz Caldera</director>
      <actor>Carlos - Miki Esparbé</actor>
      <actor>Matilde - Angels Gonyalons</actor>
      <actor>Paco - Berto Romero</actor>
      <actor>Mia - Anna Castillo</actor>
      <actor>Ingrid - Nausicaa Bonnín</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Ruth Llopis</actor>
      <actor>Juana - Montse Alcoverro</actor>
      <actor>Director Serie - Dafnis Balduz</actor>
      <actor>Directora de Casting - Reichel Delgado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423145500 +0500" stop="20260423162000 +0500">
    <title>The Addams Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Gomez and Morticia Addams are looking for a safe place to live and raise their children.Therefore, they move to a dark, abandoned mansion in New Jersey.The estate is surrounded by swamps and hidden on top of a mountain amidst thick fog.13 years have passed.Gomez teaches the family's traditional saber fighting to Pugslay's son.Meanwhile, Morticia must face daughter Wednesday's questions about life outside the mansion gates.Soon, TV star Margaux Needler appears in the area and starts building a modern housing estate.Her plans are hindered by the fact that the Addams residence does not fit the modernist vision of the theme park.The woman decides to get rid of the strange family.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Conrad Vernon</director>
      <director>Greg Tiernan</director>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423162000 +0500" stop="20260423171000 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Exit Event</sub-title>
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Alec Berg</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423171000 +0500" stop="20260423190000 +0500">
    <title>Completement cramé</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A widowed, wealthy Englishman, Andrew Blake (John Malkovich), goes to France, the homeland of his beloved wife.When he arrives at the stately mansion with a suitcase, to his surprise he is not mistaken for a guest, but a candidate for a butler.To stay as long as possible in the place where he met the love of his life years ago, he accepts a job offer and does not reveal the real destination of his trip to anyone.He meets the owner of the historic mansion, the widow Nathalie Beauvillier (Fanny Ardant), the housekeeper and cook Odile (Émilie Dequenne), the maid Manon (Eugénie Anselin) and the estate manager Philippe.Over time, he becomes friends with the residents and helps them look at their lives from a different perspective.Thanks to this, he also finds his lost joy and motivation to act.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gilles Legardinier</director>
      <actor>Andrew Blake - John Malkovich</actor>
      <actor>Nathalie Beauvillier - Fanny Ardant</actor>
      <actor>Odile - Émilie Dequenne</actor>
      <actor>Magnier - Philippe Bas</actor>
      <actor>Manon - Eugenie Anselin</actor>
      <actor>Mme Berliner - Christel Henon</actor>
      <actor>Passer-by - Daniel Kovacs</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423190000 +0500" stop="20260423204500 +0500">
    <title>Tempete</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Zoe (Carmen Kassovitz) grew up surrounded by horses in her parents' (Mélanie Laurent and Pio Marmai) racing stable.This is her place on earth.He dreams of one day becoming a jockey like his father.When a new foal is born, the girl is the first to notice its potential to become a champion.The family's life changes one tragic night, when a scared mare accidentally injures Zoe.The teenager, overcome with despair, completely breaks down.Thanks to the support of her parents and the help of the stable boy (Kacey Mottet Klein), who has an extraordinary gift for communicating with horses, Zoe decides to overcome adversity and regain what seemed lost.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christian Duguay</director>
      <actor>Marie - Mélanie Laurent</actor>
      <actor>Philippe - Pio Marmai</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Carmen Kassovitz</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Charlie Paulet</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - June Benard</actor>
      <actor>Monsieur Cooper - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Madame Cooper - Carole Bouquet</actor>
      <actor>Sébastien - Kacey Mottet Klein</actor>
      <actor>Haddid - Atmen Kelif</actor>
      <actor>Éric - Antoine Cholet</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423204500 +0500" stop="20260423223000 +0500">
    <title>You're Cordially Invited</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A booking error causes two weddings to take place in one place at the same time.Both families face the challenge of having to share space.However, they have no intention of letting anything stop them from organizing a special ceremony for their loved one.Jim (Will Ferrell), the father of Jenni (Geraldine Viswanathan), who is getting ready to marry, and Margot (Reese Witherspoon), sister of the second bride, Neve (Meredith Hagner), try to keep their cool in a difficult situation, but they are still fighting a desperate duel.A comedy directed by Nicholas Stoller, the creator of "Neighbors".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Jim - Will Ferrell</actor>
      <actor>Margot - Reese Witherspoon</actor>
      <actor>Jenni - Geraldine Viswanathan</actor>
      <actor>Neve - Meredith Hagner</actor>
      <actor>Dixon - Jimmy Tatro</actor>
      <actor>Oliver - Stony Blyden</actor>
      <actor>Gwyneth - Leanne Morgan</actor>
      <actor>Colton - Rory Scovel</actor>
      <actor>Heather - Keyla Monterroso Mejia</actor>
      <actor>Kelly - Ramona Young</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423223000 +0500" stop="20260423235500 +0500">
    <title>Infinitely Polar Bear</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1970s, Boston.Cam Stuart (Mark Ruffalo) suffers from bipolar disorder.Due to his illness, he had to be hospitalized and lost his job.One day, his wife, nurse Maggie (Zoe Saldana), accepts a scholarship to New York University.The MBA degree obtained there will help her find a well-paid job, thanks to which she will provide for her family and take care of her children's education.While staying in another city, her husband has to take care of his daughters - adolescent Amelia (Imogene Wolodarsky) and Faith (Ashley Aufderheide).He faces an exceptionally difficult task.Girls are often embarrassed by the behavior of their father, who keeps coming up with various unusual ideas.However, they help him face everyday challenges.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Maya Forbes</director>
      <actor>Cam Stuart - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Maggie Stuart - Zoe Saldana</actor>
      <actor>Faith Stuart - Ashley Aufderheide</actor>
      <actor>Pauline Stuart - Beth Dixon</actor>
      <actor>Amelia Stuart - Imogene Wolodarsky</actor>
      <actor>Kim - Nekhebet Kum Juch</actor>
      <actor>Thurgood - Manoah Angelo</actor>
      <actor>Gaga - Muriel Gould</actor>
      <actor>Ruth-Ann - Tod Randolph</actor>
      <actor>Murray Stuart - Keir Dullea</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260423235500 +0500" stop="20260424014500 +0500">
    <title>Ghostlight</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Grieving construction worker Dan (Keith Kupferer) joins a local theater group working on a production of Romeo and Juliet.There are changes in his life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kelly O'Sullivan</director>
      <director>Alex Thompson</director>
      <actor>Dan - Keith Kupferer</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Tara Mallen</actor>
      <actor>Rita - Dolly De Leon</actor>
      <actor>Lanora - Hanna Dworkin</actor>
      <actor>Daisy - Katherine Kupferer</actor>
      <actor>Greg - Dexter Zollicoffer</actor>
      <actor>Jonah - H.B. Ward</actor>
      <actor>Lucian - Tommy Rivera-Vega</actor>
      <actor>Moira - Alma Washington</actor>
      <actor>Mikey - Matthew C. Yee</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>