<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502025500 +0500" stop="20260502052000 +0500">
    <title>Gone Girl</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>On the day of his fifth wedding anniversary with Amy (Rosamund Pike), Nick Dunne (Ben Affleck) reports to the police that his wife has disappeared in mysterious circumstances.The case of her disappearance quickly reaches the media.Detective Rhonda Boney (Kim Dickens) leading the investigation discovers numerous inconsistencies in the man's testimony.There are speculations that Nick may have had something to do with Amy's mysterious disappearance.Supported by his twin sister, Margo (Carrie Coon), the man desperately tries to prove his innocence.Over time, new facts come to light which show that the Dunnes' marriage was a toxic relationship.The film by the creator of the cult thriller "Seven", David Fincher, was nominated, among others,to the Golden Globe.For her role as Amy, Rosamund Pike received nominations for an Oscar, a Golden Globe and other awards.The film's script, also nominated for a Golden Globe, was based on the best-selling novel by Gillian Flynn.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Fincher</director>
      <actor>Nick Dunne - Ben Affleck</actor>
      <actor>Amy Dunne - Rosamund Pike</actor>
      <actor>Desi Collings - Neil Patrick Harris</actor>
      <actor>Tanner Bolt - Tyler Perry</actor>
      <actor>Margo Dunne - Carrie Coon</actor>
      <actor>Detective Rhonda Boney - Kim Dickens</actor>
      <actor>Officer James Gilpin - Patrick Fugit</actor>
      <actor>Rand Elliott - David Clennon</actor>
      <actor>Marybeth Elliott - Lisa Banes</actor>
      <actor>Ellen Abbott - Missi Pyle</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502052000 +0500" stop="20260502072500 +0500">
    <title>The Outrun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A young woman named Rona (Saoirse Ronan), who has recently left an addiction treatment center, returns from London to her native Scotland, to one of the islands of the Orkney archipelago.Because her parents are separated, she lives alternately with her mother, where she meets with her religious friends, and with her father, whom she helps on the farm.At the same time, she is still trying to cope with difficult memories - the beginning of her stay in London, where she started studying biology and often went to clubs with her boyfriend Daynin (Paapa Essiedu).She didn't even notice when she fell into alcoholism, which led to problems in her relationship and began to destroy her life.Meanwhile, while staying on the island, Rona decides to return to London.However, already on the ferry he feels that he is unable to control the urge to drink alcohol.He must re-plan his life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nora Fingscheidt</director>
      <actor>Rona - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Young Rona - Freya Evans</actor>
      <actor>Daynin - Paapa Essiedu</actor>
      <actor>Barman James - Seamus Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Bouncer Dave - David Garrick</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Rasamalar - Aniya Sekkanu</actor>
      <actor>Andrew - Stephen Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Saskia Reeves</actor>
      <actor>Young Orcadian Man - Liam Smith</actor>
      <actor>Bible Group Evie - Eilidh Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502072500 +0500" stop="20260502090000 +0500">
    <title>Tripped Up</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lizzy (Leah Lewis) has always dreamed of becoming a chef.However, participating in a culinary reality show and later working in a New York restaurant became a source of frustration for her.A cooking enthusiast is one step away from giving up her greatest passion.The last chance to stay in the catering industry is to participate in a culinary festival.Together with her friends, Mary (Ashley Moore), Kai (Ariel Winter) and Taylor (Sasha Fox), she sets off on an adventure.If she fails, she is ready to look for another path in life.Unfortunately, the team has been plagued by bad luck since the beginning of the expedition.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Shruti Ganguly</director>
      <actor>Lizzy - Leah Lewis</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Ashley Moore</actor>
      <actor>Kai - Ariel Winter</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Sasha Fox</actor>
      <actor>Patty - Vanessa L. Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ashley - Jo Ellen Pellman</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Danny Kornfeld</actor>
      <actor>Jose - Gil Perez-Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Missy - Judy Gold</actor>
      <actor>Lotus - Justin Guarini</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502090000 +0500" stop="20260502104500 +0500">
    <title>The Munsters</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Transylvania.Dr. Henry Augustus Wolfgang (Richard Brake) and his not very bright assistant Floop (Jorge Garcia) want to create a perfect man from the dead bodies of geniuses of the past century.By mistake, instead of the brain of a great scientist, they implant the organ of his twin brother, a bad comedian, into the creature they created.This is how Herman Potwornicki (Jeff Daniel Phillips) is created.When Wolfgang decides to show it to the world on TV, he is devastated.However, the uncouth, joking giant attracts the attention of the unmarried and undead Lily (Sheri Moon), who is fed up with unsuccessful dates.The girl finds Herman and they quickly become a couple.The future son-in-law, although he gained fame and won Lily's heart, does not like her father, a vampire and a refined count (Daniel Roebuck).However, the lovers get married.Due to the intrigues of the count's cunning ex-wife, Zoya Krupp (Catherine Schell) and her assistant, the werewolf Lester (Tomas Boykin), they lose their palace and fortune.They decide to go to America, where Herman intends to conquer Hollywood.They start a new life in a ruined house in the suburbs.A colorful production referring to the series from the 1960s. Director Rob Zombie is his big fan.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rob Zombie</director>
      <actor>Herman - Jeff Daniel Phillips</actor>
      <actor>Lily - Sheri Moon Zombie</actor>
      <actor>The Count - Daniel Roebuck</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Wolfgang - Richard Brake</actor>
      <actor>Floop - Jorge Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Igor - Sylvester McCoy</actor>
      <actor>Zoya Krupp - Catherine Schell</actor>
      <actor>Barbara Carr - Cassandra Peterson</actor>
      <actor>Lester - Tomas Boykin</actor>
      <actor>Bela Krupp - Levente Törköly</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502104500 +0500" stop="20260502124000 +0500">
    <title>Red One</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The third joint film of Jake Kasdan and Dwayne Johnson, after two installments of the new version of "Jumanji".The head of North Pole security and a bounty hunter search for the missing Santa Claus.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Callum Drift - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Jack O'Malley - Chris Evans</actor>
      <actor>Zoe - Lucy Liu</actor>
      <actor>Nick - J.K. Simmons</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Claus - Bonnie Hunt</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502124000 +0500" stop="20260502141000 +0500">
    <title>The Book of Life</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two powerful magicians bet whether people are pure in heart.La Muerte is the ruler of the World of the Remembered.The dead stay there, remaining in the hearts of their loved ones.Xibalba rules the Land of the Forgotten - a sad place for souls that no one remembers.The magicians are tested by: fashion matador Manolo, who dreams of being a musician, and Joaquin - an athlete and the pride of the city.The boys compete for the affections of Maria, the daughter of the local mayor.However, the beautiful bride is resistant to their advances.Manolo and Joaquin will go on a wonderful journey, during which they will visit extraordinary lands, meet colorful characters and discover the truth about themselves.The project by Guillermo del Toro and Jorge R. Gutierrez was nominated for a Golden Globe in the category of best animated film.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jorge R. Gutiérrez</director>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502141000 +0500" stop="20260502161000 +0500">
    <title>Everest</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 1996. Rob Hall (Jason Clarke) organizes a commercial expedition to the highest mountain in the world.His brigade includes, among others:Texan Beck Weathers (Josh Brolin) and reporter Jon Krakauer (Michael Kelly).The mountaineers reach the base camp.Over the course of several weeks, they get used to extreme weather conditions and pressure that disregulates the body.Apart from them, other teams are heading to the summit.Hall makes a strategic decision to join Scott Fischer (Jake Gyllenhaal), the head of the Mountain Madness expedition.At the beginning of May, climbers leave the base camp.They struggle with snow storms, bitter cold and lack of oxygen.Extreme conditions put them at the edge of their mental and physical endurance.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Baltasar Kormákur</director>
      <actor>Rob Hall - Jason Clarke</actor>
      <actor>Scott Fischer - Jake Gyllenhaal</actor>
      <actor>Beck Weathers - Josh Brolin</actor>
      <actor>Ang Dorjee - Ang Phula Sherpa</actor>
      <actor>Michael Groom - Thomas M. Wright</actor>
      <actor>Andy 'Harold' Harris - Martin Henderson</actor>
      <actor>Neal Beidleman - Tom Goodman-Hill</actor>
      <actor>Lene Gammelgaard - Charlotte Boving</actor>
      <actor>Lopsang - Pemba Sherpa</actor>
      <actor>Charlotte Fox - Amy Shindler</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Disaster Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502161000 +0500" stop="20260502184500 +0500">
    <title>The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The hobbit Bilbo (Martin Freeman), Gandalf (Ian McKellen) and the dwarves led by Thorin (Richard Armitage) continue their dangerous journey.The goal of their expedition is to regain Erebor - the kingdom of the dwarves, which is currently occupied by the dragon Smaug (Benedict Cumberbatch).The travelers meet the bear warrior Beorn (Mikael Persbrandt), giant spiders inhabiting Mirkwood, the Wood Elves and their master, King Thranduil (Lee Pace), his son Legolas (Orlando Bloom), and the elf Tauriel (Evangeline Lilly).Thanks to an archer called Bard (Luke Evans), they get to Lake Town.When they reach the Lonely Mountain, they will come face to face with their greatest danger.The second part of the trilogy based on the novel by J.R.R.Tolkien.The film starred, among others: Ian McKellen ("Gods and Monsters"), Martin Freeman ("Fargo", "Sherlock") and Richard Armitage ("Versa", "Epicenter").The film, made on a grand scale, received three Oscar nominations, including for best special effects.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Thorin - Richard Armitage</actor>
      <actor>Gandalf - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Bilbo - Martin Freeman</actor>
      <actor>Balin - Ken Stott</actor>
      <actor>Dwalin - Graham McTavish</actor>
      <actor>Bifur - William Kircher</actor>
      <actor>Bofur - James Nesbitt</actor>
      <actor>Bombur - Stephen Hunter</actor>
      <actor>Fili - Dean O'Gorman</actor>
      <actor>Kili - Aidan Turner</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502184500 +0500" stop="20260502203000 +0500">
    <title>Tempete</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Zoe (Carmen Kassovitz) grew up surrounded by horses in her parents' (Mélanie Laurent and Pio Marmai) racing stable.This is her place on earth.He dreams of one day becoming a jockey like his father.When a new foal is born, the girl is the first to notice its potential to become a champion.The family's life changes one tragic night, when a scared mare accidentally injures Zoe.The teenager, overcome with despair, completely breaks down.Thanks to the support of her parents and the help of the stable boy (Kacey Mottet Klein), who has an extraordinary gift for communicating with horses, Zoe decides to overcome adversity and regain what seemed lost.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christian Duguay</director>
      <actor>Marie - Mélanie Laurent</actor>
      <actor>Philippe - Pio Marmai</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Carmen Kassovitz</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Charlie Paulet</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - June Benard</actor>
      <actor>Monsieur Cooper - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Madame Cooper - Carole Bouquet</actor>
      <actor>Sébastien - Kacey Mottet Klein</actor>
      <actor>Haddid - Atmen Kelif</actor>
      <actor>Éric - Antoine Cholet</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502203000 +0500" stop="20260502223000 +0500">
    <title>Alita: Battle Angel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alita (Rosa Salazar), a cyborg girl, wakes up from a coma.It turns out that he doesn't remember who he is or where he is.Doctor Ido (Christoph Waltz) subjected her to a series of tests that revealed that she was a young woman with a unique story.Wanting to protect her, he does not reveal the truth about her past.Alita must adapt to the conditions and rules of life in Scrap City.After some time, he regains his memory thanks to the help of his friend, Hugo (Keean Johnson).Then he realizes that he has incredible fighting skills.She must use them against the power that tries to control her.The film's director is Robert Rodriguez, known from "From Dusk Till Dawn" and "Machete".The script was written by the winner of three Oscars, James Cameron, who considered making "Alita" back in the 1990s. The film was based on the manga.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Rodriguez</director>
      <actor>Alita - Rosa Salazar</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Dyson Ido - Christoph Waltz</actor>
      <actor>Chiren - Jennifer Connelly</actor>
      <actor>Vector - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Zapan - Ed Skrein</actor>
      <actor>Grewishka - Jackie Earle Haley</actor>
      <actor>Hugo - Keean Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tanji - Jorge Lendeborg Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Koyomi - Lana Condor</actor>
      <actor>Nurse Gerhad - Idara Victor</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260502223000 +0500" stop="20260503003500 +0500">
    <title>Challengers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Tennis player Tashi Duncan (Zendaya) has had impressive success on the court in the past.Her career was ended by an injury.Today, the woman is the trainer of Art Donaldson (Mike Faist) - her partner and father of her daughter.The man is one title short of the Grand Slam, but he is struggling with injury and age, which may ruin the pair's ambitions.After a series of defeats, the player plans to take part in the Challenger tournament in New Rochelle, New York, which is to be his warm-up before the US Open and a chance to regain his form.Unexpectedly, in the finale, Art will have to face Patrick Zweig (Josh O'Connor) - his childhood friend and Tashi's ex-boyfriend.The match becomes an opportunity for all three to confront their turbulent past.The film by Italian director Luca Guadagnino, the creator of the Oscar-nominated "Those Days, Those Nights", is a combination of a sports drama and a story about a love triangle.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Luca Guadagnino</director>
      <actor>Tashi - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Patrick - Josh O'Connor</actor>
      <actor>Art - Mike Faist</actor>
      <actor>Finn Larsen - Jake Jensen</actor>
      <actor>Spectator - Faith Fay</actor>
      <actor>Lily - A.J. Lister</actor>
      <actor>US Open line Judge - Scottie DiGiacomo</actor>
      <actor>Tennis man - Sid Jarvis</actor>
      <actor>Tennis spectator - Charles Massey</actor>
      <actor>Asian Cook - Keanu Ham</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503003500 +0500" stop="20260503023500 +0500">
    <title>Future Diva</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A story about women with an unquenchable thirst for freedom who decide to work in the porn industry.Ilona is among them.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Riccardo Schicchi - Pietro Castellitto</actor>
      <actor>Debora Attanasio - Barbara Ronchi</actor>
      <actor>Moana Pozzi - Denise Capezza</actor>
      <actor>Eva Henger - Tesa Litvan</actor>
      <actor>Ilona Staller Cicciolina - Lidija Kordic</actor>
      <actor>Massimiliano Caroletti - Davide Iachini</actor>
      <actor>Valentino - Marco Iermano</actor>
      <actor>Marietto - Alfonso Postiglione</actor>
      <actor>Mamma Debora - Cinzia Mascoli</actor>
      <actor>Simone Pagani - Alessandro Moser</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503023500 +0500" stop="20260503033500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503033500 +0500" stop="20260503043000 +0500">
    <title>Heated Rivalry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two ice hockey players, Shane Hollander (Hudson Williams) and Ilya Rozanov (Connor Storrie), are united not only by ambition and the need for competition, but also by a magnetic attraction that neither of them fully understands.What begins as a secret romance between two debutants turns into an extraordinary love journey.Athletes spend eight years chasing fame on the ice while trying to deal with their feelings off it.They must decide whether there is room for something as fragile as love in a world of brutal competition.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Jacob Tierney</director>
      <actor>Shane Hollander - Hudson Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ilya Rozanov - Connor Storrie</actor>
      <actor>Scott Hunter - François Arnaud</actor>
      <actor>Yuna Hollander - Christina Chang</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Marleau - Franco Lo Presti</actor>
      <actor>Hayden Pike - Callan Potter</actor>
      <actor>Svetlana - Ksenia Daniela Kharlamova</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #2 - Shaun Starr</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #1 - Conor McKenna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503043000 +0500" stop="20260503050000 +0500">
    <title>Comeback 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Valerie Cherish, a once popular television actress, rose to fame as a sitcom star.After many years, he wants to return to the small screen at all costs.He decides to take part in a new reality show.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Patrick King</director>
      <actor>Valerie Cherish - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Jane Benson - Laura Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mark Berman - Damian Young</actor>
      <actor>Billy Stanton - Dan Bucatinsky</actor>
      <actor>Juna Millken - Malin Akerman</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503050000 +0500" stop="20260503065000 +0500">
    <title>Forgetting Sarah Marshall</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Los Angeles.Peter Bretter is a musician.His compositions can be heard in many television productions.However, the man's real dream is to stage a puppet musical about Count Dracula, who is looking for true love.He has been living in a happy relationship with actress Sarah Marshall for six years.Peter loves the girl completely and doesn't seem to notice her flaws.And Sarah has too many of them.As the star of a popular crime series, he makes himself felt by those around him with his selfishness, lack of respect for the feelings of others and the expectation of constant adoration.One day, Bretter is abandoned by his beloved.Devastated and hurt, he cannot regain his balance for many weeks.Finally, on the advice of his brother Brian, he decides to go on vacation to a resort in Hawaii.There he hopes to recover from unhappy love.Unfortunately, on arrival he is horrified to discover that Sarah and her new partner, rocker Aldous Snow, have rented a room in the same hotel.Meanwhile, a suffering Peter attracts the attention of attractive receptionist Rachel Jansen.The woman decides to help him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Peter Bretter - Jason Segel</actor>
      <actor>Sarah Marshall - Kristen Bell</actor>
      <actor>Rachel Jansen - Mila Kunis</actor>
      <actor>Aldous Snow - Russell Brand</actor>
      <actor>Brian Bretter - Bill Hader</actor>
      <actor>Liz Bretter - Liz Cackowski</actor>
      <actor>Wyoma - Maria Thayer</actor>
      <actor>Darald - Jack McBrayer</actor>
      <actor>Kemo - Taylor Wily</actor>
      <actor>Dwayne the Bartender - Davon McDonald</actor>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503065000 +0500" stop="20260503090000 +0500">
    <title>Challengers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Tennis player Tashi Duncan (Zendaya) has had impressive success on the court in the past.Her career was ended by an injury.Today, the woman is the trainer of Art Donaldson (Mike Faist) - her partner and father of her daughter.The man is one title short of the Grand Slam, but he is struggling with injury and age, which may ruin the pair's ambitions.After a series of defeats, the player plans to take part in the Challenger tournament in New Rochelle, New York, which is to be his warm-up before the US Open and a chance to regain his form.Unexpectedly, in the finale, Art will have to face Patrick Zweig (Josh O'Connor) - his childhood friend and Tashi's ex-boyfriend.The match becomes an opportunity for all three to confront their turbulent past.The film by Italian director Luca Guadagnino, the creator of the Oscar-nominated "Those Days, Those Nights", is a combination of a sports drama and a story about a love triangle.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Luca Guadagnino</director>
      <actor>Tashi - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Patrick - Josh O'Connor</actor>
      <actor>Art - Mike Faist</actor>
      <actor>Finn Larsen - Jake Jensen</actor>
      <actor>Spectator - Faith Fay</actor>
      <actor>Lily - A.J. Lister</actor>
      <actor>US Open line Judge - Scottie DiGiacomo</actor>
      <actor>Tennis man - Sid Jarvis</actor>
      <actor>Tennis spectator - Charles Massey</actor>
      <actor>Asian Cook - Keanu Ham</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503090000 +0500" stop="20260503104500 +0500">
    <title>Tempete</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Zoe (Carmen Kassovitz) grew up surrounded by horses in her parents' (Mélanie Laurent and Pio Marmai) racing stable.This is her place on earth.He dreams of one day becoming a jockey like his father.When a new foal is born, the girl is the first to notice its potential to become a champion.The family's life changes one tragic night, when a scared mare accidentally injures Zoe.The teenager, overcome with despair, completely breaks down.Thanks to the support of her parents and the help of the stable boy (Kacey Mottet Klein), who has an extraordinary gift for communicating with horses, Zoe decides to overcome adversity and regain what seemed lost.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christian Duguay</director>
      <actor>Marie - Mélanie Laurent</actor>
      <actor>Philippe - Pio Marmai</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Carmen Kassovitz</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Charlie Paulet</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - June Benard</actor>
      <actor>Monsieur Cooper - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Madame Cooper - Carole Bouquet</actor>
      <actor>Sébastien - Kacey Mottet Klein</actor>
      <actor>Haddid - Atmen Kelif</actor>
      <actor>Éric - Antoine Cholet</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503104500 +0500" stop="20260503124000 +0500">
    <title>Alita: Battle Angel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alita (Rosa Salazar), a cyborg girl, wakes up from a coma.It turns out that he doesn't remember who he is or where he is.Doctor Ido (Christoph Waltz) subjected her to a series of tests that revealed that she was a young woman with a unique story.Wanting to protect her, he does not reveal the truth about her past.Alita must adapt to the conditions and rules of life in Scrap City.After some time, he regains his memory thanks to the help of his friend, Hugo (Keean Johnson).Then he realizes that he has incredible fighting skills.She must use them against the power that tries to control her.The film's director is Robert Rodriguez, known from "From Dusk Till Dawn" and "Machete".The script was written by the winner of three Oscars, James Cameron, who considered making "Alita" back in the 1990s. The film was based on the manga.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Rodriguez</director>
      <actor>Alita - Rosa Salazar</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Dyson Ido - Christoph Waltz</actor>
      <actor>Chiren - Jennifer Connelly</actor>
      <actor>Vector - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Zapan - Ed Skrein</actor>
      <actor>Grewishka - Jackie Earle Haley</actor>
      <actor>Hugo - Keean Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tanji - Jorge Lendeborg Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Koyomi - Lana Condor</actor>
      <actor>Nurse Gerhad - Idara Victor</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503124000 +0500" stop="20260503140500 +0500">
    <title>The Emoji Movie</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Millions of smartphones around the world have an application for sending messages through which you can communicate your feelings and moods.This is where the city of Textopolis, where emotes live, is hidden.The task of each of them is to express a different state of mind.The exception is Minek, who can express every emotion.However, he dreams of being like others.Together with Piątek and the superhacker Matrix, they set off on a journey through the phone in search of a solution.The animated film is directed by Tony Leondis ("Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters").The Polish language version featured, among others: Paweł Ciołkosz, Szymon Roszak, Monika Pikuła and Katarzyna Kwiatkowska.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tony Leondis</director>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503140500 +0500" stop="20260503155000 +0500">
    <title>A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lloyd Vogel (Matthew Rhys) is in crisis.His marriage to Andrea (Susan Kelechi Watson) is not going well.His son was recently born and he can't quite cope with the role of a parent.His wife, in turn, completely lost patience with his moods.He is also stressed by his relationship with his father, Jerry (Chris Cooper).She cannot forgive him for abandoning his family in the past and leaving him alone with his sick mother.Things aren't going well at work either.An aspiring investigative journalist is given a task by his superior that is below his skills.He is to prepare a short article as part of a series about inspiring people.He comes to interview the nationally beloved children's show host, Fred Rogers (Tom Hanks).Without any enthusiasm, he meets America's favorite, who immediately surprises him with his cheerfulness.Suddenly, the roles in their relationship are reversed.While it was Lloyd who was supposed to question Rogers, it was Rogers who steered the conversation and got him to confess.A friendship develops between the men.Under the influence of meetings with Fred, Vogel rediscovers the joy of life and begins to believe that he can repair relationships with his loved ones and experience happiness.A film inspired by a true story.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Marielle Heller</director>
      <actor>Fred Rogers - Tom Hanks</actor>
      <actor>Lloyd Vogel - Matthew Rhys</actor>
      <actor>Jerry Vogel - Chris Cooper</actor>
      <actor>Andrea Vogel - Susan Kelechi Watson</actor>
      <actor>Joanne Rogers - Maryann Plunkett</actor>
      <actor>Bill Isler - Enrico Colantoni</actor>
      <actor>Dorothy - Wendy Makkena</actor>
      <actor>Lorraine - Tammy Blanchard</actor>
      <actor>Todd - Noah Harpster</actor>
      <actor>Margy - Carmen Cusack</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503155000 +0500" stop="20260503181000 +0500">
    <title>The Hobbit: The Battle of the Five Armies</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thorin Oakenshield, the hobbit Bilbo and their companions recover the treasure of Erebor, which was guarded by Smaug.The leader of a company of dwarves cannot resist wealth.He sacrifices friendship and honor to gloat over him.To make matters worse, armies of elves and humans appear at the Lonely Mountain, intending to take over some of the dwarves' gold as compensation for the losses caused by the dragon.For years, the beast ravaged the area and destroyed their settlements.Proud Thorin does not intend to give in to the demands of the newcomers.To resolve conflicts, Bilbo secretly gives the elves the archjewel.They use the treasure as an argument in negotiations with Thorin, and the hobbit becomes a traitor to the dwarves.While representatives of different races are arguing with each other and trying to force concessions, the army of their common enemy is approaching the dwarves' headquarters.In the face of danger, the conflicting parties must unite.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Gandalf - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Bilbo - Martin Freeman</actor>
      <actor>Thorin - Richard Armitage</actor>
      <actor>Balin - Ken Stott</actor>
      <actor>Dwalin - Graham McTavish</actor>
      <actor>Bifur - William Kircher</actor>
      <actor>Bofur - James Nesbitt</actor>
      <actor>Bombur - Stephen Hunter</actor>
      <actor>Fili - Dean O'Gorman</actor>
      <actor>Kili - Aidan Turner</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503181000 +0500" stop="20260503195000 +0500">
    <title>Minecraft</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Garrett (Jason Momoa), Henry (Sebastian Hansen), Natalie (Emma Myers) and Dawn (Danielle Brooks) constantly struggle with problems.The lives of these four change when a magical portal pulls them into a strange land full of cubes.The Overworld turns out to be a place where everything is possible thanks to imagination, which, however, is sometimes difficult to control.Once there, Garrett, Henry, Natalie and Dawn meet Steve (Jack Black), who was trapped on this side of the portal many years earlier.Together with him, they decide to defend the unusual land from evil creatures called piglins.For them to succeed, they will have to show courage and discover qualities that will make it easier for them to find their place in the real world later.A hit production for the whole family, inspired by the popular game.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jared Hess</director>
      <actor>Vice Principal Marlene - Jennifer Coolidge</actor>
      <actor>Garett Garrison - Jason Momoa</actor>
      <actor>Natalie - Emma Myers</actor>
      <actor>Steve - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Dawn - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Henry - Sebastian Hansen</actor>
      <actor>Malgosha - Allan Henry</actor>
      <actor>Young Steve - Bram Scott-Breheny</actor>
      <actor>Young Garrett - Moana Williams</actor>
      <actor>HR Person - Mark Wright</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Family Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503195000 +0500" stop="20260503223000 +0500">
    <title>Dune: Part Two</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After an insidious attack by the Harkonnens and the death of his father, Paul Atreides (Timothée Chalamet) and his pregnant mother, Jessica (Rebecca Ferguson), hide in the desert among the Fremen.There, a young man's feelings for Chani (Zendaya) sprout.At the same time, he matures spiritually.The leader of the wandering people, Stilgar (Javier Bardem), closely observes the only descendant of the Atreides family and becomes convinced that he is the chosen one, whose coming has been predicted for generations.However, to be accepted by the Fremen, Paul must pass the ultimate test by riding a monstrous worm.Meanwhile, Baron Vladimir Harkonnen (Stellan Skarsgard) finds out that Paul is alive.He knows he has to hurry.He decides to take control of the entire planet Arrakis.He starts launching attack after attack.A continuation of the spectacular production from 2021, which was awarded six Oscars.Both films are adaptations of the famous science fiction novel by Frank Herbert.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>Paul Atreides - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Chani - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Lady Jessica Atreides - Rebecca Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Stilgar - Javier Bardem</actor>
      <actor>Gurney Halleck - Josh Brolin</actor>
      <actor>Feyd-Rautha Harkonnen - Austin Butler</actor>
      <actor>Princess Irulan Corrino - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Glossu Rabban Harkonnen - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Emperor Shaddam IV - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Thufir Hawat - Stephen Henderson</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503223000 +0500" stop="20260504002500 +0500">
    <title>Beautiful</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The intertwined adventures of several women who are looking for happiness and fulfillment at different stages of life.Magda (Marta Nieradkiewicz) tries to reconcile raising children and running a home with her professional ambitions.Distrustful Basia (Marta Ścisłowicz) avoids love, even though she wants it very much.Krysia (Hanna Śleszyńska), a married woman for 30 years, tries to arouse a bit of enthusiasm in the bored and apathetic Władek (Olaf Lubaszenko).Businesswoman Agata (Katarzyna Herman) is successful at work, but cannot find a common language with her daughter.Julia (Kamila Urzędowska) tries to make it in an industry that values ​​only youth and beauty.She discovers how much she will have to sacrifice.Polish remake of the German comedy "Wunderschön" from 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Katia Priwieziencew</director>
      <actor>Krystyna - Hanna Śleszyńska</actor>
      <actor>Władek - Olaf Lubaszenko</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Marta Nieradkiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Maciek - Mikołaj Roznerski</actor>
      <actor>Baśka - Marta Ścisłowicz</actor>
      <actor>Kuba - Konrad Eleryk</actor>
      <actor>Agata - Katarzyna Herman</actor>
      <actor>Julka - Kamila Urzędowska</actor>
      <actor>Klaudia - Wiktoria Bylinka</actor>
      <actor>Patryk - Hugo Tarres</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>