<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506035500 +0500" stop="20260506053500 +0500">
    <title>Kneecap</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>2010. Liam (Mo Chara) and Naoise (Móglaí Bap) live in west Belfast.Growing up, they learned to speak Irish from the other's father, Arl (Michael Fassbender), who faked his own death to avoid repression from the British authorities and is now disillusioned with his son's hedonistic lifestyle.One night, Liam is arrested for drug possession.During interrogation, he refuses to speak English.So the police call in a translator, JJ Ó Dochartaigh (DJ Próvai), a music teacher at an Irish-speaking school.He helps Liam avoid charges and takes his notes with him.When at home he realizes that the lyrics are in Irish, he convinces the boy and his friend to start a hip-hop band, claiming that music would be a way to introduce the native language to the young generation.Liam names the group Kneecap.When the trio starts giving concerts, it turns out that crowds come to them.However, the musicians immediately begin to fall victim to sharp attacks from both the media and the extreme republican organization RRAD.Inspired by true events, the story of the creation of a popular Irish band.The main roles in the film were played by musicians who formed the group in reality.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rich Peppiatt</director>
      <actor>Naoise - Móglaí Bap</actor>
      <actor>Liam - Mo Chara</actor>
      <actor>JJ - DJ Próvai</actor>
      <actor>Detective Ellis - Josie Walker</actor>
      <actor>Caitlin - Fionnuala Flaherty</actor>
      <actor>Georgia - Jessica Reynolds</actor>
      <actor>Doyle - Adam Best</actor>
      <actor>Dolores - Simone Kirby</actor>
      <actor>Arló Ó Cairealláin - Michael Fassbender</actor>
      <actor>Sean - Matthew Sharpe</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506053500 +0500" stop="20260506072500 +0500">
    <title>Life</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Research carried out by a six-person team of cosmonauts is underway on the International Space Station.The crew makes a breakthrough discovery - they manage to observe the first evidence of life on Mars.However, the astronauts discover that the form of life they have found is unexpectedly intelligent, and at the same time dangerous.Behind the camera, Swedish director Daniel Espinosa, and on screen, among others:Oscar candidate Jake Gyllenhaal, Golden Globe nominees Rebecca Ferguson and Ryan Reynolds, and Hiroyuki Sanada - winner of the award granted by the Japanese Film Academy.The advantage of the production are its spectacular special effects.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Daniel Espinosa</director>
      <actor>David Jordan - Jake Gyllenhaal</actor>
      <actor>Sho Murakami - Hiroyuki Sanada</actor>
      <actor>Rory Adams - Ryan Reynolds</actor>
      <actor>Miranda North - Rebecca Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Ekaterina Golovkina - Olga Dihovichnaya</actor>
      <actor>Hugh Derry - Ariyon Bakare</actor>
      <actor>Student 2 - Jesus Del Orden</actor>
      <actor>Student 1 - Allen McLean</actor>
      <actor>Student 3 - Leila Grace</actor>
      <actor>Student 4 - Mari Gvelesiani</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506072500 +0500" stop="20260506090000 +0500">
    <title>Sanctuary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hal Porterfield (Christopher Abbott) orders room service at a posh hotel.Rebecca Marin (Margaret Qualley) shows up at the apartment to interview him for the position of general manager of this chain of facilities.Her questions become more and more personal and lead to a surprising ending.In reality, the woman is a dominatrix who follows the script prepared by Hal.However, the relationship does not follow the script ordered by the client.The woman decides to blackmail the rich man.She claims that she recorded a compromising sex tape with him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zachary Wigon</director>
      <actor>Hal - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Hallway - Francisco Castaneda</actor>
      <actor>Woman in the Hallway - Kathie Young</actor>
      <actor>Older Phil Porterfield - Dominic Defilips</actor>
      <actor>Younger Phil Porterfield - Rene Calvo</actor>
      <actor>Hal's Mother - Danita Battle</actor>
      <actor>Young Hal - Christian Casatelli</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506090000 +0500" stop="20260506103000 +0500">
    <title>Tripped Up</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lizzy (Leah Lewis) has always dreamed of becoming a chef.However, participating in a culinary reality show and later working in a New York restaurant became a source of frustration for her.A cooking enthusiast is one step away from giving up her greatest passion.The last chance to stay in the catering industry is to participate in a culinary festival.Together with her friends, Mary (Ashley Moore), Kai (Ariel Winter) and Taylor (Sasha Fox), she sets off on an adventure.If she fails, she is ready to look for another path in life.Unfortunately, the team has been plagued by bad luck since the beginning of the expedition.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Shruti Ganguly</director>
      <actor>Lizzy - Leah Lewis</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Ashley Moore</actor>
      <actor>Kai - Ariel Winter</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Sasha Fox</actor>
      <actor>Patty - Vanessa L. Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ashley - Jo Ellen Pellman</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Danny Kornfeld</actor>
      <actor>Jose - Gil Perez-Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Missy - Judy Gold</actor>
      <actor>Lotus - Justin Guarini</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506103000 +0500" stop="20260506124000 +0500">
    <title>Little women</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The times of the Civil War.In the absence of their father, who is serving in the military away from the family, the four March sisters from Orchard House are cared for by their mother alone.Marmee wants them to find their own path and helps them enter adulthood.Each of them has a different personality.The oldest Meg dreams of becoming an actress.Family-oriented and warm, Beth has a talent for playing the piano.Jo, an aspiring writer, pursues her goal with her characteristic energy and tenacity.Amy, a bit smart, wants to become a painter.Despite their own problems, the girls are not indifferent to other people's suffering.Young women will get to know the taste of first loves and disappointments.Fate subjects them to tests, after which their lives will never be the same again.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Greta Gerwig</director>
      <actor>Jo March - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Meg March - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Amy March - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Beth March - Eliza Scanlen</actor>
      <actor>Marmee March - Laura Dern</actor>
      <actor>Theodore 'Laurie' Laurence - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Dashwood - Tracy Letts</actor>
      <actor>Father March - Bob Odenkirk</actor>
      <actor>John Brooke - James Norton</actor>
      <actor>Friedrich Bhaer - Louis Garrel</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506124000 +0500" stop="20260506145000 +0500">
    <title>Spider-Man: Homecoming</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Young Peter Parker is fascinated by the Avengers team.He has the opportunity to experience an amazing adventure alongside his idols and unrivaled role models.After all, the teenager must return home and try to get used to his uninteresting everyday life as an ordinary mortal.He still lives with his good Aunt May, goes to college, and hangs out with friends.At the same time, he remains under the watchful care of Tony Stark, i.e. Iron Man - his mentor and greatest authority.He also tries to fight the pessimistic thoughts that plague him, that no one appreciates his activities, which bring so much benefit to society.Everything changes when it turns out that a new enemy is waiting for the superhero.One day, a dangerous Vulture appears on the boy's path.Peter must stand up for what he loves most.Not only are the lives of his loved ones at risk, but also those of other New York residents.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jon Watts</director>
      <actor>Peter Parker - Tom Holland</actor>
      <actor>Adrian Toomes - Michael Keaton</actor>
      <actor>Tony Stark - Robert Downey Jr.</actor>
      <actor>May Parker - Marisa Tomei</actor>
      <actor>Happy Hogan - Jon Favreau</actor>
      <actor>Pepper Potts - Gwyneth Paltrow</actor>
      <actor>Michelle - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Aaron Davis - Donald Glover</actor>
      <actor>Ned - Jacob Batalon</actor>
      <actor>Liz - Laura Harrier</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506145000 +0500" stop="20260506151500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Running</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tim Kirkby</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506151500 +0500" stop="20260506154500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">D.C</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tim Kirkby</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506154500 +0500" stop="20260506170000 +0500">
    <title>Living Large</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12-year-old Ben sings in a rock band and loves cooking.A real revolution comes in the boy's life when he decides to lose excess weight.Unfortunately, maintaining discipline is not easy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kristina Dufková</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506170000 +0500" stop="20260506184500 +0500">
    <title>Summer School, 2001</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kien returns to Cheb in the Czech Republic, where his relatives run a stall at the market.His appearance changes the family's life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Duzan Duong</director>
      <actor>Kien - Duong Bui</actor>
      <actor>Nudista - Pablo Maldonado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506184500 +0500" stop="20260506203000 +0500">
    <title>Wolfgang (extraordinari)</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the sudden death of his mother, nine-year-old Wolfgang (Jordi Catalán), an exceptionally gifted boy with features on the autism spectrum, is forced to live with his father, Carles (Miki Esparbé), whom he has never met before.An orderly nine-year-old who strives for perfection cannot stand his father's chaotic lifestyle.He wants to escape to Paris to study at the Grimald Academy and become the best pianist in the world.When Carles discovers his plan, he must make the most important decision in his life: follow his dream of an acting career or sacrifice his plans and become the father Wolfgang really needs.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Ruiz Caldera</director>
      <actor>Carlos - Miki Esparbé</actor>
      <actor>Matilde - Angels Gonyalons</actor>
      <actor>Paco - Berto Romero</actor>
      <actor>Mia - Anna Castillo</actor>
      <actor>Ingrid - Nausicaa Bonnín</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Ruth Llopis</actor>
      <actor>Juana - Montse Alcoverro</actor>
      <actor>Director Serie - Dafnis Balduz</actor>
      <actor>Directora de Casting - Reichel Delgado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506203000 +0500" stop="20260506223000 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: Eclipse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After a painful separation, Bella and her lover can enjoy each other's company again.The teenager wants to be transformed into an immortal being, which will allow them to be united forever.Before that, however, he has to take care of more mundane matters - pass his high school leaving exams and get into college.In addition, he is worried about his friend Jacob.It turns out that soon he and Edward will have to join forces to ensure the safety of the girl who has won their hearts.The relative peace of all the bloodsuckers and werewolves of Forks is disturbed by disturbing news from Seattle.It turns out that mysterious murders are taking place there.People are being killed by a pack of vampires, spreading fear and destruction around.The gang is recruiting new members.It is headed by Riley.He was chosen as the leader by the vengeful Victoria, who is seeking Bella's life.Thanks to Alice's visions and the Cullens' vigilance, they manage to protect her.Enemy races unite in the face of danger.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Slade</director>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Victoria - Bryce Dallas Howard</actor>
      <actor>Riley - Xavier Samuel</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Carlisle Cullen - Peter Facinelli</actor>
      <actor>Jessica Stanley - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Mike - Michael Welch</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506223000 +0500" stop="20260506232500 +0500">
    <title>The Tourist</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">In the dew of Lethe's flood</sub-title>
    <desc>A man (Jamie Dornan) traveling through the wilderness has an accident.His car is rammed by a tanker and he barely escapes with his life.When he wakes up injured in the hospital, he doesn't remember anything.He doesn't know what happened or who he is.He tries to use all the meetings with people and the clues he receives to discover his identity and past.He must do this before his enemies find him.A suspenseful, full of mysteries story of a man who faces amnesia and a dark past.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Sweeney</director>
      <actor>The Man - Jamie Dornan</actor>
      <actor>Helen Chambers - Danielle Macdonald</actor>
      <actor>Luci - Shalom Brune-Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Ólafur Darri Ólafsson</actor>
      <actor>Ralph - Danny Adcock</actor>
      <actor>Detective Inspector Lachlan Rogers - Damon Herriman</actor>
      <actor>Sergeant Rodney Lammon - Kamil Ellis</actor>
      <actor>Marko - Damien Strouthos</actor>
      <actor>Ethan Krum - Greg Larsen</actor>
      <actor>Lena Pascal - Victoria Haralabidou</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260506232500 +0500" stop="20260507002000 +0500">
    <title>The Tourist</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Waiting for the Sun</sub-title>
    <desc>A man (Jamie Dornan) traveling through the wilderness has an accident.His car is rammed by a tanker and he barely escapes with his life.When he wakes up injured in the hospital, he doesn't remember anything.He doesn't know what happened or who he is.He tries to use all the meetings with people and the clues he receives to discover his identity and past.He must do this before his enemies find him.A suspenseful, full of mysteries story of a man who faces amnesia and a dark past.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Sweeney</director>
      <actor>The Man - Jamie Dornan</actor>
      <actor>Helen Chambers - Danielle Macdonald</actor>
      <actor>Luci - Shalom Brune-Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Ólafur Darri Ólafsson</actor>
      <actor>Ralph - Danny Adcock</actor>
      <actor>Detective Inspector Lachlan Rogers - Damon Herriman</actor>
      <actor>Sergeant Rodney Lammon - Kamil Ellis</actor>
      <actor>Marko - Damien Strouthos</actor>
      <actor>Ethan Krum - Greg Larsen</actor>
      <actor>Lena Pascal - Victoria Haralabidou</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507002000 +0500" stop="20260507023000 +0500">
    <title>Sinners</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1932. Twin brothers Smoke and Stack (double role of Michael B. Jordan), who have a difficult past, return from Chicago to their hometown in Mississippi.They try to escape from problems and a life of crime.They establish a music club for black people and hope for a new beginning.Their enemy, however, are dark, sinister forces that they must face.At stake is not only the lives of the brothers and their loved ones, but also their culture, history and memory.A dark cinema combining elements of action, horror and a musical drawing on the blues tradition.It is a story about an attempt at redemption and the fight against an invisible evil that symbolizes the weight of the past and past sins.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ryan Coogler</director>
      <actor>Mary - Hailee Steinfeld</actor>
      <actor>Remmick - Jack O'Connell</actor>
      <actor>Smoke - Michael B. Jordan</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Wunmi Mosaku</actor>
      <actor>Joan - Lola Kirke</actor>
      <actor>Delta Slim - Delroy Lindo</actor>
      <actor>Grace Chow - Li Jun Li</actor>
      <actor>Cornbread - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Pearline - Jayme Lawson</actor>
      <actor>Hogwood - David Maldonado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507023000 +0500" stop="20260507040500 +0500">
    <title>Drag Me to Hell</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Los Angeles.Christine Brown (Alison Lohman) works in a bank in the lending department and successfully climbs the career ladder.One day, an unusual client comes to her, an old and strange-looking gypsy girl, Sylvia Ganush (Lorna Raver).She asks for help in postponing the mortgage installment payment date.When Christine refuses to fulfill the order, the furious old woman curses her.He only has three days to remove the charm.After this time, the terrifying demon Lamia will take her to hell... An effective, suspenseful horror film, successfully combining elements of horror and black humor.The film was directed by Sam Raimi, author of the cult "Evil Dead", three parts of "Spider-Man" and "The Grudge" trilogy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sam Raimi</director>
      <actor>Christine Brown - Alison Lohman</actor>
      <actor>Clay Dalton - Justin Long</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Jacks - David Paymer</actor>
      <actor>Shaun San Dena - Adriana Barraza</actor>
      <actor>Leonard Dalton - Chelcie Ross</actor>
      <actor>Stu Rubin - Reggie Lee</actor>
      <actor>Trudy Dalton - Molly Cheek</actor>
      <actor>Ilenka Ganush - Bojana Novakovic</actor>
      <actor>Milos - Kevin Foster</actor>
      <actor>Farm Worker - Alexis Cruz</actor>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507040500 +0500" stop="20260507053000 +0500">
    <title>Gaslit By My Husband: The Morgan Metzer Story</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Morgan (Jana Kramer) is attacked by a masked assailant.A moment later, her ex-husband appears.His testimony raises concerns - has he come to help her, or is he hiding a dark secret?</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Lee Gabiana</director>
      <actor>Morgan Metzer - Jana Kramer</actor>
      <actor>Rodney Metzer - Austin Nichols</actor>
      <actor>Nicole - Abigail Esmena</actor>
      <actor>Amilia Metzer - Jolie Rae Caussin</actor>
      <actor>Mason Metzer - Maximo Sebastian</actor>
      <actor>Kathy Metzer - Stephanie Cotton</actor>
      <actor>Rod Metzer - Pete Burris</actor>
      <actor>Lindsey - Denise Dal Vera</actor>
      <actor>Richard - J. Barrett Cooper</actor>
      <actor>Therapist - Lee Avant</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507053000 +0500" stop="20260507073500 +0500">
    <title>The Outrun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A young woman named Rona (Saoirse Ronan), who has recently left an addiction treatment center, returns from London to her native Scotland, to one of the islands of the Orkney archipelago.Because her parents are separated, she lives alternately with her mother, where she meets with her religious friends, and with her father, whom she helps on the farm.At the same time, she is still trying to cope with difficult memories - the beginning of her stay in London, where she started studying biology and often went to clubs with her boyfriend Daynin (Paapa Essiedu).She didn't even notice when she fell into alcoholism, which led to problems in her relationship and began to destroy her life.Meanwhile, while staying on the island, Rona decides to return to London.However, already on the ferry he feels that he is unable to control the urge to drink alcohol.He must re-plan his life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nora Fingscheidt</director>
      <actor>Rona - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Young Rona - Freya Evans</actor>
      <actor>Daynin - Paapa Essiedu</actor>
      <actor>Barman James - Seamus Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Bouncer Dave - David Garrick</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Rasamalar - Aniya Sekkanu</actor>
      <actor>Andrew - Stephen Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Saskia Reeves</actor>
      <actor>Young Orcadian Man - Liam Smith</actor>
      <actor>Bible Group Evie - Eilidh Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507073500 +0500" stop="20260507090000 +0500">
    <title>Critical Incident: A Death At The Border</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Anastasio Hernández-Rojas died a few days after being detained by border authorities in 2010.Everything points to murder, but no one has been charged in this case.</desc>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507090000 +0500" stop="20260507104500 +0500">
    <title>Summer School, 2001</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kien returns to Cheb in the Czech Republic, where his relatives run a stall at the market.His appearance changes the family's life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Duzan Duong</director>
      <actor>Kien - Duong Bui</actor>
      <actor>Nudista - Pablo Maldonado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507104500 +0500" stop="20260507123000 +0500">
    <title>Wolfgang (extraordinari)</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the sudden death of his mother, nine-year-old Wolfgang (Jordi Catalán), an exceptionally gifted boy with features on the autism spectrum, is forced to live with his father, Carles (Miki Esparbé), whom he has never met before.An orderly nine-year-old who strives for perfection cannot stand his father's chaotic lifestyle.He wants to escape to Paris to study at the Grimald Academy and become the best pianist in the world.When Carles discovers his plan, he must make the most important decision in his life: follow his dream of an acting career or sacrifice his plans and become the father Wolfgang really needs.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Ruiz Caldera</director>
      <actor>Carlos - Miki Esparbé</actor>
      <actor>Matilde - Angels Gonyalons</actor>
      <actor>Paco - Berto Romero</actor>
      <actor>Mia - Anna Castillo</actor>
      <actor>Ingrid - Nausicaa Bonnín</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Ruth Llopis</actor>
      <actor>Juana - Montse Alcoverro</actor>
      <actor>Director Serie - Dafnis Balduz</actor>
      <actor>Directora de Casting - Reichel Delgado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507123000 +0500" stop="20260507143500 +0500">
    <title>Spider-Man: Far From Home</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The authorities of the Midtown School of Science and Technology are organizing a two-week expedition to the Old Continent.Tour participants visit, among others, Venice.The city is attacked by a powerful Water Elemental.Peter Parker tries to save his friends, but he is powerless against the creature.Fortunately, Mysterio comes to his aid and kills the creature.A mysterious savior once lived in an alternate reality.He convinces Parker to engage in the fight against the creatures that were supposed to destroy his civilization.The boy refuses because he wants to live the life of an ordinary teenager and find happiness with MJ.As a result of a trick involving Nick Fury, he changes his mind.He makes a disastrous decision when he gives Beck the glasses he inherited from his mentor Tony Stark, which enable him to take control of the artificial intelligence created by the millionaire.He must correct his mistake as soon as possible.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jon Watts</director>
      <actor>Peter Parker - Tom Holland</actor>
      <actor>Nick Fury - Samuel L. Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Quentin Beck - Jake Gyllenhaal</actor>
      <actor>May Parker - Marisa Tomei</actor>
      <actor>Happy Hogan - Jon Favreau</actor>
      <actor>MJ - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Ned Leeds - Jacob Batalon</actor>
      <actor>Flash Thompson - Tony Revolori</actor>
      <actor>Betty Brant - Angourie Rice</actor>
      <actor>Brad Davis - Remy Hii</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507143500 +0500" stop="20260507150000 +0500">
    <title>Veep 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Some New Beginning</sub-title>
    <desc>In the third season, vice president Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) tries for a promotion.To this end, he is trying to win over voters during the premiere of his new book 'Some New Beginnings'.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Addison</director>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507150000 +0500" stop="20260507153000 +0500">
    <title>Veep 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Choice</sub-title>
    <desc>In the third season, vice president Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) tries for a promotion.To this end, he is trying to win over voters during the premiere of his new book 'Some New Beginnings'.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Becky Martin</director>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507153000 +0500" stop="20260507170500 +0500">
    <title>Drazen</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1970s.Teenage Dražen Petrovic (Tonko Stosic) living in Šibenik discovers, thanks to his older brother, Aleksander (Lovre Tanfara), that he has a talent for playing basketball.At first, he trained only with him or alone - in the evenings in the gym.When his abilities are noticed at school, he joins the local team, Šibenka, where he is successful.During this time, he falls in love with Renata (Romina Tonkovic).Over time, a talented young man (Domagoj Nizic) goes to a club in Zagreb and then abroad, among others.to Real Madrid, and finally received an offer to play with the New York Brooklyn Nets team, part of the NBA league.Unfortunately, Dražen's passion for basketball also becomes his curse, and success is associated with problems in his personal life, also in his relationship with Renata.A biographical story about the outstanding Croatian athlete, called the Mozart of basketball, who was the first European to play in the NBA.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Danilo Serbedzija</director>
      <director>Ljubo Zdjelarevic</director>
      <actor>Drazen Petrovic - Tonko Stosic</actor>
      <actor>Drazen Petrovic - Domagoj Nizic</actor>
      <actor>Renata - Romina Tonkovic</actor>
      <actor>Biserka Petrovic - Zrinka Cvitešić</actor>
      <actor>Jole Petrovic - Dragan Micanović</actor>
      <actor>Aleksandar Petrovic - Lovre Tanfara</actor>
      <actor>Warren LeGarie - Valentin Perkovic</actor>
      <actor>Klara - Victoria Hauer</actor>
      <actor>Aleksandar Petrovic - Pavle Matusko</actor>
      <actor>Willis Reed - James Perri</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507170500 +0500" stop="20260507182500 +0500">
    <title>The Night Before Christmas In Wonderland</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>One day, Santa Claus receives a letter from the Queen of Hearts.Together with his faithful team of reindeer, he sets off to Karina Czarów to deliver a gift for her.However, he quickly gets into serious trouble.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Baynton</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507182500 +0500" stop="20260507184500 +0500">
    <title>Book of Dragons</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hiccup, Astrid, Fishlegs and Gobber learn the secrets of the dragons contained in the book.Gobber tells the others the story of Borek the Unlucky, who was the first to describe these unusual creatures.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Steve Hickner</director>
    </credits><date>2011</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507184500 +0500" stop="20260507203500 +0500">
    <title>Soul On Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nine-year-old John O'Leary suffers burns to almost his entire body.He struggles with pain and limitations.However, he wins love and makes his dreams come true.He inspires others by showing how to live life to the fullest.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sean McNamara</director>
      <actor>John O'Leary - Joel Courtney</actor>
      <actor>Denny O'Leary - John Corbett</actor>
      <actor>Susan O'Leary - Stephanie Szostak</actor>
      <actor>Beth O'Leary - Masey McLain</actor>
      <actor>Nurse Roy - DeVon Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Jack Buck - William H. Macy</actor>
      <actor>Young John - James McCracken</actor>
      <actor>Amy O'Leary - Stella Bratcher</actor>
      <actor>Susie O'Leary - Lucy Panozzo</actor>
      <actor>Jim O'Leary - Mikey Cestone</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507203500 +0500" stop="20260507223000 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn - Part 1</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bella Swan and Edward Cullen are getting married.They spend their honeymoon on a private island in Brazil belonging to the groom's family.Two weeks later, Bella discovers she is pregnant.The fetus is developing at a rapid pace.The couple returns to Forks.It turns out that Bella's condition means great danger to her.The werewolves, led by Sam, want to kill her unborn offspring, who may turn out to be a demon.Jacob defies his pack and decides to protect his lost loved one.The Cullen family prepares for a difficult birth.Edward will have to fight to save the person he loves with all his heart.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Condon</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Jessica Stanley - Anna Kendrick</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Jane - Dakota Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Aro - Michael Sheen</actor>
      <actor>Emmett Cullen - Kellan Lutz</actor>
      <actor>Rosalie Hale - Nikki Reed</actor>
      <actor>Caius - Jamie Campbell Bower</actor>
      <actor>Irina - Maggie Grace</actor>
    </credits><date>2011</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260507223000 +0500" stop="20260508001000 +0500">
    <title>French Courier from Liberty, Kansas Evening Sun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The 20th-century fictional French town of Ennui-sur-Blasé is the headquarters of "Kurier Francuski", a magazine published by American emigrants.When a respected editor, Kansas native Arthur Howitzer Jr (Bill Murray), dies, the entire team gathers to write an obituary.Their memories make up four colorful stories.Herbsaint Sazerac (Owen Wilson), an avid cyclist, recalls dark stories related to the city, showing its dangerous alleys.J.K.L.Berensen (Tilda Swinton) presents the story of an insane painter, Moses Rosenthaler (Benicio del Toro), who creates from behind prison bars.A brilliant artist is involved in an affair with a guard and his muse (Lea Seydoux).An art dealer, Julian Cadazio (Adrien Brody), tries to make money from his paintings.Lucinda Krementz (Frances McDormand) tells the story of a fiery student rebellion led by Zeffirelli (Timothée Chalamet).It is also a story of beautiful love and tragic death on the barricades.Roebuck Wright (Jeffrey Wright) presents a story about drugs, kidnappings and refined cuisine, and its hero will be Lieutenant Nescaffier (Steve Park).Another visual masterpiece from Wes Anderson is a tribute to old-style journalism.The elaborate, nostalgic anthology is inspired by the famous weekly "The New Yorker" and the personalities who made up its editorial staff.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Wes Anderson</director>
      <actor>Moses Rosenthaler - Benicio Del Toro</actor>
      <actor>Julian Cadazio - Adrien Brody</actor>
      <actor>J.K.L. Berensen - Tilda Swinton</actor>
      <actor>Simone - Léa Seydoux</actor>
      <actor>Lucinda Krementz - Frances McDormand</actor>
      <actor>Zeffirelli - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Juliette - Lyna Khoudri</actor>
      <actor>Roebuck Wright - Jeffrey Wright</actor>
      <actor>The Commissaire - Mathieu Amalric</actor>
      <actor>Nescaffier - Stephen Park</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>