<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504051000 +0500" stop="20260504070500 +0500">
    <title>Get him to the Greek</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>British rock star Aldous Snow (Russell Brand) is in crisis.His latest album turned out to be a failure, he broke up with his life partner, and the court took away his parental rights.After all this, the musician decided to use stimulants again, which he had previously given up for several years.One day, he is approached by Aaron Green (Jonah Hill), an employee of the record company that publishes his works.At the request of his boss (Sean "P. Diddy" Combs), the man is to bring Snow to an amphitheater in Los Angeles to celebrate his concert from a decade ago with another performance.It turns out that this task is not that easy.The film is a loose continuation of the 2008 comedy "Boys Cry Too."Nicholas Stoller was back behind the camera, and the controversial actor and comedian, Russell Brand, played the main role.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Aldous Snow - Russell Brand</actor>
      <actor>Jackie Q - Rose Byrne</actor>
      <actor>African Child in Video - Tyler McKinney</actor>
      <actor>Herself - Zoe Salmon</actor>
      <actor>Naples - Lino Facioli</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Lars Ulrich</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Mario López</actor>
      <actor>Herself - Pink</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Billy Bush</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Kurt Loder</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Musical Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504070500 +0500" stop="20260504090000 +0500">
    <title>Beautiful</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The intertwined adventures of several women who are looking for happiness and fulfillment at different stages of life.Magda (Marta Nieradkiewicz) tries to reconcile raising children and running a home with her professional ambitions.Distrustful Basia (Marta Ścisłowicz) avoids love, even though she wants it very much.Krysia (Hanna Śleszyńska), a married woman for 30 years, tries to arouse a bit of enthusiasm in the bored and apathetic Władek (Olaf Lubaszenko).Businesswoman Agata (Katarzyna Herman) is successful at work, but cannot find a common language with her daughter.Julia (Kamila Urzędowska) tries to make it in an industry that values ​​only youth and beauty.She discovers how much she will have to sacrifice.Polish remake of the German comedy "Wunderschön" from 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Katia Priwieziencew</director>
      <actor>Krystyna - Hanna Śleszyńska</actor>
      <actor>Władek - Olaf Lubaszenko</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Marta Nieradkiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Maciek - Mikołaj Roznerski</actor>
      <actor>Baśka - Marta Ścisłowicz</actor>
      <actor>Kuba - Konrad Eleryk</actor>
      <actor>Agata - Katarzyna Herman</actor>
      <actor>Julka - Kamila Urzędowska</actor>
      <actor>Klaudia - Wiktoria Bylinka</actor>
      <actor>Patryk - Hugo Tarres</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504090000 +0500" stop="20260504103500 +0500">
    <title>Minecraft</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Garrett (Jason Momoa), Henry (Sebastian Hansen), Natalie (Emma Myers) and Dawn (Danielle Brooks) constantly struggle with problems.The lives of these four change when a magical portal pulls them into a strange land full of cubes.The Overworld turns out to be a place where everything is possible thanks to imagination, which, however, is sometimes difficult to control.Once there, Garrett, Henry, Natalie and Dawn meet Steve (Jack Black), who was trapped on this side of the portal many years earlier.Together with him, they decide to defend the unusual land from evil creatures called piglins.For them to succeed, they will have to show courage and discover qualities that will make it easier for them to find their place in the real world later.A hit production for the whole family, inspired by the popular game.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jared Hess</director>
      <actor>Vice Principal Marlene - Jennifer Coolidge</actor>
      <actor>Garett Garrison - Jason Momoa</actor>
      <actor>Natalie - Emma Myers</actor>
      <actor>Steve - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Dawn - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Henry - Sebastian Hansen</actor>
      <actor>Malgosha - Allan Henry</actor>
      <actor>Young Steve - Bram Scott-Breheny</actor>
      <actor>Young Garrett - Moana Williams</actor>
      <actor>HR Person - Mark Wright</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Family Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504103500 +0500" stop="20260504131500 +0500">
    <title>Dune: Part Two</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After an insidious attack by the Harkonnens and the death of his father, Paul Atreides (Timothée Chalamet) and his pregnant mother, Jessica (Rebecca Ferguson), hide in the desert among the Fremen.There, a young man's feelings for Chani (Zendaya) sprout.At the same time, he matures spiritually.The leader of the wandering people, Stilgar (Javier Bardem), closely observes the only descendant of the Atreides family and becomes convinced that he is the chosen one, whose coming has been predicted for generations.However, to be accepted by the Fremen, Paul must pass the ultimate test by riding a monstrous worm.Meanwhile, Baron Vladimir Harkonnen (Stellan Skarsgard) finds out that Paul is alive.He knows he has to hurry.He decides to take control of the entire planet Arrakis.He starts launching attack after attack.A continuation of the spectacular production from 2021, which was awarded six Oscars.Both films are adaptations of the famous science fiction novel by Frank Herbert.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>Paul Atreides - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Chani - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Lady Jessica Atreides - Rebecca Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Stilgar - Javier Bardem</actor>
      <actor>Gurney Halleck - Josh Brolin</actor>
      <actor>Feyd-Rautha Harkonnen - Austin Butler</actor>
      <actor>Princess Irulan Corrino - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Glossu Rabban Harkonnen - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Emperor Shaddam IV - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Thufir Hawat - Stephen Henderson</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504131500 +0500" stop="20260504150500 +0500">
    <title>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>New York teenager Miles Morales visits an abandoned subway station.There he is bitten by a radioactive spider.He soon realizes that he has gained abilities similar to those of Spider-Man.Soon, Miles witnesses the fight between Spider Man and Kingpin, the Green Goblin and the Prowler.The superhero tries to turn off the accelerator, thanks to which the first of the villains wants to gain access to parallel universes and can destroy the city.He manages to give Miles a USB drive to deactivate the device and is then killed.Miles decides to honor his memory by becoming a new superhero.First of all, he must face Kingspin and his men, who will stop at nothing to recover the USB.The film won numerous awards, including an Oscar.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rodney Rothman</director>
      <director>Peter Ramsey</director>
      <director>Bob Persichetti</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504150500 +0500" stop="20260504153500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Helsinki</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Becky Martin</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504153500 +0500" stop="20260504160500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Andrew</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Christopher Morris</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504160500 +0500" stop="20260504181000 +0500">
    <title>Queen Of The Ring</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1930s.Single mother Mildred Bliss (Emily Bett Rickards), who has always been interested in sports, dreams of becoming a wrestler.When she meets the promoter of this sport, Billy Wolfe (Josh Lucas), she decides to try her hand at this discipline, although it belongs entirely to men and the law prohibits women from entering the ring.It quickly turns out that he can cope very well, even with players who are more powerful than him.Billy becomes her manager and lover, and soon her husband.The increasingly successful woman adopts the pseudonym Mildred Burke and over time becomes the first millionaire wrestling professional.Unfortunately, her successes in the ring do not go hand in hand with a successful personal life.First of all, her marriage is not a happy one.Based on a true story about the life of women's wrestling pioneer Mildred Burke.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ash Avildsen</director>
      <actor>Mildred 'Millie' Burke - Emily Bett Rickards</actor>
      <actor>Billy Wolfe - Josh Lucas</actor>
      <actor>G. Bill - Tyler Posey</actor>
      <actor>Jack Pfefer - Walton Goggins</actor>
      <actor>Mae Young - Francesca Eastwood</actor>
      <actor>Elvira Snodgrass - Marie Avgeropoulos</actor>
      <actor>June Byers - Kailey Farmer</actor>
      <actor>Bertha - Cara Buono</actor>
      <actor>Joe Jr. - Gavin Casalegno</actor>
      <actor>Gorgeous George Wagner - Adam Demos</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504181000 +0500" stop="20260504185500 +0500">
    <title>Doc Ii.</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dr. Amy Larsen, former chief of internal medicine, is rebuilding her life after a tragic accident that left her with no memory.Now she is an intern.Her past still haunts me.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E13</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Russell Lee Fine</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504185500 +0500" stop="20260504203000 +0500">
    <title>The Glassworker</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vincent Oliver, the son of renowned glassmaker Tomasz, is preparing for his first exhibition when he finds a letter from his childhood friend, Alliz Amano, whom he has always loved.He recalls how - raised by a pacifist father - he saw her for the first time.Alliz arrives in Vincent's city, Waterfront, with her parent, Colonel Amano.They become a couple.Meanwhile, a war breaks out and both he and his rival for the girl's favor, Malik, join the army.Tomasz is forced to produce glass rectifiers for the army.Some time later, the girl's father dies without any news at the front.When Malik returns to town with him, Alliz rewards him with a kiss, which Vincent witnesses.Devastated, he sabotages the production of rectifiers, but this leads to tragedy.The anime-inspired production with an anti-war message is the first Pakistani film made using the hand-animated technique.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Usman Riaz</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504203000 +0500" stop="20260504223000 +0500">
    <title>Twilight</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seventeen-year-old Bella Swan moves in with her father, who is the sheriff of a small town.At her new school, the teenager notices Edward Cullen.The unnaturally pale boy, who has the ability to read people's minds, is an inaccessible loner.Hoping that this will scare Bella away, Edward confesses to her that he is a vampire and that he and his entire family have been feeding on animal blood for centuries.This shocking truth does not discourage a girl in love.She and Cullen become inseparable.Their love, however, is threatened by a primal predatory instinct that is increasingly difficult for the boy to control.The couple is surrounded by wanderers hungry for human blood: Laurent, James and Victoria.The lovers face them.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Catherine Hardwicke</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Swan - Billy Burke</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Carlisle Cullen - Peter Facinelli</actor>
      <actor>Esme Cullen - Elizabeth Reaser</actor>
      <actor>Rosalie Hale - Nikki Reed</actor>
      <actor>Jasper Hale - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Emmett Cullen - Kellan Lutz</actor>
      <actor>James - Cam Gigandet</actor>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504223000 +0500" stop="20260505001000 +0500">
    <title>Your Monster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Actress Laura (Melissa Barrera) was supposed to become a star of the stage and live happily with the director of the show, Jacob (Edmund Donovan), but her beloved dumped her and took the role away.The devastated woman returns to her family home, where she spends all day in a bathrobe and crying.Her wailing gets on the nerves of the monster (Tommy Dewey), who has been living in the closet for years.The monster gives Laura two weeks to move out and threatens bloody revenge.Over time, however, an extraordinary bond develops between them, which helps Laura open her heart and follow her dreams.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Caroline Lindy</director>
      <actor>Laura Franco - Melissa Barrera</actor>
      <actor>Monster - Tommy Dewey</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Sullivan - Edmund Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Mazie Silverberg - Kayla Foster</actor>
      <actor>Jackie Dennon - Meghann Fahy</actor>
      <actor>Don McBride - Ikechukwu Ufomadu</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Megan Haley</actor>
      <actor>Will - Brandon Victor Dixon</actor>
      <actor>Scotty - Taylor Trensch</actor>
      <actor>Ellyn - Lana Young</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505001000 +0500" stop="20260505020000 +0500">
    <title>30 days of darkness</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The town of Barrow, Alaska, goes dark for thirty days every year.Most residents leave their homes at this time.The safety of those who decided to stay is ensured by young sheriff Eben Olsen (Josh Hartnett).He is struggling with serious personal problems.His marriage with Stella (Melissa George) is in crisis and she wants to leave him.Soon, however, they must unite their forces and fight the vampires who attack a town cut off from the world and plunged in darkness.Hungry monsters launch a bloody hunt for people imprisoned in Barrow.Eben, Stella and a handful of survivors begin their fight for survival.They do everything to wait for the end of the polar night.Adapted from a comic book by Steve Niles and Ben Templesmith.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Slade</director>
      <actor>Marlow - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Beau Brower - Mark Boone Junior</actor>
      <actor>Jake Oleson - Mark Rendall</actor>
      <actor>Denise - Amber Sainsbury</actor>
      <actor>Billy Kitka - Manu Bennett</actor>
      <actor>Iris - Megan Franich</actor>
      <actor>Doug Hertz - Joel Tobeck</actor>
      <actor>Lucy Ikos - Elizabeth Hawthorne</actor>
      <actor>Carter Davies - Nathaniel Lees</actor>
      <actor>Wilson Bulosan - Craig Hall</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505020000 +0500" stop="20260505033000 +0500">
    <title>Last Swim</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ziba (Deba Hekmat), whose family comes from Iran, lives in London and is an ambitious young woman.However, she hides a painful secret that none of her friends know about.Ziba has just gotten into university, where she is going to study astrophysics.On this occasion, he meets with his friends: Tara (Lydia Fleming), Shea (Solly McLeod) and Merf (Jay Lycurgo), with whom he intends to celebrate this event.She feels irritated when she learns that they are to be joined by a promising young football player, Malcolm (Denzel Baidoo), whom she does not know.Soon, however, an event occurs that makes him emotionally closer to her than her long-time friends.The future for both of them is not as bright as it might seem.Sasha Nathwani's feature-length directorial debut.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sasha Nathwani</director>
      <actor>Ziba - Deba Hekmat</actor>
      <actor>Tara - Lydia Fleming</actor>
      <actor>Shea - Solly McLeod</actor>
      <actor>Merf - Jay Lycurgo</actor>
      <actor>Malcolm - Denzel Baidoo</actor>
      <actor>Mona - Narges Rashidi</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505033000 +0500" stop="20260505050500 +0500">
    <title>Killer Heat</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greece.American Nick Bali (Joseph Gordon-Levitt) is hired to investigate the circumstances of the death of young shipping magnate Leo Vardakis (Richard Madden) in Crete.The deceased's sister-in-law, Penelope Vardakis (Shailene Woodley), does not believe the official police report.A private detective discovers that sunny landscapes hide many dark secrets and anyone can be a suspect.He discovers further facts about the rich and influential Vardakis family, as well as the brothers' complicated relationship.Adaptation of the short story "The Jealousy Man" by Jo Nesbo.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Philippe Lacôte</director>
      <actor>Nick Bali - Joseph Gordon-Levitt</actor>
      <actor>Penelope Vardakis - Shailene Woodley</actor>
      <actor>Elias 'Leonidas' - Richard Madden</actor>
      <actor>Audrey - Clare Holman</actor>
      <actor>Georges Mensah - Babou Ceesay</actor>
      <actor>Monique - Abbey Lee</actor>
      <actor>Victoria - Eleni Vergeti</actor>
      <actor>Yannis - Emmanouil Gavridakis</actor>
      <actor>Governor - Dimitris Topalidis</actor>
      <actor>Christopher - Christos Efthimiou</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505050500 +0500" stop="20260505071500 +0500">
    <title>NO</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Animal tamer OJ Haywood (Daniel Kaluuya) and his sister Emerald (Keke Palmer) live on a ranch in southern California where horses are trained for Hollywood film productions.They take over the business of their father, who died in suspicious circumstances.Problems are piling up for them.One day they become witnesses of inexplicable phenomena.Together with a former child star (Steven Yeun), an emcee at a family amusement park, they try to film supernatural incidents to make money by selling sensational materials.Their actions have unforeseen consequences.Director Jordan Peele made his debut in 2017 with the acclaimed thriller "Get Out!", for which he won an Oscar for the script.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jordan Peele</director>
      <actor>OJ Haywood - Daniel Kaluuya</actor>
      <actor>Emerald Haywood - Keke Palmer</actor>
      <actor>Angel Torres - Brandon Perea</actor>
      <actor>Antlers Holst - Michael Wincott</actor>
      <actor>Ricky 'Jupe' Park - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Amber Park - Wrenn Schmidt</actor>
      <actor>Otis Haywood Sr. - Keith David</actor>
      <actor>Ryder Muybridge - Devon Graye</actor>
      <actor>Gordy - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Nessie - Barbie Ferreira</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505071500 +0500" stop="20260505090000 +0500">
    <title>Your Monster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Actress Laura (Melissa Barrera) was supposed to become a star of the stage and live happily with the director of the show, Jacob (Edmund Donovan), but her beloved dumped her and took the role away.The devastated woman returns to her family home, where she spends all day in a bathrobe and crying.Her wailing gets on the nerves of the monster (Tommy Dewey), who has been living in the closet for years.The monster gives Laura two weeks to move out and threatens bloody revenge.Over time, however, an extraordinary bond develops between them, which helps Laura open her heart and follow her dreams.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Caroline Lindy</director>
      <actor>Laura Franco - Melissa Barrera</actor>
      <actor>Monster - Tommy Dewey</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Sullivan - Edmund Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Mazie Silverberg - Kayla Foster</actor>
      <actor>Jackie Dennon - Meghann Fahy</actor>
      <actor>Don McBride - Ikechukwu Ufomadu</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Megan Haley</actor>
      <actor>Will - Brandon Victor Dixon</actor>
      <actor>Scotty - Taylor Trensch</actor>
      <actor>Ellyn - Lana Young</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505090000 +0500" stop="20260505103500 +0500">
    <title>The Glassworker</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vincent Oliver, the son of renowned glassmaker Tomasz, is preparing for his first exhibition when he finds a letter from his childhood friend, Alliz Amano, whom he has always loved.He recalls how - raised by a pacifist father - he saw her for the first time.Alliz arrives in Vincent's city, Waterfront, with her parent, Colonel Amano.They become a couple.Meanwhile, a war breaks out and both he and his rival for the girl's favor, Malik, join the army.Tomasz is forced to produce glass rectifiers for the army.Some time later, the girl's father dies without any news at the front.When Malik returns to town with him, Alliz rewards him with a kiss, which Vincent witnesses.Devastated, he sabotages the production of rectifiers, but this leads to tragedy.The anime-inspired production with an anti-war message is the first Pakistani film made using the hand-animated technique.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Usman Riaz</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505103500 +0500" stop="20260505121000 +0500">
    <title>Verano en diciembre</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Four generations of women meet in Madrid at a convention organized by Teresa.She is accompanied by four daughters in their thirties, a granddaughter and her 95-year-old mother-in-law, who suffers from dementia.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Carolina África</director>
      <actor>Teresa - Carmen Machi</actor>
      <actor>Carmen - Bárbara Lennie</actor>
      <actor>Paloma - Vicky Luengo</actor>
      <actor>Martina - Lola Cordón</actor>
      <actor>Alicia - Beatriz Grimaldos</actor>
      <actor>Zoe - Vega Bosque</actor>
      <actor>Don Ramón - Antonio Resines</actor>
      <actor>Noelia - Irene Escolar</actor>
      <actor>Rodrigo - Nacho Fresneda</actor>
      <actor>Mujer de Rodrigo - Silvia Marsó</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505121000 +0500" stop="20260505140000 +0500">
    <title>Oscar's Eye</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nine-year-old Oscar cannot speak.Because of this, he is rejected and bullied by his peers.However, he becomes friends with the owner of the workshop, Erik, with whom he shares a common passion - photography.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jay Silverman</director>
      <actor>Eric Conway - Beau Bridges</actor>
      <actor>Evelyn Kennedy - Jessica Parker Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Frank Flynn - Bruce Davison</actor>
      <actor>Victor Kennedy - Scotty Tovar</actor>
      <actor>Oscar Kennedy - Miguel Gabriel</actor>
      <actor>Dermot Flynn - Ross Partridge</actor>
      <actor>Manny - Jorge Pallo</actor>
      <actor>Tony - Ayinde Howell</actor>
      <actor>Jim - Bob Bledsoe</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Ezekiel Bridges</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505140000 +0500" stop="20260505154500 +0500">
    <title>Frieda's Case</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 1904. A seamstress accused of a crime becomes the center of a trial that exposes the injustices of the legal system.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Maria Brendle</director>
      <actor>Frieda Keller - Julia Buchmann</actor>
      <actor>Walter Gmür - Stefan Merki</actor>
      <actor>Erna Gmür - Rachel Braunschweig</actor>
      <actor>Gesine - Marlene Tanczik</actor>
      <actor>Arnold Janggen - Max Simonischek</actor>
      <actor>Bertha - Liliane Amuat</actor>
      <actor>Frau Hartmann - Bigna Körner</actor>
      <actor>Landjäger Schönenberger - Aaron Hitz</actor>
      <actor>Arbeiterin - Ramona Saluz</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505154500 +0500" stop="20260505161000 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Shutdown</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Becky Martin</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505161000 +0500" stop="20260505164000 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">First Response</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), press secretary Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Armando Iannucci</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505164000 +0500" stop="20260505181500 +0500">
    <title>Tripped Up</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lizzy (Leah Lewis) has always dreamed of becoming a chef.However, participating in a culinary reality show and later working in a New York restaurant became a source of frustration for her.A cooking enthusiast is one step away from giving up her greatest passion.The last chance to stay in the catering industry is to participate in a culinary festival.Together with her friends, Mary (Ashley Moore), Kai (Ariel Winter) and Taylor (Sasha Fox), she sets off on an adventure.If she fails, she is ready to look for another path in life.Unfortunately, the team has been plagued by bad luck since the beginning of the expedition.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Shruti Ganguly</director>
      <actor>Lizzy - Leah Lewis</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Ashley Moore</actor>
      <actor>Kai - Ariel Winter</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Sasha Fox</actor>
      <actor>Patty - Vanessa L. Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ashley - Jo Ellen Pellman</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Danny Kornfeld</actor>
      <actor>Jose - Gil Perez-Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Missy - Judy Gold</actor>
      <actor>Lotus - Justin Guarini</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505181500 +0500" stop="20260505202500 +0500">
    <title>Little women</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The times of the Civil War.In the absence of their father, who is serving in the military away from the family, the four March sisters from Orchard House are cared for by their mother alone.Marmee wants them to find their own path and helps them enter adulthood.Each of them has a different personality.The oldest Meg dreams of becoming an actress.Family-oriented and warm, Beth has a talent for playing the piano.Jo, an aspiring writer, pursues her goal with her characteristic energy and tenacity.Amy, a bit smart, wants to become a painter.Despite their own problems, the girls are not indifferent to other people's suffering.Young women will get to know the taste of first loves and disappointments.Fate subjects them to tests, after which their lives will never be the same again.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Greta Gerwig</director>
      <actor>Jo March - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Meg March - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Amy March - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Beth March - Eliza Scanlen</actor>
      <actor>Marmee March - Laura Dern</actor>
      <actor>Theodore 'Laurie' Laurence - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Dashwood - Tracy Letts</actor>
      <actor>Father March - Bob Odenkirk</actor>
      <actor>John Brooke - James Norton</actor>
      <actor>Friedrich Bhaer - Louis Garrel</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505202500 +0500" stop="20260505223000 +0500">
    <title>The Twilight Saga: New Moon</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bella Swan (Kristen Stewart) celebrates her 18th birthday.The passing moments make her realize that she will one day grow old, while her boyfriend Edward Cullen (Robert Pattinson), who is a vampire, will always physically remain young.Despite this, the girl agrees to come to the party organized by the Cullen family.During her birthday party, Bella accidentally cuts her finger.At the sight of blood, one of the members of the vampire clan, Jasper (Jackson Rathbone), cannot stop feeling hungry.Unable to control himself, he attacks the girl.Edward saves his beloved, but decides not to put her in danger anymore.For her sake, he decides to leave the area.Before leaving, he tells Bella that he doesn't feel anything for her anymore.A lonely and betrayed teenager falls into depression.Only her acquaintance with a handsome Indian, Jacob Black (Taylor Lautner), helps her regain her balance.The boy falls in love with Bella, but hides his greatest secret from her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Weitz</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Alice Cullen - Ashley Greene</actor>
      <actor>Jasper Hale - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Swan - Billy Burke</actor>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260505223000 +0500" stop="20260506000500 +0500">
    <title>Sanctuary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hal Porterfield (Christopher Abbott) orders room service at a posh hotel.Rebecca Marin (Margaret Qualley) shows up at the apartment to interview him for the position of general manager of this chain of facilities.Her questions become more and more personal and lead to a surprising ending.In reality, the woman is a dominatrix who follows the script prepared by Hal.However, the relationship does not follow the script ordered by the client.The woman decides to blackmail the rich man.She claims that she recorded a compromising sex tape with him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zachary Wigon</director>
      <actor>Hal - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Hallway - Francisco Castaneda</actor>
      <actor>Woman in the Hallway - Kathie Young</actor>
      <actor>Older Phil Porterfield - Dominic Defilips</actor>
      <actor>Younger Phil Porterfield - Rene Calvo</actor>
      <actor>Hal's Mother - Danita Battle</actor>
      <actor>Young Hal - Christian Casatelli</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>