<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260429193000 +0500" stop="20260429205500 +0500">
    <title>A Carpenter Christmas Romance</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Writer Andrea returns to her family farm in Wildwood just before the holidays.She begins an affair with her ex-boyfriend Seth, who was employed in the crew renovating the town after the recent fire.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Helgren</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260429205500 +0500" stop="20260429223000 +0500">
    <title>One of Them Days</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dreux (Keke Palmer) and Alyssa (SZA) are like lovebirds, they have been friends for years and share an apartment.Their everyday lives suddenly turn upside down when they discover that Alyssa's boyfriend has squandered all their savings - money that was supposed to be used to pay the rent.The girls face a real challenge: in an atmosphere full of funny adventures, they must quickly find a way to get the missing amount and avoid eviction.It quickly turns out that they will be forced to take truly unusual actions to not only save their home, but also put their friendship to the test.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Lawrence Lamont</director>
      <actor>Dreux - Keke Palmer</actor>
      <actor>Alyssa - SZA</actor>
      <actor>Bethany - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>The Buyer - Lil Rel Howery</actor>
      <actor>Ruby - Janelle James</actor>
      <actor>Mama Ruth - Vanessa Bell Calloway</actor>
      <actor>Lucky - Katt Williams</actor>
      <actor>Maniac - Patrick Cage</actor>
      <actor>Shayla - Gabrielle Dennis</actor>
      <actor>King Lolo - Amin Joseph</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260429223000 +0500" stop="20260429232000 +0500">
    <title>Tokyo Vice 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Consequences</sub-title>
    <desc>Tokyo, 1990s.Young journalist Jake Adelstein (Ansel Elgort) must face the consequences of his actions.After he was beaten by Yakuza men, he felt that he was not untouchable.However, although he realizes that he cannot count on help from law enforcement officers or the media, and that his life and that of his loved ones are in danger, he does not intend to give up.He wants to continue investigating police corruption.The only one who helps him is his mentor and friend, former detective Hiroto Katagiri (Ken Watanabe).Perhaps, however, the journalist will also be able to count on the cooperation of Shoko Nagata (Miki Maya), a detective - like him - determined to destroy the Yakuza.The second series of an excellent series based on the reports of journalist Jake Anderson.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Josef Kubota Wladyka</director>
      <actor>Taro - Koshi Uehara</actor>
      <actor>Masahito Ohno - Takayuki Suzuki</actor>
      <actor>Paul Luthold - Jonathan Whittaker</actor>
      <actor>Jason Oki - Aoi Takeya</actor>
      <actor>Airport Patron - Jim Chad</actor>
      <actor>American Embassy Guest - David Atkinson</actor>
      <actor>Ruri - Yukina Tsuchiya</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #2 - Paula Berwanger</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #1 - Ruby Young</actor>
      <actor>FBI Agent - Steve Wiley</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260429232000 +0500" stop="20260430002000 +0500">
    <title>Tokyo Vice 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Endgame</sub-title>
    <desc>Tokyo, 1990s.Young journalist Jake Adelstein (Ansel Elgort) must face the consequences of his actions.After he was beaten by Yakuza men, he felt that he was not untouchable.However, although he realizes that he cannot count on help from law enforcement officers or the media, and that his life and that of his loved ones are in danger, he does not intend to give up.He wants to continue investigating police corruption.The only one who helps him is his mentor and friend, former detective Hiroto Katagiri (Ken Watanabe).Perhaps, however, the journalist will also be able to count on the cooperation of Shoko Nagata (Miki Maya), a detective - like him - determined to destroy the Yakuza.The second series of an excellent series based on the reports of journalist Jake Anderson.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Josef Kubota Wladyka</director>
      <actor>Taro - Koshi Uehara</actor>
      <actor>Masahito Ohno - Takayuki Suzuki</actor>
      <actor>Paul Luthold - Jonathan Whittaker</actor>
      <actor>Jason Oki - Aoi Takeya</actor>
      <actor>Airport Patron - Jim Chad</actor>
      <actor>American Embassy Guest - David Atkinson</actor>
      <actor>Ruri - Yukina Tsuchiya</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #2 - Paula Berwanger</actor>
      <actor>Waitress #1 - Ruby Young</actor>
      <actor>FBI Agent - Steve Wiley</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430002000 +0500" stop="20260430025500 +0500">
    <title>Blade Runner 2049</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The future, a world dominated by machines created to perform various dangerous tasks.Hunter Rick Deckard was tasked with tracking down and then eliminating the androids from Los Angeles three decades ago.Now the roles are reversed and he is the one who has to hide.At the same time, a new blade runner enters the game.Officer K from a special police unit tracks down humanoid robots hiding in society.When he returns home, his computer-generated companion, Joi, is always waiting for him.During the next task, the investigator comes across a shocking discovery proving that replicators can reproduce, which was previously considered impossible.Officer K's superior, Lieutenant Joshi, fears that the discovery will shock society and lead to war.So he orders the matter to be hushed up.Intrigued, K begins a private investigation.The help of the experienced Deckard turns out to be indispensable.Finding it is a difficult task in itself.Moreover, his enemies are hot on his heels.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>'K' - Ryan Gosling</actor>
      <actor>Rick Deckard - Harrison Ford</actor>
      <actor>Joi - Ana de Armas</actor>
      <actor>Luv - Sylvia Hoeks</actor>
      <actor>Lieutenant Joshi - Robin Wright</actor>
      <actor>Sapper Morton - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Interviewer - Mark Arnold</actor>
      <actor>Angry Old Lady - Vilma Szécsi</actor>
      <actor>Nandez - Wood Harris</actor>
      <actor>Coco - David Dastmalchian</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430025500 +0500" stop="20260430050500 +0500">
    <title>Mickey 17</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2050. Mickey Barnes (Robert Pattinson) takes out a loan on usurious terms.Wanting to escape from an aggressive debt collector, together with his friend Timo (Steven Yeun), he joins the crew of a spaceship that is to colonize the ice planet Niflheim.However, when the second of them becomes a shuttle pilot, Mickey - not entirely consciously - becomes the person assigned to the most dangerous tasks.When he dies, in a process called reprinting, a clone of himself is created, which retains his memories.The situation of the version of man number 17 becomes even more complicated when, contrary to expectations, he is not killed during one of the missions, and when he returns to the ship, he finds Mickey 18 there. In these circumstances, the commander of the expedition, Hieronymous Marshall (Mark Ruffalo), decides to eliminate both of them.A surprising, fast-paced and humorous picture by the Oscar-winning writer and director of "Parasite", Bong Joon Ho.The production is an adaptation of the novel by Edward Ashton.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joon-ho Bong</director>
      <actor>Mickey Barnes - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Gwen Johansen - Toni Collette</actor>
      <actor>Hieronymous Marshall - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Timo - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Nasha Adjaya - Naomi Ackie</actor>
      <actor>Kai Katz - Anamaria Vartolomei</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Cameron Britton</actor>
      <actor>Shrimp Eyes - Angus Imrie</actor>
      <actor>Preston - Daniel Henshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Fantasy Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430050500 +0500" stop="20260430064500 +0500">
    <title>La extorsión</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Experienced airline pilot Alejandro Petrossián (Guillermo Francella) does not want to retire yet, although he is approaching that age.He begins to be blackmailed by the secret services, which threaten him with revealing the bad results of his hearing tests, which would result in the immediate end of his career.Alejandro has to carry several suitcases on subsequent flights from Buenos Aires to Madrid.Although he is not allowed to ask any questions, the pilot is intrigued by the contents of the briefcases, which causes him to plunge into the world of intrigue and corruption, which endangers both the life of the man himself and his loved ones.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Martino Zaidelis</director>
      <actor>Alejandro Petrossián - Guillermo Francella</actor>
      <actor>Saavedra - Pablo Rago</actor>
      <actor>Carolina Guerrero - Andrea Frigerio</actor>
      <actor>Porchietto - Alberto Ajaka</actor>
      <actor>Fernando Marconi - Guillermo Arengo</actor>
      <actor>Mario Aldana - Carlos Portaluppi</actor>
      <actor>Rita Tirabosco - Mónica Villa</actor>
      <actor>Andrés Sadik - Juan Lo Sasso</actor>
      <actor>Cristaldo - Joselo Bella</actor>
      <actor>Beltramino - Osvaldo Djeredjian</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430064500 +0500" stop="20260430080000 +0500">
    <title>Upon Entry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Venezuelan Diego (Alberto Ammann) and Spanish Elena (Bruna Cusí) decide to move to the United States.The couple successfully passed the visa procedure and packed all their belongings.It seems that nothing will stop them from building a new life in the USA soon.At the immigration area at the New York airport, they are asked to talk.Inside the cramped interior, Diego and Elena are subjected to a thorough inspection by border officers.Routine activities turn into a grueling interrogation that lasts several hours.Secrets that they never shared with each other are revealed.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Alejandro Rojas</director>
      <director>Juan Vasquez</director>
      <actor>Diego - Alberto Ammann</actor>
      <actor>Elena - Bruna Cusí</actor>
      <actor>Agent Barrett - Ben Temple</actor>
      <actor>Agent Vásquez - Laura Gómez</actor>
      <actor>Taxista - Laura Bernis</actor>
      <actor>Policia cua - Nuris Blu</actor>
      <actor>Policia sala 1 - David Comrie</actor>
      <actor>Jove - Alicia Durán</actor>
      <actor>Gos policia - Kamyla</actor>
      <actor>Policia finestreta - Colin Morgan</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430080000 +0500" stop="20260430090000 +0500">
    <title>An Update on Our Family</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Where's Huxley?</sub-title>
    <desc>Fans and the media, concerned about Huxley's fate, are increasingly expressing their concerns, and the discussion on online forums quickly turns into a wave of criticism.Commentators analyze archival materials published by the Stauffers, paying attention to their lifestyle and the way they presented their adopted son.When the family finally makes an official statement, sponsors withdraw their cooperation and public pressure mounts.Consequently, Myka disappears from the Internet, leaving behind an avalanche of unanswered questions and unexplained controversies.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Rachel Mason</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430090000 +0500" stop="20260430102000 +0500">
    <title>A Carpenter Christmas Romance</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Writer Andrea returns to her family farm in Wildwood just before the holidays.She begins an affair with her ex-boyfriend Seth, who was employed in the crew renovating the town after the recent fire.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Helgren</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430102000 +0500" stop="20260430115500 +0500">
    <title>One of Them Days</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dreux (Keke Palmer) and Alyssa (SZA) are like lovebirds, they have been friends for years and share an apartment.Their everyday lives suddenly turn upside down when they discover that Alyssa's boyfriend has squandered all their savings - money that was supposed to be used to pay the rent.The girls face a real challenge: in an atmosphere full of funny adventures, they must quickly find a way to get the missing amount and avoid eviction.It quickly turns out that they will be forced to take truly unusual actions to not only save their home, but also put their friendship to the test.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Lawrence Lamont</director>
      <actor>Dreux - Keke Palmer</actor>
      <actor>Alyssa - SZA</actor>
      <actor>Bethany - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>The Buyer - Lil Rel Howery</actor>
      <actor>Ruby - Janelle James</actor>
      <actor>Mama Ruth - Vanessa Bell Calloway</actor>
      <actor>Lucky - Katt Williams</actor>
      <actor>Maniac - Patrick Cage</actor>
      <actor>Shayla - Gabrielle Dennis</actor>
      <actor>King Lolo - Amin Joseph</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430115500 +0500" stop="20260430131500 +0500">
    <title>The Grinch</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The only companion of the lonely and malicious Grinch is the dog Max. The green creature only leaves the cave in search of food.Meanwhile, the residents of Whosiów are eagerly awaiting a special time of the year, Christmas.Wanting to keep the peace, the Grinch plans to spoil the grand celebrations and kidnap Santa Claus.At the same time, Cindy-Lou and her friends intend to capture a Lappish benefactor to thank him for helping the girl's busy mother.Two opposing intentions will face an inevitable confrontation.Another film adaptation of the adventures of a character created by a children's book writer, Dr.Seuss.Previously, Jim Carrey played the green creature in the 2000 film "The Grinch: No Christmas."In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others:Jarosław Boberek, Lila Wassermann, Ewa Prus and Karol Kwiatkowski.The carol was performed by Katarzyna Owczarz, Małgorzata Szymańska, Adam Krylik and Krzysztof Pietrzak.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Scott Mosier</director>
      <director>Yarrow Cheney</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430131500 +0500" stop="20260430145500 +0500">
    <title>Maid in Manhattan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>New York.Divorcee Marisa Ventura (Jennifer Lopez) raises her son alone.She works as a maid at the luxurious Beresford Hotel in Manhattan.While cleaning the apartment of aristocrat Caroline Lane (Natasha Richardson), the woman tries on her elegant outfit, in which she looks exceptionally nice.Another hotel guest sees her so changed.He is lawyer Christopher Matthew (Ralph Fiennes), running for parliament.He takes Marisa as a person of a similar social status to himself.They go for a walk together and then eat dinner together.The woman cannot bring herself to correct the mistake, especially since she likes Christopher.However, it is not known how the future senator will react to the fact that his chosen one is an ordinary girl from the Bronx... The luxurious Beresford hotel, where the main character of the film works, is in fact the famous Waldorf-Astoria on Park Avenue.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Wayne Wang</director>
      <actor>Marisa Ventura - Jennifer Lopez</actor>
      <actor>Christopher 'Chris' Marshall, N.Y. Assemblyman - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Caroline Lane - Natasha Richardson</actor>
      <actor>Jerry Siegel - Stanley Tucci</actor>
      <actor>Ty Ventura - Tyler Posey</actor>
      <actor>Paula Burns - Frances Conroy</actor>
      <actor>John Bextrum, Personnel Manager - Chris Eigeman</actor>
      <actor>Rachel Hoffberg - Amy Sedaris</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Kehoe, Maid - Marissa Matrone</actor>
      <actor>Veronica Ventura - Priscilla Lopez</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430145500 +0500" stop="20260430162000 +0500">
    <title>IO</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A donkey working in a circus performs with a young artist (Sandra Drzymalska).When he regains freedom thanks to activists, his wandering begins.During his journey, he experiences joy and pain.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jerzy Skolimowski</director>
      <actor>Kasandra - Sandra Drzymalska</actor>
      <actor>Vito - Lorenzo Zurzolo</actor>
      <actor>Mateo - Mateusz Kościukiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Księżna - Isabelle Huppert</actor>
      <actor>Ziom - Tomasz Organek</actor>
      <actor>Dora - Lolita Chammah</actor>
      <actor>Kaja - Agata Sasinowska</actor>
      <actor>Dorota - Anna Rokita</actor>
      <actor>Zenek - Michał Przybysławski</actor>
      <actor>Zea - Gloria Iradukunda</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430162000 +0500" stop="20260430164500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Midterms</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), spokesman Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Christopher Morris</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430164500 +0500" stop="20260430171500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Signals</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), spokesman Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Addison</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430171500 +0500" stop="20260430184000 +0500">
    <title>The Last Showgirl</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After thirty years, dancer Shelly Gardner (Pamela Anderson) ends her career.For decades, she performed in a strip revue in Las Vegas, which was inspired by French burlesque.The stage, costumes and music are her passion, for which she sacrificed her family life and relationship with her daughter, Hannah (Billie Lourd).She shared her knowledge and experience with beginner friends Marianne (Brenda Song) and Jodie (Kiernan Shipka).One day, however, producer Eddie (Dave Bautista) announces that the show has been canceled.Devastated, Shelly must re-plan her future.A similar fate will befall her friend Annette (Jamie Lee Curtis), a dealer at an arcade.Golden Globe for Pamela Anderson.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gia Coppola</director>
      <actor>Shelly - Pamela Anderson</actor>
      <actor>Annette - Jamie Lee Curtis</actor>
      <actor>Hannah - Billie Lourd</actor>
      <actor>Jodie - Kiernan Shipka</actor>
      <actor>Mary-Anne - Brenda Song</actor>
      <actor>Eddie - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Brad - Patrick Hilgart</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430184000 +0500" stop="20260430195000 +0500">
    <title>Christmas Carole</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Carole Mackay sells holiday-themed trinkets online.Unfortunately, her success made her even more ruthless, but the upcoming Christmas is about to change everything.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ian Fitzgibbon</director>
      <actor>Carole - Suranne Jones</actor>
      <actor>Ghost of Christmas Present - Jo Brand</actor>
      <actor>Leon - Mark Benton</actor>
      <actor>Jackie - Rosie Cavaliero</actor>
      <actor>Eric Morecambe - Jonty Stephens</actor>
      <actor>Ernie Wise - Ian Ashpitel</actor>
      <actor>Bobbie - Taj Atwal</actor>
      <actor>Ghost of Christmas Yet To Come - Nish Kumar</actor>
      <actor>Ade - Alex Carter</actor>
      <actor>Rita - Kirsty Averton</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430195000 +0500" stop="20260430210500 +0500">
    <title>The Heist Before Christmas</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The brothers meet a man dressed as Santa Claus in the forest who is running away from the police after a robbery.At the same time, they meet another stranger (Timothy Spall) who claims he fell off a sleigh...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Edward Hall</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430210500 +0500" stop="20260430223000 +0500">
    <title>Gli addestratori</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A somewhat clumsy but passionate dog trainer, Pasquale Marolla (Pasquale Petrolo), dreams of opening his own training center for dogs.Unfortunately, he loses the competition and a bet with his ex-wife, Marta (Geppi Cucciari), which causes the woman to take away his beloved pet, the border collie Cecchino.To get money and prove to the woman that he is enterprising, the man advertises a summer course for dogs.He is very surprised when he discovers that, as a result of a mistake, instead of pets, several children come to him.At first he can't cope with them, but then he comes up with a clever idea.Over time, the entire group begins to form an extraordinary bond, and through laughter and shared challenges, both Pasquale and the children learn true values: friendship, respect and sensitivity.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Andrea Jublin</director>
      <actor>Pasquale Marolla - Pasquale Petrolo</actor>
      <actor>Marta Fiorini - Geppi Cucciari</actor>
      <actor>Pietro - Giovanni Vernia</actor>
      <actor>Caterina - Francesca Agostini</actor>
      <actor>Federico - Massimo De Lorenzo</actor>
      <actor>Letizia - Bianca Nappi</actor>
      <actor>Davide - Paolo Mazzarelli</actor>
      <actor>Paola - Anita Caprioli</actor>
      <actor>Corrado - Francesco Pannofino</actor>
      <actor>Elvis - Adriano Civitani</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260430223000 +0500" stop="20260501000500 +0500">
    <title>The Fountain</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three stories about man's pursuit of immortality.16th century.In the forests of South America, Spanish conquistador Tomas Creo (Hugh Jackman), head over heels in love with Queen Isabella I of Castile (Rachel Weisz), is looking for the legendary tree of life for her.The ruler wants to use them to finally solve the problem of the power struggle with a certain high-ranking cardinal.In the 20th century, scientist Tom Creo (Hugh Jackman) tries to find a cure that will save his seriously ill wife Izzi (Rachel Weisz).A man cannot come to terms with the fact that his beloved is dying.He decides to devote himself to finding a way to overcome death.Six centuries later, astronaut Tommy (Hugh Jackman) travels through space in a glass ball.He wants to reach the golden nebula, hoping to bring Izzi back to life.A science-fiction drama by Darren Aronofsky, author of "Requiem for a Dream", "Black Swan" and "The Wrestler".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Darren Aronofsky</director>
      <actor>Tomas - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Isabel - Rachel Weisz</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Lillian Guzetti - Ellen Burstyn</actor>
      <actor>Father Avila - Mark Margolis</actor>
      <actor>Grand Inquisitor Silecio - Stephen McHattie</actor>
      <actor>Lord of Xibalba - Fernando Hernandez</actor>
      <actor>Captain Ariel - Cliff Curtis</actor>
      <actor>Antonio - Sean Patrick Thomas</actor>
      <actor>Betty - Donna Murphy</actor>
      <actor>Manny - Ethan Suplee</actor>
    </credits><date>2006</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>