<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503050000 +0500" stop="20260503065000 +0500">
    <title>Forgetting Sarah Marshall</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Los Angeles.Peter Bretter is a musician.His compositions can be heard in many television productions.However, the man's real dream is to stage a puppet musical about Count Dracula, who is looking for true love.He has been living in a happy relationship with actress Sarah Marshall for six years.Peter loves the girl completely and doesn't seem to notice her flaws.And Sarah has too many of them.As the star of a popular crime series, he makes himself felt by those around him with his selfishness, lack of respect for the feelings of others and the expectation of constant adoration.One day, Bretter is abandoned by his beloved.Devastated and hurt, he cannot regain his balance for many weeks.Finally, on the advice of his brother Brian, he decides to go on vacation to a resort in Hawaii.There he hopes to recover from unhappy love.Unfortunately, on arrival he is horrified to discover that Sarah and her new partner, rocker Aldous Snow, have rented a room in the same hotel.Meanwhile, a suffering Peter attracts the attention of attractive receptionist Rachel Jansen.The woman decides to help him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Peter Bretter - Jason Segel</actor>
      <actor>Sarah Marshall - Kristen Bell</actor>
      <actor>Rachel Jansen - Mila Kunis</actor>
      <actor>Aldous Snow - Russell Brand</actor>
      <actor>Brian Bretter - Bill Hader</actor>
      <actor>Liz Bretter - Liz Cackowski</actor>
      <actor>Wyoma - Maria Thayer</actor>
      <actor>Darald - Jack McBrayer</actor>
      <actor>Kemo - Taylor Wily</actor>
      <actor>Dwayne the Bartender - Davon McDonald</actor>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503065000 +0500" stop="20260503090000 +0500">
    <title>Challengers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Tennis player Tashi Duncan (Zendaya) has had impressive success on the court in the past.Her career was ended by an injury.Today, the woman is the trainer of Art Donaldson (Mike Faist) - her partner and father of her daughter.The man is one title short of the Grand Slam, but he is struggling with injury and age, which may ruin the pair's ambitions.After a series of defeats, the player plans to take part in the Challenger tournament in New Rochelle, New York, which is to be his warm-up before the US Open and a chance to regain his form.Unexpectedly, in the finale, Art will have to face Patrick Zweig (Josh O'Connor) - his childhood friend and Tashi's ex-boyfriend.The match becomes an opportunity for all three to confront their turbulent past.The film by Italian director Luca Guadagnino, the creator of the Oscar-nominated "Those Days, Those Nights", is a combination of a sports drama and a story about a love triangle.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Luca Guadagnino</director>
      <actor>Tashi - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Patrick - Josh O'Connor</actor>
      <actor>Art - Mike Faist</actor>
      <actor>Finn Larsen - Jake Jensen</actor>
      <actor>Spectator - Faith Fay</actor>
      <actor>Lily - A.J. Lister</actor>
      <actor>US Open line Judge - Scottie DiGiacomo</actor>
      <actor>Tennis man - Sid Jarvis</actor>
      <actor>Tennis spectator - Charles Massey</actor>
      <actor>Asian Cook - Keanu Ham</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503090000 +0500" stop="20260503104500 +0500">
    <title>Tempete</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Zoe (Carmen Kassovitz) grew up surrounded by horses in her parents' (Mélanie Laurent and Pio Marmai) racing stable.This is her place on earth.He dreams of one day becoming a jockey like his father.When a new foal is born, the girl is the first to notice its potential to become a champion.The family's life changes one tragic night, when a scared mare accidentally injures Zoe.The teenager, overcome with despair, completely breaks down.Thanks to the support of her parents and the help of the stable boy (Kacey Mottet Klein), who has an extraordinary gift for communicating with horses, Zoe decides to overcome adversity and regain what seemed lost.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christian Duguay</director>
      <actor>Marie - Mélanie Laurent</actor>
      <actor>Philippe - Pio Marmai</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Carmen Kassovitz</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - Charlie Paulet</actor>
      <actor>Zoé - June Benard</actor>
      <actor>Monsieur Cooper - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Madame Cooper - Carole Bouquet</actor>
      <actor>Sébastien - Kacey Mottet Klein</actor>
      <actor>Haddid - Atmen Kelif</actor>
      <actor>Éric - Antoine Cholet</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503104500 +0500" stop="20260503124000 +0500">
    <title>Alita: Battle Angel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alita (Rosa Salazar), a cyborg girl, wakes up from a coma.It turns out that he doesn't remember who he is or where he is.Doctor Ido (Christoph Waltz) subjected her to a series of tests that revealed that she was a young woman with a unique story.Wanting to protect her, he does not reveal the truth about her past.Alita must adapt to the conditions and rules of life in Scrap City.After some time, he regains his memory thanks to the help of his friend, Hugo (Keean Johnson).Then he realizes that he has incredible fighting skills.She must use them against the power that tries to control her.The film's director is Robert Rodriguez, known from "From Dusk Till Dawn" and "Machete".The script was written by the winner of three Oscars, James Cameron, who considered making "Alita" back in the 1990s. The film was based on the manga.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Rodriguez</director>
      <actor>Alita - Rosa Salazar</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Dyson Ido - Christoph Waltz</actor>
      <actor>Chiren - Jennifer Connelly</actor>
      <actor>Vector - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Zapan - Ed Skrein</actor>
      <actor>Grewishka - Jackie Earle Haley</actor>
      <actor>Hugo - Keean Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tanji - Jorge Lendeborg Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Koyomi - Lana Condor</actor>
      <actor>Nurse Gerhad - Idara Victor</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503124000 +0500" stop="20260503140500 +0500">
    <title>The Emoji Movie</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Millions of smartphones around the world have an application for sending messages through which you can communicate your feelings and moods.This is where the city of Textopolis, where emotes live, is hidden.The task of each of them is to express a different state of mind.The exception is Minek, who can express every emotion.However, he dreams of being like others.Together with Piątek and the superhacker Matrix, they set off on a journey through the phone in search of a solution.The animated film is directed by Tony Leondis ("Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Masters").The Polish language version featured, among others: Paweł Ciołkosz, Szymon Roszak, Monika Pikuła and Katarzyna Kwiatkowska.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tony Leondis</director>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503140500 +0500" stop="20260503155000 +0500">
    <title>A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lloyd Vogel (Matthew Rhys) is in crisis.His marriage to Andrea (Susan Kelechi Watson) is not going well.His son was recently born and he can't quite cope with the role of a parent.His wife, in turn, completely lost patience with his moods.He is also stressed by his relationship with his father, Jerry (Chris Cooper).She cannot forgive him for abandoning his family in the past and leaving him alone with his sick mother.Things aren't going well at work either.An aspiring investigative journalist is given a task by his superior that is below his skills.He is to prepare a short article as part of a series about inspiring people.He comes to interview the nationally beloved children's show host, Fred Rogers (Tom Hanks).Without any enthusiasm, he meets America's favorite, who immediately surprises him with his cheerfulness.Suddenly, the roles in their relationship are reversed.While it was Lloyd who was supposed to question Rogers, it was Rogers who steered the conversation and got him to confess.A friendship develops between the men.Under the influence of meetings with Fred, Vogel rediscovers the joy of life and begins to believe that he can repair relationships with his loved ones and experience happiness.A film inspired by a true story.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Marielle Heller</director>
      <actor>Fred Rogers - Tom Hanks</actor>
      <actor>Lloyd Vogel - Matthew Rhys</actor>
      <actor>Jerry Vogel - Chris Cooper</actor>
      <actor>Andrea Vogel - Susan Kelechi Watson</actor>
      <actor>Joanne Rogers - Maryann Plunkett</actor>
      <actor>Bill Isler - Enrico Colantoni</actor>
      <actor>Dorothy - Wendy Makkena</actor>
      <actor>Lorraine - Tammy Blanchard</actor>
      <actor>Todd - Noah Harpster</actor>
      <actor>Margy - Carmen Cusack</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503155000 +0500" stop="20260503181000 +0500">
    <title>The Hobbit: The Battle of the Five Armies</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thorin Oakenshield, the hobbit Bilbo and their companions recover the treasure of Erebor, which was guarded by Smaug.The leader of a company of dwarves cannot resist wealth.He sacrifices friendship and honor to gloat over him.To make matters worse, armies of elves and humans appear at the Lonely Mountain, intending to take over some of the dwarves' gold as compensation for the losses caused by the dragon.For years, the beast ravaged the area and destroyed their settlements.Proud Thorin does not intend to give in to the demands of the newcomers.To resolve conflicts, Bilbo secretly gives the elves the archjewel.They use the treasure as an argument in negotiations with Thorin, and the hobbit becomes a traitor to the dwarves.While representatives of different races are arguing with each other and trying to force concessions, the army of their common enemy is approaching the dwarves' headquarters.In the face of danger, the conflicting parties must unite.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Gandalf - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Bilbo - Martin Freeman</actor>
      <actor>Thorin - Richard Armitage</actor>
      <actor>Balin - Ken Stott</actor>
      <actor>Dwalin - Graham McTavish</actor>
      <actor>Bifur - William Kircher</actor>
      <actor>Bofur - James Nesbitt</actor>
      <actor>Bombur - Stephen Hunter</actor>
      <actor>Fili - Dean O'Gorman</actor>
      <actor>Kili - Aidan Turner</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503181000 +0500" stop="20260503195000 +0500">
    <title>Minecraft</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Garrett (Jason Momoa), Henry (Sebastian Hansen), Natalie (Emma Myers) and Dawn (Danielle Brooks) constantly struggle with problems.The lives of these four change when a magical portal pulls them into a strange land full of cubes.The Overworld turns out to be a place where everything is possible thanks to imagination, which, however, is sometimes difficult to control.Once there, Garrett, Henry, Natalie and Dawn meet Steve (Jack Black), who was trapped on this side of the portal many years earlier.Together with him, they decide to defend the unusual land from evil creatures called piglins.For them to succeed, they will have to show courage and discover qualities that will make it easier for them to find their place in the real world later.A hit production for the whole family, inspired by the popular game.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jared Hess</director>
      <actor>Vice Principal Marlene - Jennifer Coolidge</actor>
      <actor>Garett Garrison - Jason Momoa</actor>
      <actor>Natalie - Emma Myers</actor>
      <actor>Steve - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Dawn - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Henry - Sebastian Hansen</actor>
      <actor>Malgosha - Allan Henry</actor>
      <actor>Young Steve - Bram Scott-Breheny</actor>
      <actor>Young Garrett - Moana Williams</actor>
      <actor>HR Person - Mark Wright</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Family Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503195000 +0500" stop="20260503223000 +0500">
    <title>Dune: Part Two</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After an insidious attack by the Harkonnens and the death of his father, Paul Atreides (Timothée Chalamet) and his pregnant mother, Jessica (Rebecca Ferguson), hide in the desert among the Fremen.There, a young man's feelings for Chani (Zendaya) sprout.At the same time, he matures spiritually.The leader of the wandering people, Stilgar (Javier Bardem), closely observes the only descendant of the Atreides family and becomes convinced that he is the chosen one, whose coming has been predicted for generations.However, to be accepted by the Fremen, Paul must pass the ultimate test by riding a monstrous worm.Meanwhile, Baron Vladimir Harkonnen (Stellan Skarsgard) finds out that Paul is alive.He knows he has to hurry.He decides to take control of the entire planet Arrakis.He starts launching attack after attack.A continuation of the spectacular production from 2021, which was awarded six Oscars.Both films are adaptations of the famous science fiction novel by Frank Herbert.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>Paul Atreides - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Chani - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Lady Jessica Atreides - Rebecca Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Stilgar - Javier Bardem</actor>
      <actor>Gurney Halleck - Josh Brolin</actor>
      <actor>Feyd-Rautha Harkonnen - Austin Butler</actor>
      <actor>Princess Irulan Corrino - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Glossu Rabban Harkonnen - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Emperor Shaddam IV - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Thufir Hawat - Stephen Henderson</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260503223000 +0500" stop="20260504002500 +0500">
    <title>Beautiful</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The intertwined adventures of several women who are looking for happiness and fulfillment at different stages of life.Magda (Marta Nieradkiewicz) tries to reconcile raising children and running a home with her professional ambitions.Distrustful Basia (Marta Ścisłowicz) avoids love, even though she wants it very much.Krysia (Hanna Śleszyńska), a married woman for 30 years, tries to arouse a bit of enthusiasm in the bored and apathetic Władek (Olaf Lubaszenko).Businesswoman Agata (Katarzyna Herman) is successful at work, but cannot find a common language with her daughter.Julia (Kamila Urzędowska) tries to make it in an industry that values ​​only youth and beauty.She discovers how much she will have to sacrifice.Polish remake of the German comedy "Wunderschön" from 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Katia Priwieziencew</director>
      <actor>Krystyna - Hanna Śleszyńska</actor>
      <actor>Władek - Olaf Lubaszenko</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Marta Nieradkiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Maciek - Mikołaj Roznerski</actor>
      <actor>Baśka - Marta Ścisłowicz</actor>
      <actor>Kuba - Konrad Eleryk</actor>
      <actor>Agata - Katarzyna Herman</actor>
      <actor>Julka - Kamila Urzędowska</actor>
      <actor>Klaudia - Wiktoria Bylinka</actor>
      <actor>Patryk - Hugo Tarres</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504002500 +0500" stop="20260504021500 +0500">
    <title>Babygirl</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Romy (Nicole Kidman) leads a stable and prosperous life.She manages a modern, dynamically developing company, lives in a comfortable house with her devoted husband Jacob (Antonio Banderas) and two teenage daughters.Her everyday life changes when a young intern, Samuel (Harris Dickinson), appears.Despite the age difference, Romy and Samuel begin a fiery romance.The woman begins to rediscover herself, although this decision may mean the loss of both her professional position and her family.She is faced with the decision of whether to follow her own desires, risking everything she has achieved so far.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Halina Reijn</director>
      <actor>Romy - Nicole Kidman</actor>
      <actor>Samuel - Harris Dickinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob - Antonio Banderas</actor>
      <actor>Esme - Sophie Wilde</actor>
      <actor>Isabel - Esther McGregor</actor>
      <actor>Nora - Vaughan Reilly</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Missel - Victor Slezak</actor>
      <actor>Hazel - Leslie Silva</actor>
      <actor>Hedda - Gaite Jansen</actor>
      <actor>Brack - Robert Farrior</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504021500 +0500" stop="20260504024500 +0500">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greg Russo (Steve Carell) has written a best-selling series of books, and readers identify him with his literary hero nicknamed Rooster.A famous writer comes to the university campus to support his daughter (Charly Clive) who is going through a marital crisis in a difficult moment.Her partner has just left her for a student, which everyone knows perfectly well.The situation is further complicated by scandals involving a woman who are the subject of gossip in the academic community.The father declares help, but his presence quickly reveals old conflicts and uncomfortable topics, instead of bringing the expected solution.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Lawrence</director>
      <director>Matt Tarses</director>
      <actor>Greg Russo - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Walter Mann - John C. McGinley</actor>
      <actor>Cristle - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Maximo Salas</actor>
      <actor>Spooner - Evan Jachelski</actor>
      <actor>George - Xavier Beloved</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504024500 +0500" stop="20260504051000 +0500">
    <title>The Last Duel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>France, 14th century.Marquerite de Carrouges (Jodie Comer) accuses Jacques le Gris (Adam Driver) of rape.The man was once friends with her husband, Jean (Matt Damon), from a respectable family.They shed blood together in battles, but later their paths diverged.They were divided by a fight for money and influence.Favored by Count Pierre d'Alencon (Ben Affleck), the less connected, but ambitious and educated Jacques won further honors.However, it was Jean who married a beautiful, proud and intelligent woman who also caught the attention of his companion.Now the knight must defend her and his honor.He challenges le Gris, who denies the allegations, to a duel.Not only pride and justice are at stake - if de Carrouges dies, his wife will also die.The spectacular story with stylish photos by Dariusz Wolski is based on facts.The last court duel took place in France in 1386.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Sir Jean de Carrouges - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Jacques Le Gris - Adam Driver</actor>
      <actor>Marguerite de Carrouges - Jodie Comer</actor>
      <actor>Nicole de Carrouges - Harriet Walter</actor>
      <actor>Pierre d'Alençon - Ben Affleck</actor>
      <actor>King Charles VI - Alex Lawther</actor>
      <actor>Crespin - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Herald at the Duel - William Houston</actor>
      <actor>Jean de Carrouges III - Oliver Cotton</actor>
      <actor>Carrouges' Priest - Aurélien Lorgnier</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504051000 +0500" stop="20260504070500 +0500">
    <title>Get him to the Greek</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>British rock star Aldous Snow (Russell Brand) is in crisis.His latest album turned out to be a failure, he broke up with his life partner, and the court took away his parental rights.After all this, the musician decided to use stimulants again, which he had previously given up for several years.One day, he is approached by Aaron Green (Jonah Hill), an employee of the record company that publishes his works.At the request of his boss (Sean "P. Diddy" Combs), the man is to bring Snow to an amphitheater in Los Angeles to celebrate his concert from a decade ago with another performance.It turns out that this task is not that easy.The film is a loose continuation of the 2008 comedy "Boys Cry Too."Nicholas Stoller was back behind the camera, and the controversial actor and comedian, Russell Brand, played the main role.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Aldous Snow - Russell Brand</actor>
      <actor>Jackie Q - Rose Byrne</actor>
      <actor>African Child in Video - Tyler McKinney</actor>
      <actor>Herself - Zoe Salmon</actor>
      <actor>Naples - Lino Facioli</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Lars Ulrich</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Mario López</actor>
      <actor>Herself - Pink</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Billy Bush</actor>
      <actor>Himself - Kurt Loder</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Musical Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504070500 +0500" stop="20260504090000 +0500">
    <title>Beautiful</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The intertwined adventures of several women who are looking for happiness and fulfillment at different stages of life.Magda (Marta Nieradkiewicz) tries to reconcile raising children and running a home with her professional ambitions.Distrustful Basia (Marta Ścisłowicz) avoids love, even though she wants it very much.Krysia (Hanna Śleszyńska), a married woman for 30 years, tries to arouse a bit of enthusiasm in the bored and apathetic Władek (Olaf Lubaszenko).Businesswoman Agata (Katarzyna Herman) is successful at work, but cannot find a common language with her daughter.Julia (Kamila Urzędowska) tries to make it in an industry that values ​​only youth and beauty.She discovers how much she will have to sacrifice.Polish remake of the German comedy "Wunderschön" from 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Katia Priwieziencew</director>
      <actor>Krystyna - Hanna Śleszyńska</actor>
      <actor>Władek - Olaf Lubaszenko</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Marta Nieradkiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Maciek - Mikołaj Roznerski</actor>
      <actor>Baśka - Marta Ścisłowicz</actor>
      <actor>Kuba - Konrad Eleryk</actor>
      <actor>Agata - Katarzyna Herman</actor>
      <actor>Julka - Kamila Urzędowska</actor>
      <actor>Klaudia - Wiktoria Bylinka</actor>
      <actor>Patryk - Hugo Tarres</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504090000 +0500" stop="20260504103500 +0500">
    <title>Minecraft</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Garrett (Jason Momoa), Henry (Sebastian Hansen), Natalie (Emma Myers) and Dawn (Danielle Brooks) constantly struggle with problems.The lives of these four change when a magical portal pulls them into a strange land full of cubes.The Overworld turns out to be a place where everything is possible thanks to imagination, which, however, is sometimes difficult to control.Once there, Garrett, Henry, Natalie and Dawn meet Steve (Jack Black), who was trapped on this side of the portal many years earlier.Together with him, they decide to defend the unusual land from evil creatures called piglins.For them to succeed, they will have to show courage and discover qualities that will make it easier for them to find their place in the real world later.A hit production for the whole family, inspired by the popular game.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jared Hess</director>
      <actor>Vice Principal Marlene - Jennifer Coolidge</actor>
      <actor>Garett Garrison - Jason Momoa</actor>
      <actor>Natalie - Emma Myers</actor>
      <actor>Steve - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Dawn - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Henry - Sebastian Hansen</actor>
      <actor>Malgosha - Allan Henry</actor>
      <actor>Young Steve - Bram Scott-Breheny</actor>
      <actor>Young Garrett - Moana Williams</actor>
      <actor>HR Person - Mark Wright</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Family Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504103500 +0500" stop="20260504131500 +0500">
    <title>Dune: Part Two</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After an insidious attack by the Harkonnens and the death of his father, Paul Atreides (Timothée Chalamet) and his pregnant mother, Jessica (Rebecca Ferguson), hide in the desert among the Fremen.There, a young man's feelings for Chani (Zendaya) sprout.At the same time, he matures spiritually.The leader of the wandering people, Stilgar (Javier Bardem), closely observes the only descendant of the Atreides family and becomes convinced that he is the chosen one, whose coming has been predicted for generations.However, to be accepted by the Fremen, Paul must pass the ultimate test by riding a monstrous worm.Meanwhile, Baron Vladimir Harkonnen (Stellan Skarsgard) finds out that Paul is alive.He knows he has to hurry.He decides to take control of the entire planet Arrakis.He starts launching attack after attack.A continuation of the spectacular production from 2021, which was awarded six Oscars.Both films are adaptations of the famous science fiction novel by Frank Herbert.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>Paul Atreides - Timothée Chalamet</actor>
      <actor>Chani - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Lady Jessica Atreides - Rebecca Ferguson</actor>
      <actor>Stilgar - Javier Bardem</actor>
      <actor>Gurney Halleck - Josh Brolin</actor>
      <actor>Feyd-Rautha Harkonnen - Austin Butler</actor>
      <actor>Princess Irulan Corrino - Florence Pugh</actor>
      <actor>Glossu Rabban Harkonnen - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Emperor Shaddam IV - Christopher Walken</actor>
      <actor>Thufir Hawat - Stephen Henderson</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504131500 +0500" stop="20260504150500 +0500">
    <title>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>New York teenager Miles Morales visits an abandoned subway station.There he is bitten by a radioactive spider.He soon realizes that he has gained abilities similar to those of Spider-Man.Soon, Miles witnesses the fight between Spider Man and Kingpin, the Green Goblin and the Prowler.The superhero tries to turn off the accelerator, thanks to which the first of the villains wants to gain access to parallel universes and can destroy the city.He manages to give Miles a USB drive to deactivate the device and is then killed.Miles decides to honor his memory by becoming a new superhero.First of all, he must face Kingspin and his men, who will stop at nothing to recover the USB.The film won numerous awards, including an Oscar.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rodney Rothman</director>
      <director>Peter Ramsey</director>
      <director>Bob Persichetti</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504150500 +0500" stop="20260504153500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Helsinki</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), spokesman Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Becky Martin</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504153500 +0500" stop="20260504160500 +0500">
    <title>Veep 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Andrew</sub-title>
    <desc>Further adventures of the Vice President of the United States, whose ideas about politics collide with brutal reality.Selina Meyer (Julia Louis-Dreyfus) has become familiar with her many responsibilities and is becoming more and more confident in moving around Washington.Loyal colleagues - chief of staff Amy Brookheimer (Anna Chlumsky), spokesman Mike McLintock (Matt Walsh), adviser Gary Walsh (Tony Hale) and personal assistant Sue Wilson (Sufe Bradshaw) - help her cope with the hostile environment in the White House.The series, an interesting combination of intelligent comedy and political fiction, was nominated for an Emmy in 2012.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Christopher Morris</director>
      <actor>Selina Meyer - Julia Louis-Dreyfus</actor>
      <actor>Amy Brookheimer - Anna Chlumsky</actor>
      <actor>Gary Walsh - Tony Hale</actor>
      <actor>Dan Egan - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jonah Ryan - Timothy Simons</actor>
      <actor>Mike McLintock - Matt Walsh</actor>
      <actor>Sue Wilson - Sufe Bradshaw</actor>
      <actor>Ralph Simmons  - Nathan Ferguson</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504160500 +0500" stop="20260504181000 +0500">
    <title>Queen Of The Ring</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1930s.Single mother Mildred Bliss (Emily Bett Rickards), who has always been interested in sports, dreams of becoming a wrestler.When she meets the promoter of this sport, Billy Wolfe (Josh Lucas), she decides to try her hand at this discipline, although it belongs entirely to men and the law prohibits women from entering the ring.It quickly turns out that he can cope very well, even with players who are more powerful than him.Billy becomes her manager and lover, and soon her husband.The increasingly successful woman adopts the pseudonym Mildred Burke and over time becomes the first millionaire wrestling professional.Unfortunately, her successes in the ring do not go hand in hand with a successful personal life.First of all, her marriage is not a happy one.Based on a true story about the life of women's wrestling pioneer Mildred Burke.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ash Avildsen</director>
      <actor>Mildred 'Millie' Burke - Emily Bett Rickards</actor>
      <actor>Billy Wolfe - Josh Lucas</actor>
      <actor>G. Bill - Tyler Posey</actor>
      <actor>Jack Pfefer - Walton Goggins</actor>
      <actor>Mae Young - Francesca Eastwood</actor>
      <actor>Elvira Snodgrass - Marie Avgeropoulos</actor>
      <actor>June Byers - Kailey Farmer</actor>
      <actor>Bertha - Cara Buono</actor>
      <actor>Joe Jr. - Gavin Casalegno</actor>
      <actor>Gorgeous George Wagner - Adam Demos</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504181000 +0500" stop="20260504185500 +0500">
    <title>Doc Ii.</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dr. Amy Larsen, former chief of internal medicine, is rebuilding her life after a tragic accident that left her with no memory.Now she is an intern.Her past still haunts me.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E13</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Russell Lee Fine</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504185500 +0500" stop="20260504203000 +0500">
    <title>The Glassworker</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vincent Oliver, the son of renowned glassmaker Tomasz, is preparing for his first exhibition when he finds a letter from his childhood friend, Alliz Amano, whom he has always loved.He recalls how - raised by a pacifist father - he saw her for the first time.Alliz arrives in Vincent's city, Waterfront, with her parent, Colonel Amano.They become a couple.Meanwhile, a war breaks out and both he and his rival for the girl's favor, Malik, join the army.Tomasz is forced to produce glass rectifiers for the army.Some time later, the girl's father dies without any news at the front.When Malik returns to town with him, Alliz rewards him with a kiss, which Vincent witnesses.Devastated, he sabotages the production of rectifiers, but this leads to tragedy.The anime-inspired production with an anti-war message is the first Pakistani film made using the hand-animated technique.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Usman Riaz</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504203000 +0500" stop="20260504223000 +0500">
    <title>Twilight</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seventeen-year-old Bella Swan moves in with her father, who is the sheriff of a small town.At her new school, the teenager notices Edward Cullen.The unnaturally pale boy, who has the ability to read people's minds, is an inaccessible loner.Hoping that this will scare Bella away, Edward confesses to her that he is a vampire and that he and his entire family have been feeding on animal blood for centuries.This shocking truth does not discourage a girl in love.She and Cullen become inseparable.Their love, however, is threatened by a primal predatory instinct that is increasingly difficult for the boy to control.The couple is surrounded by wanderers hungry for human blood: Laurent, James and Victoria.The lovers face them.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Catherine Hardwicke</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Swan - Billy Burke</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Carlisle Cullen - Peter Facinelli</actor>
      <actor>Esme Cullen - Elizabeth Reaser</actor>
      <actor>Rosalie Hale - Nikki Reed</actor>
      <actor>Jasper Hale - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Emmett Cullen - Kellan Lutz</actor>
      <actor>James - Cam Gigandet</actor>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260504223000 +0500" stop="20260505001000 +0500">
    <title>Your Monster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Actress Laura (Melissa Barrera) was supposed to become a star of the stage and live happily with the director of the show, Jacob (Edmund Donovan), but her beloved dumped her and took the role away.The devastated woman returns to her family home, where she spends all day in a bathrobe and crying.Her wailing gets on the nerves of the monster (Tommy Dewey), who has been living in the closet for years.The monster gives Laura two weeks to move out and threatens bloody revenge.Over time, however, an extraordinary bond develops between them, which helps Laura open her heart and follow her dreams.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Caroline Lindy</director>
      <actor>Laura Franco - Melissa Barrera</actor>
      <actor>Monster - Tommy Dewey</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Sullivan - Edmund Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Mazie Silverberg - Kayla Foster</actor>
      <actor>Jackie Dennon - Meghann Fahy</actor>
      <actor>Don McBride - Ikechukwu Ufomadu</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Megan Haley</actor>
      <actor>Will - Brandon Victor Dixon</actor>
      <actor>Scotty - Taylor Trensch</actor>
      <actor>Ellyn - Lana Young</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Black Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>