<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO3-PL">
    <display-name>HBO3</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO3-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423054500 +0500" stop="20260423073500 +0500">
    <title>Final Destination: Bloodlines</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Student Stefani (Kaitlyn Santa Juana) is plagued by nightmares about her grandparents.In their dreams, they die along with other people in the Skyview skyscraper in 1969.Although such an event never happened, the girl decides to investigate the cause of her visions.To do this, he returns to his hometown, Cloverdale.She is greeted there by her father, Marty (Tinpo Lee), and younger brother, Charlie (Teo Briones).Stefani begins searching for Iris (Brec Bassinger), the grandmother she sees in her nightmares and who has broken off contact with her family.To do this, he visits his Uncle Howard (Alex Zahara) and Aunt Brenda (April Telek).Thanks to the letters found among them, he reaches a woman (Gabrielle Rose) who is dying of cancer and lives in a remote area.She tells her that the skyscraper did not collapse only thanks to her vision and earlier intervention.At the same time, he warns that from that day on, death has haunted everyone who died in the disaster, and even the descendants of the would-be victims.As she dies, her words quickly come true.Stefani wants to save her relatives from the gruesome death that inevitably awaits them.The sixth installment of the series launched in 2000.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zach Lipovsky</director>
      <director>Adam B. Stein</director>
      <actor>Stefani Reyes - Kaitlyn Santa Juana</actor>
      <actor>Old Iris - Gabrielle Rose</actor>
      <actor>William Bludworth - Tony Todd</actor>
      <actor>Erik - Richard Harmon</actor>
      <actor>Iris Campbell - Brec Bassinger</actor>
      <actor>Paul Campbell - Max Lloyd-Jones</actor>
      <actor>Darlene Lewis - Rya Kihlstedt</actor>
      <actor>Val - Brenna Llewellyn</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Brenda - April Telek</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Lewis - Teo Briones</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423073500 +0500" stop="20260423090000 +0500">
    <title>Locke</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ivan Locke (Tom Hardy) is one of the best civil engineers in England.He has just finished working on a construction site in Birmingham and is driving to London, where he lives.Tomorrow is the most important day of his career so far, and it is related to the project of a gigantic apartment building.While traveling home, Ivan receives one phone call that completely changes his life... Tom Hardy and Steven Knight had already met during the production of the second season of the series about English gangs of the 1920s, entitled"Peaky Blinders".Hardy played the boss of a Jewish gang, Alfie Salomons, and Knight co-wrote the script.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Steven Knight</director>
      <actor>Ivan Locke - Tom Hardy</actor>
      <actor>Katrin - Ruth Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Bethan - Olivia Colman</actor>
      <actor>Gereth - Ben Daniels</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423090000 +0500" stop="20260423111500 +0500">
    <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Harry Potter spends the summer with the Dursleys in London.In the Muggle neighborhood, he and his cousin Dudley are attacked by Dementors.Soon, members of the Order of the Phoenix escort him to their organization's headquarters.Harry learns that the association was established to fight Voldemort.After the holidays, Potter returns to Hogwarts to begin his fifth year of study.A rumor begins to circulate about him that he lied and never actually met Voldemort.This time, Defense Against the Dark Arts is taught at Dolores Umbridge's school.As it turns out, the woman does not intend to practically prepare students to fight dark forces, because she believes that there is no need.Soon the teacher takes over the office of the school's grand inquisitor.Harry, sensing the approaching danger, shares his fears with Ron and Hermione.He secretly begins teaching selected colleagues Defense Against the Dark Arts.It soon turns out that he was right.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Yates</director>
      <actor>Harry Potter - Daniel Radcliffe</actor>
      <actor>Ron Weasley - Rupert Grint</actor>
      <actor>Hermione Granger - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Lord Voldemort - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Sirius Black - Gary Oldman</actor>
      <actor>Dolores Umbridge - Imelda Staunton</actor>
      <actor>Dudley Dursley - Harry Melling</actor>
      <actor>Piers - Jason Boyd</actor>
      <actor>Malcolm - Richard Macklin</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Arabella Figg - Kathryn Hunter</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423111500 +0500" stop="20260423131000 +0500">
    <title>Yesterday</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jack Malik (Himesh Patel), a supermarket employee, dreams of a musical career.Despite his efforts, he is still far from achieving the desired fame, and his songs do not impress anyone.He is supported only by his manager and closest friend, Ellie Appleton (Lily James).One morning, the day after a mysterious power outage, Jack wakes up in a completely different world - it turns out that no one remembers the Beatles.The singer quickly sees an opportunity for himself.He records the greatest hits of the cult band and presents them as his own songs.He achieves instant success and becomes a real star in the music world.Ed Sheeran himself (Ed Sheeran) wants to go on tour with him.There are also proposals for contracts with record labels, and manager Debra Hammer (Kate McKinnon) intends to establish permanent cooperation with the singer.Director Danny Boyle and screenwriter Richard Curtis were looking for an actor who could sing and play the guitar and piano for the main role.Himesh Patel was chosen because of his rendition of "USSR".Ed Sheeran stated that Himesh did an excellent job with the vocals and should consider recording an album.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Danny Boyle</director>
      <actor>Jack Malik - Himesh Patel</actor>
      <actor>Ellie Appleton - Lily James</actor>
      <actor>Carol - Sophia Di Martino</actor>
      <actor>Lucy - Ellise Chappell</actor>
      <actor>Sheila Malik - Meera Syal</actor>
      <actor>Nick - Harry Michell</actor>
      <actor>Brian - Vincent Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Rocky - Joel Fry</actor>
      <actor>Michael Kiwanuka - Michael Kiwanuka</actor>
      <actor>Young Jack - Karma Sood</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423131000 +0500" stop="20260423144500 +0500">
    <title>Karate Kid: Legends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li Fong's friend needs help.He decided to take part in a karate tournament, but his skills are insufficient.Teacher Han turns to the legendary Daniel LaRusso for help.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Li Fong - Ben Wang</actor>
      <actor>Victor Lipani - Joshua Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Mia Lipani - Sadie Stanley</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Fong - Ming-Na</actor>
      <actor>Alan - Wyatt Oleff</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Aramis Knight</actor>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Young Girl - Olivia Yang Avis</actor>
      <actor>Young Student - Aaron Wang</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423144500 +0500" stop="20260423151000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Rough Ride</sub-title>
    <desc>The further fate of Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne Johnson), a former American football star who, after ending his brilliant sports career, tries to rebuild his life.Strasmore does not want to go against his ideals and rejects the possibility of collaborating with the Anderson brothers.Together with his business partner, Joe Krutel (Rob Corddry), he decides to develop a customer relationship management company.The men also plan to make new investments.The fourth season of the series about the lives of former and current American football stars.Full of emotion and humor, the production reveals the behind-the-scenes life of representatives of one of the most popular sports disciplines in America.It shows their wealth, but also the pressure they are subjected to every day.The originator and producer of the series is Steve Levinson (HBO series "Entourage", "Boardwalk Empire").The main roles are played by, among others: action movie star Dwayne Johnson ("Bars and Cash", "The Scorpion King"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile"), winner of two Emmy Awards Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow") and John David Washington ("Malcolm X").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Julian Farino</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423151000 +0500" stop="20260423154000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Don't You Wanna Be Obama?</sub-title>
    <desc>The further fate of Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne Johnson), a former American football star who, after ending his brilliant sports career, tries to rebuild his life.Strasmore does not want to go against his ideals and rejects the possibility of collaborating with the Anderson brothers.Together with his business partner, Joe Krutel (Rob Corddry), he decides to develop a customer relationship management company.The men also plan to make new investments.The fourth season of the series about the lives of former and current American football stars.Full of emotion and humor, the production reveals the behind-the-scenes life of representatives of one of the most popular sports disciplines in America.It shows their wealth, but also the pressure they are subjected to every day.The originator and producer of the series is Steve Levinson (HBO series "Entourage", "Boardwalk Empire").The main roles are played by, among others: action movie star Dwayne Johnson ("Bars and Cash", "The Scorpion King"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile"), winner of two Emmy Awards Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow") and John David Washington ("Malcolm X").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Julian Farino</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423154000 +0500" stop="20260423173000 +0500">
    <title>Hail Mary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Popular writer Maria (Laura Weissmahr) has recently become a mother.Her days are filled with caring for her son and visiting doctors.There is virtually no time left to create.To make matters worse, the husband keeps postponing the promised paternity leave and ignores the difficulties his wife is facing.At this time, Barcelona is shaken by information about the crime committed by a young French woman who drowned her 10-month-old twins in the bathtub.Maria follows this case with increasing attention, which slowly becomes her obsession.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mar Coll</director>
      <actor>Laura Weissmahr - Laura Weissmahr</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423173000 +0500" stop="20260423195000 +0500">
    <title>War for the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The situation of the mutant monkeys changes with the appearance of a formation led by the Colonel, which seeks to take control of the apes.Meanwhile, Blue Eyes informs his father that he has found a place for their tribe to live.The decision is made to march.Under the cover of darkness, an attack occurs.Caesar's son and wife are killed.Despite the tragedy, the primate leader believes in the success of a peaceful solution.On his own, he searches for the person responsible for the massacre, but falls into the hands of the enemy.He then finds out that his compatriots were forced to work as slaves.People are attacked by a virus that reverses the process of evolution.The final showdown is inevitably approaching.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Reeves</director>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>The Colonel - Woody Harrelson</actor>
      <actor>Bad Ape - Steve Zahn</actor>
      <actor>Maurice - Karin Konoval</actor>
      <actor>Nova - Amiah Miller</actor>
      <actor>Rocket - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Red Donkey - Ty Olsson</actor>
      <actor>Luca - Michael Adamthwaite</actor>
      <actor>Koba - Toby Kebbell</actor>
      <actor>Preacher - Gabriel Chavarria</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423195000 +0500" stop="20260423221000 +0500">
    <title>Kingdom of Heaven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12th century.The young blacksmith Balian (Orlando Bloom) loses his entire family in tragic circumstances.He begins to doubt the existence of God.Then he is visited by the crusader Godfrey of Ibelin (Liam Neeson), who turns out to be his father.He suggests his son learn knightly crafts.One day, Balian kills a priest in a fight.He must escape.Together with Godfrey, he sets off for Jerusalem.On the way, his father is killed by the bishop's men.Prudent King Baldwin IV (Edward Norton) and his advisor Tiberias (Jeremy Irons) strive for peaceful solutions.Thanks to them, there are no hostilities in Jerusalem.They even manage to reach a truce with the leader of the Muslims, Saladin (Ghassan Massoud).However, the ruler's conciliatory policy does not please some greedy and fanatical crusaders.Meanwhile, Balian falls in love with the king's sister, the already married princess Sibyl (Eva Green).The girl does not love her husband, Baron Guy de Lusignan (Marton Csokas).Soon the Crusaders start a war with the Muslims.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Balian - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Sybilla - Eva Green</actor>
      <actor>Tiberias - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Godfrey z Ibelinu - Liam Neeson</actor>
      <actor>Gravedigger - Martin Hancock</actor>
      <actor>Guy de Lusignan - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Reynald de Chatillon - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Stary Strażnik - Tim Barlow</actor>
      <actor>król Baldwin IV - Edward Norton</actor>
      <actor>Saladin - Ghassan Massoud</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423221000 +0500" stop="20260423230500 +0500">
    <title>Industry</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Learned Behaviour</sub-title>
    <desc>Harper Stern (Myha'la Herrold) moves to London from a small town in upstate New York.He takes up a job at a major international bank, Pierpoint &amp; Co.She really wants to prove herself to her superiors and do better than her peers.However, he quickly comes face to face with the brutal reality.He discovers that in the fight for a job it is not only competence that counts, but also origin.People from privileged families have much greater opportunities.However, this does not take away from her enthusiasm and motivates her even more to try to get her dream job.Together with other graduates from his age group, he learns about the hierarchical realities of the industry.Young people fall into the ruthless corporate machine where no one trusts anyone and everyone, regardless of ethical issues, tries to take the place of their colleagues in a better position.
A former employee of Pierpoint Bank speaks critically of the institution.Eric decides to spend the entire day away from the office.Meanwhile, Harper unannounced joins a meeting with an important client of Eric's, who changed banks because of the service.In turn, Gus and Harper, risking their future in the bank, cross a certain line.Just after a fruitful business trip, Robert unexpectedly receives an invitation from Clement.Yasmin does not hesitate to use her contacts to arrange a meeting with an influential client.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Ed Lilly</director>
      <actor>Gus - David Jonsson</actor>
      <actor>Hari - Nabhaan Rizwan</actor>
      <actor>Harper - Myha'la Herrold</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Kilblane - Conor MacNeill</actor>
      <actor>Yasmin - Marisa Abela</actor>
      <actor>Sara Dhadwal - Priyanga Burford</actor>
      <actor>Tate Connelley - Trader - Charlotte Callaghan</actor>
      <actor>Graduate - Clemmie France Hayhurst</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Harry Lawtey</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ken Leung</actor>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423230500 +0500" stop="20260424000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Stag</sub-title>
    <desc>A continuation of the story about Tsarina Catherine (Elle Fanning), in which facts mix with satire.After the woman recently tried to kill her husband, Piotr (Nicholas Hoult), and imprisoned all his friends, the relationship between them is not good.Meanwhile, Katarzyna also faces political problems.Wanting to solve them, the ruler becomes famous also outside Russia.During this time, Piotr tries to accept the fact that he lives in his wife's shadow.He devotes himself to fatherhood, takes part in hunting and discovers culinary novelties.Finally, they both decide to take a responsible step - they decide to save their marriage.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <director>Sheree Folkson</director>
      <director>Matthew Moore</director>
      <director>Bert</director>
      <actor>Katarzyna - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Piotr - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Marial - Phoebe Fox</actor>
      <actor>Velementov - Douglas Hodge</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Elizabeth - Belinda Bromilow</actor>
      <actor>Archbishop - Adam Godley</actor>
      <actor>Georgina - Charity Wakefield</actor>
      <actor>Queen Agnes - Grace Molony</actor>
      <actor>Grigor Dymov - Gwilym Lee</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424000000 +0500" stop="20260424004500 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E8</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424004500 +0500" stop="20260424013500 +0500">
    <title>The Pitt</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">8:00 A.M</sub-title>
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Amanda Marsalis</director>
      <actor>Dr. Michael Robinavitch - Noah Wyle</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Cassie McKay - Fiona Dourif</actor>
      <actor>Dana Evans - Katherine LaNasa</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Dennis Whitaker - Gerran Howell</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Trinity Santos - Isa Briones</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Heather Collins - Tracy Ifeachor</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Melissa King - Taylor Dearden</actor>
      <actor>Mateo Diaz - Jalen Thomas Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Victoria Javadi - Shabana Azeez</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Samira Mohan - Supriya Ganesh</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424013500 +0500" stop="20260424024000 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424024000 +0500" stop="20260424031000 +0500">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greg Russo (Steve Carell) has written a best-selling series of books, and readers identify him with his literary hero nicknamed Rooster.A famous writer comes to the university campus to support his daughter (Charly Clive) who is going through a marital crisis in a difficult moment.Her partner has just left her for a student, which everyone knows perfectly well.The situation is further complicated by scandals involving a woman who are the subject of gossip in the academic community.The father declares help, but his presence quickly reveals old conflicts and uncomfortable topics, instead of bringing the expected solution.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Lawrence</director>
      <director>Matt Tarses</director>
      <actor>Greg Russo - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Walter Mann - John C. McGinley</actor>
      <actor>Cristle - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Maximo Salas</actor>
      <actor>Spooner - Evan Jachelski</actor>
      <actor>George - Xavier Beloved</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424031000 +0500" stop="20260424034500 +0500">
    <title>Comeback 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Valerie Cherish, a once popular television actress, rose to fame as a sitcom star.After many years, he wants to return to the small screen at all costs.He decides to take part in a new reality show.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Patrick King</director>
      <actor>Valerie Cherish - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Jane Benson - Laura Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mark Berman - Damian Young</actor>
      <actor>Billy Stanton - Dan Bucatinsky</actor>
      <actor>Juna Millken - Malin Akerman</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424034500 +0500" stop="20260424055500 +0500">
    <title>Kraven: The Hunter</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kraven (Aaron Taylor-Johnson), a hunter from Russia, is extremely strong and fast thanks to an extraordinary potion.He can hunt wild animals and always comes out victorious in battles with them.His life is overshadowed by his complicated relationship with his cruel father, Nikolai Kravinoff (Russell Crowe), who drags him into a spiral of revenge.Parent expects Kraven to become the greatest and most feared hunter in the world.To prove this, the young man must catch the spider-man.A slightly exaggerated, but suspenseful origin story of one of the most iconic anti-heroes of Marvel comics.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>J.C. Chandor</director>
      <actor>Sergiej Kravinoff - Aaron Taylor-Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Nikołaj Kravinoff - Russell Crowe</actor>
      <actor>Calypso Ezili - Ariana DeBose</actor>
      <actor>Dmitri Kravinoff - Fred Hechinger</actor>
      <actor>Aleksei Sytsevich - Alessandro Nivola</actor>
      <actor>The Foreigner - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Semyon Chorney - Yuri Kolokolnikov</actor>
      <actor>Young Sergei - Levi Miller</actor>
      <actor>Bert - Tom Reed</actor>
      <actor>Young Dmitri - Billy Barratt</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424055500 +0500" stop="20260424062500 +0500">
    <title>Hollywood On Set 23</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E12</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424062500 +0500" stop="20260424070500 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E8</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424070500 +0500" stop="20260424090000 +0500">
    <title>Blue Valentine</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dean grew up in a broken home.He never planned to build a lasting relationship until he met Cindy, with whom he fell in love at first sight.When, after a few weeks of dating, it turns out that the girl is expecting another man's child, she makes the difficult decision to get married.The couple tries to create a happy family, but over time they begin to face a serious crisis.The infatuation disappears, and everyday problems make it difficult for them to find understanding.Dean abuses alcohol and does simple physical work, unable to guarantee his wife real stability and support.The couple falls into conflicts more and more often.However, he still tries to rebuild his relationships for the sake of little Frankie.This perfectly portrayed study of the breakdown of a relationship was nominated for the Grand Jury Prize at the Sundance Film Festival.The role of Michelle Williams was nominated for an Oscar and a Golden Globe.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Derek Cianfrance</director>
      <actor>Dean - Ryan Gosling</actor>
      <actor>Cindy - Michelle Williams</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - John Doman</actor>
      <actor>Bobby - Mike Vogel</actor>
      <actor>Frankie - Faith Wladyka</actor>
      <actor>Marshall - Marshall Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Gramma - Jen Jones</actor>
      <actor>Glenda - Maryann Plunkett</actor>
      <actor>Jamie - James Benatti</actor>
      <actor>Jo - Barbara Troy</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424090000 +0500" stop="20260424113000 +0500">
    <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Harry Potter and his friends, Hermione and Ron, are starting their sixth year at Hogwarts.Magic school is no longer a safe place.The teaching staff is changing.Horace Slughorn becomes a potions teacher, and Severus Snape conducts Defense Against the Dark Arts classes.Meanwhile, Harry, supported by Albus Dumbledore, tries to learn about Lord Voldemort's dark past.The new professor can help with this, but he does not want to admit the mistake he made many years ago.Potter borrows a mysterious textbook that formerly belonged to the Half-Blood Prince.Thanks to the previous owner's notes there, he becomes top student in Potions classes.At the same time, he is preparing for a fight with the Dark Lord.Together with Dumbledore, he searches for horcruxes - magical objects in which Voldemort locked pieces of his soul.However, Harry does not know that his powerful enemy has a spy at Hogwarts.He was given a task by Voldemort.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Yates</director>
      <actor>Harry Potter - Daniel Radcliffe</actor>
      <actor>Ron Weasley - Rupert Grint</actor>
      <actor>Hermione Granger - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Professor Albus Dumbledore - Michael Gambon</actor>
      <actor>Professor Horace Slughorn - Jim Broadbent</actor>
      <actor>Lord Voldemort - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Severus Snape - Alan Rickman</actor>
      <actor>Fenrir Greyback - Dave Legeno</actor>
      <actor>Waitress - Elarica Gallacher</actor>
      <actor>Lily Potter - Geraldine Somerville</actor>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424113000 +0500" stop="20260424132500 +0500">
    <title>Passengers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A group of people set off on a spaceship to a planet intended for colonization in a distant galaxy.Since the journey is expected to last 120 years, the expedition participants are put into hibernation.Unfortunately, the system turns out to be unreliable and mechanic Jim wakes up early.Because he feels lonely, he decides to find a companion.His choice falls on the charming writer Aurora.He wakes her up from sleep.They fall in love, but the idyll does not last long.They discover that the spaceship they are traveling on is in great danger, and the lives of other passengers depend only on them.They also gradually realize why their waking up was not accidental.Soon the couple's love is put to a difficult test.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Morten Tyldum</director>
      <actor>Aurora Lane - Jennifer Lawrence</actor>
      <actor>Jim Preston - Chris Pratt</actor>
      <actor>Arthur - Michael Sheen</actor>
      <actor>Gus Mancuso - Laurence Fishburne</actor>
      <actor>Captain Norris - Andy Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Executive Officer - Vince Foster</actor>
      <actor>Communications Officer - Kara Flowers</actor>
      <actor>Crew Member - Conor Brophy</actor>
      <actor>Instructor - Julee Cerda</actor>
      <actor>Best Friend - Aurora Perrineau</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Dramat Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424132500 +0500" stop="20260424151500 +0500">
    <title>The Front Runner</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Senator Gary Hart (Hugh Jackman) is extremely popular, especially among younger voters.In 1988, he decided to run for the presidency of the United States for the second time.He is considered by many to be the favorite.However, unexpectedly, his extramarital relationship with Donna Rice (Sara Paxton) comes to light.The media is publicizing this case, and Hart's career is in question... The director and screenwriter of the film, Jason Reitman, was nominated for the Festival Award at the Toronto International Film Festival.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jason Reitman</director>
      <actor>Gary Hart - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Lee Hart - Vera Farmiga</actor>
      <actor>Bill Dixon - J.K. Simmons</actor>
      <actor>Ben Bradlee - Alfred Molina</actor>
      <actor>Irene Kelly - Molly Ephraim</actor>
      <actor>Billy Shore - Mark O'Brien</actor>
      <actor>Kevin Sweeney - Chris Coy</actor>
      <actor>Mike Stratton - Alex Karpovsky</actor>
      <actor>Doug Wilson - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>John Emerson - Tommy Dewey</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424151500 +0500" stop="20260424154000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">This Is Not Our World</sub-title>
    <desc>The further fate of Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne Johnson), a former American football star who, after ending his brilliant sports career, tries to rebuild his life.Strasmore does not want to go against his ideals and rejects the possibility of collaborating with the Anderson brothers.Together with his business partner, Joe Krutel (Rob Corddry), he decides to develop a customer relationship management company.The men also plan to make new investments.The fourth season of the series about the lives of former and current American football stars.Full of emotion and humor, the production reveals the behind-the-scenes life of representatives of one of the most popular sports disciplines in America.It shows their wealth, but also the pressure they are subjected to every day.The originator and producer of the series is Steve Levinson (HBO series "Entourage", "Boardwalk Empire").The main roles are played by, among others: action movie star Dwayne Johnson ("Bars and Cash", "The Scorpion King"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile"), winner of two Emmy Awards Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow") and John David Washington ("Malcolm X").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Julian Farino</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424154000 +0500" stop="20260424160500 +0500">
    <title>Ballers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Forgiving Is Living</sub-title>
    <desc>The further fate of Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne Johnson), a former American football star who, after ending his brilliant sports career, tries to rebuild his life.Strasmore does not want to go against his ideals and rejects the possibility of collaborating with the Anderson brothers.Together with his business partner, Joe Krutel (Rob Corddry), he decides to develop a customer relationship management company.The men also plan to make new investments.The fourth season of the series about the lives of former and current American football stars.Full of emotion and humor, the production reveals the behind-the-scenes life of representatives of one of the most popular sports disciplines in America.It shows their wealth, but also the pressure they are subjected to every day.The originator and producer of the series is Steve Levinson (HBO series "Entourage", "Boardwalk Empire").The main roles are played by, among others: action movie star Dwayne Johnson ("Bars and Cash", "The Scorpion King"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile"), winner of two Emmy Awards Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow") and John David Washington ("Malcolm X").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Rob Weiss</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424160500 +0500" stop="20260424175000 +0500">
    <title>Jojo Rabbit</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Set in Germany during World War II, the story of Jojo (Roman Griffin Davis), a member of the Hitler Youth.His best friend is an imaginary friend - Adolf Hitler (Taika Waititi).The boy asks him for advice on key issues, such as how to be the best little Nazi or how to recognize a Jew.One day, Jojo discovers that a Jewish teenager (Thomasin McKenzie) is hiding in his house with the consent of his single mother (Scarlett Johansson).His world turns upside down, and his current views clash with his sympathy for the girl he just met.A moving but also funny story about a young German coming of age during the Holocaust.The director, screenwriter and actor of the role of Hitler is Taika Waititi.The film won an Oscar in the best adapted screenplay category.He also received five nominations for this prestigious award.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Taika Waititi</director>
      <actor>Jojo - Roman Griffin Davis</actor>
      <actor>Elsa - Thomasin McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Rosie - Scarlett Johansson</actor>
      <actor>Adolf - Taika Waititi</actor>
      <actor>Captain Klenzendorf - Sam Rockwell</actor>
      <actor>Fraulein Rahm - Rebel Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Finkel - Alfie Allen</actor>
      <actor>Deertz - Stephen Merchant</actor>
      <actor>Yorki - Archie Yates</actor>
      <actor>Christoph - Luke Brandon Field</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424175000 +0500" stop="20260424195000 +0500">
    <title>Spider-Man</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Peter Parker (Tobey Maguire) is an ordinary young New Yorker.Shy, a bit clumsy, he has been secretly in love with the charming Mary Jane Watson (Kirsten Dunst) for a long time.While exploring the laboratory, he is bitten by a mutated, radioactive spider.Since then, his life changes - he becomes a superhero.He is strong, fit and enduring, and his eyesight is improving.In addition, there are extraordinary abilities - climbing walls, jumping from heights, weaving spider webs.When his beloved uncle, Ben Parker (Cliff Robertson), is murdered by a burglar, Peter decides to avenge him.Using his supernatural abilities, he begins to fight the world of evil.His main enemy soon becomes the dangerous Green Goblin (Willem Dafoe).Adaptation of a popular comic book.One of the biggest box office successes in cinema history.The film received two Oscar nominations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sam Raimi</director>
      <actor>Spider-Man - Tobey Maguire</actor>
      <actor>Green Goblin - Willem Dafoe</actor>
      <actor>Mary Jane Watson - Kirsten Dunst</actor>
      <actor>Harry Osborn - James Franco</actor>
      <actor>Ben Parker - Cliff Robertson</actor>
      <actor>May Parker - Rosemary Harris</actor>
      <actor>J. Jonah Jameson - J.K. Simmons</actor>
      <actor>Flash Thompson - Joe Manganiello</actor>
      <actor>Maximilian Fargas - Gerry Becker</actor>
      <actor>Joseph 'Robbie' Robertson - Bill Nunn</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424195000 +0500" stop="20260424204000 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E8</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424204000 +0500" stop="20260424222000 +0500">
    <title>Avenue of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>California.For years, 74-year-old Herbert Heller hid from his family his traumatic experiences during World War II and his stay in the Auschwitz-Birkenau camp, where he was sent at the age of twelve, and three years later he attempted to escape.All this changes when he meets Abbey (Fisher), rejected by his peers, whose own difficult experiences prompt him to open up.A moving, healing friendship develops between a man and a teenager.The story is based on the true memories of Herbert Heller, a former concentration camp prisoner who settled in the USA after the war.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Finn Taylor</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424222000 +0500" stop="20260424231000 +0500">
    <title>Industry</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Nutcracker</sub-title>
    <desc>Harper Stern (Myha'la Herrold) moves to London from a small town in upstate New York.He takes up a job at a major international bank, Pierpoint &amp; Co.She really wants to prove herself to her superiors and do better than her peers.However, he quickly comes face to face with the brutal reality.He discovers that in the fight for a job it is not only competence that counts, but also origin.People from privileged families have much greater opportunities.However, this does not take away from her enthusiasm and motivates her even more to try to get her dream job.Together with other graduates from his age group, he learns about the hierarchical realities of the industry.Young people fall into the ruthless corporate machine where no one trusts anyone, and everyone, regardless of ethical issues, tries to take the place of their colleagues in a better position.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tinge Krishnan</director>
      <actor>Gus - David Jonsson</actor>
      <actor>Hari - Nabhaan Rizwan</actor>
      <actor>Harper - Myha'la Herrold</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Kilblane - Conor MacNeill</actor>
      <actor>Yasmin - Marisa Abela</actor>
      <actor>Sara Dhadwal - Priyanga Burford</actor>
      <actor>Tate Connelley - Trader - Charlotte Callaghan</actor>
      <actor>Graduate - Clemmie France Hayhurst</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Harry Lawtey</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ken Leung</actor>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260424231000 +0500" stop="20260425000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Sweden</sub-title>
    <desc>A continuation of the story about Tsarina Catherine (Elle Fanning), in which facts mix with satire.After the woman recently tried to kill her husband, Piotr (Nicholas Hoult), and imprisoned all his friends, the relationship between them is not good.Meanwhile, Katarzyna also faces political problems.Wanting to solve them, the ruler becomes famous also outside Russia.During this time, Piotr tries to accept the fact that he lives in his wife's shadow.He devotes himself to fatherhood, takes part in hunting and discovers culinary novelties.Finally, they both decide to take a responsible step - they decide to save their marriage
On Archie's orders, Pugachev incites the crowds against Catherine.The rebellion is made to appear to have been inspired by Peter.Cities are burning and people are destroying dolls representing the Tsarina.While Archie reveals to Marial his plan to drive Catherine to desperation, the ruler and Elizabeth guess that Pugachev has a mysterious employer.Meanwhile, Hugo manipulates Peter.She encourages him to prove that, like his father, he is gifted as a military strategist.The young ruler, without his wife's knowledge, decides to attack Sweden.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <director>Jaffar Mahmood</director>
      <director>Matthew Moore</director>
      <director>Bert</director>
      <actor>Katarzyna - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Piotr - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Marial - Phoebe Fox</actor>
      <actor>Velementov - Douglas Hodge</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Elizabeth - Belinda Bromilow</actor>
      <actor>Archbishop - Adam Godley</actor>
      <actor>Georgina - Charity Wakefield</actor>
      <actor>Queen Agnes - Grace Molony</actor>
      <actor>Grigor Dymov - Gwilym Lee</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>