<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO3-PL">
    <display-name>HBO3</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO3-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422041500 +0500" stop="20260422055500 +0500">
    <title>I Know What You Did Last Summer</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Southport, a fishing community in North Carolina.Four friends - Helen, her boyfriend Barry, Julie and Ray - are driving home from celebrating the Fourth of July.Suddenly, a figure in a fisherman's cape appears on the road.Barry, who is under the influence of alcohol, hits the brake too late.The young people decide not to notify the police about the accident and throw the body into the water.Their plans are not changed even by the fact that the victim shows faint signs of life.After returning home, they cannot recover.Julie becomes depressed.A year after the tragic events, the girl receives a blood-curdling anonymous letter.It reads: "I know what you did last summer."Soon the nightmare begins.A box office hit of horror cinema, which turned out to be a career ticket for the actors playing the main roles.A slasher based on the 1973 novel, written by Kevin Williamson, who proved his ability to scare by writing the script for "Scream".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jim Gillespie</director>
      <actor>Julie James - Jennifer Love Hewitt</actor>
      <actor>Helen Shivers - Sarah Michelle Gellar</actor>
      <actor>Barry William Cox - Ryan Phillippe</actor>
      <actor>Ray Bronson - Freddie Prinze Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Elsa Shivers - Bridgette Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Melissa 'Missy' Egan - Anne Heche</actor>
      <actor>Max Neurick - Johnny Galecki</actor>
      <actor>Benjamin Willis - Muse Watson</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Cox - Mary McMillan</actor>
      <actor>Officer - Stuart Greer</actor>
    </credits><date>1997</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422055500 +0500" stop="20260422064000 +0500">
    <title>Heated Rivalry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two ice hockey players, Shane Hollander (Hudson Williams) and Ilya Rozanov (Connor Storrie), are united not only by ambition and the need for competition, but also by a magnetic attraction that neither of them fully understands.What begins as a secret romance between two debutants turns into an extraordinary love journey.Athletes spend eight years chasing fame on the ice while trying to deal with their feelings off it.They must decide whether there is room for something as fragile as love in a world of brutal competition.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Jacob Tierney</director>
      <actor>Shane Hollander - Hudson Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ilya Rozanov - Connor Storrie</actor>
      <actor>Scott Hunter - François Arnaud</actor>
      <actor>Yuna Hollander - Christina Chang</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Marleau - Franco Lo Presti</actor>
      <actor>Hayden Pike - Callan Potter</actor>
      <actor>Svetlana - Ksenia Daniela Kharlamova</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #2 - Shaun Starr</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #1 - Conor McKenna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422064000 +0500" stop="20260422083500 +0500">
    <title>The Forgiven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Wealthy Londoners David (Ralph Fiennes) and Jo (Jessica Chastain) Henninger, whose marriage is in serious crisis, go to Morocco for the weekend, where they are to attend a lavish party hosted by an old friend.A man driving very fast and under the influence of alcohol fatally hits a teenager in the desert.The couple takes the body to a friend's house, where they try to cover up the incident in cooperation with the local police.However, soon the boy's father appears in the villa, demanding not only the body, but also justice.There is a violent clash of cultures, after which David will have to face the consequences of his actions.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John Michael McDonagh</director>
      <actor>Jo Henninger - Jessica Chastain</actor>
      <actor>David Henninger - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Cody - Abbey Lee</actor>
      <actor>Richard Galloway - Matt Smith</actor>
      <actor>Dally Margolis - Caleb Landry Jones</actor>
      <actor>Tom Day - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Isabelle - Marie-Josée Croze</actor>
      <actor>Lord Swanthorne - Alex Jennings</actor>
      <actor>Anouar - Said Taghmaoui</actor>
      <actor>Maisy Joyce - Fiona O'Shaughnessy</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422083500 +0500" stop="20260422090000 +0500">
    <title>Hollywood On Set 23</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E10</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422090000 +0500" stop="20260422113500 +0500">
    <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Harry Potter begins his fourth year at the School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.The Triwizard Tournament is also approaching, with representatives of the three most prestigious universities taking part: Hogwarts, Beauxbatons and Durmstrang.The Goblet of Fire predicts the players.Harry Potter is also one of the lucky ones, even though he has not reached the required age.The young wizard's friends, Hermione and Ron, sense that there is some trick behind it.Regardless of the suspicions, the boy must face three competition tasks.In addition, he must also face his greatest enemy - Lord Voldemort.The fourth volume of the popular series of novels by J.K.Rowling was successfully brought to the screen by Mike Newell, the creator of the hits "Four Weddings and a Funeral" and "Donnie Brasco".The film received, among others:Oscar nomination for scenography.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Newell</director>
      <actor>Harry Potter - Daniel Radcliffe</actor>
      <actor>Ron Weasley - Rupert Grint</actor>
      <actor>Hermione Granger - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Rubeus Hagrid - Robbie Coltrane</actor>
      <actor>lord Voldemort - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Frank Bryce - Eric Sykes</actor>
      <actor>Wormtail - Timothy Spall</actor>
      <actor>Barty Crouch Junior - David Tennant</actor>
      <actor>Fleur Delacour - Clémence Poésy</actor>
      <actor>Arthur Weasley - Mark Williams</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422113500 +0500" stop="20260422120500 +0500">
    <title>Dawn of the Dragon Racers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The dragon riders are preparing for the next showdown.At Dragon Academy, Snotlout launches sheep into the air.However, the animals end up in various places in the village, disturbing its inhabitants in their daily activities.On Stoick's orders, the young trainers chase them around the island on the backs of their dragons.The activity quickly turns into a competition.Finally, a race is organized with the participation of fluffy creatures that are released from the pastures especially for this occasion.The competition becomes the new official sport for equestrians.In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others:Grzegorz Drojewski, Artur Pontek, Sebastian Cybulski and Julia Kołakowska-Bytner.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Elaine Bogan</director>
      <director>John Sanford</director>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422120500 +0500" stop="20260422145000 +0500">
    <title>Billy Elliot: The Musical Live</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>England, mid-1980s.Eleven-year-old orphaned by his mother, Billy (Elliott Hanna) lives in a mining town.When a strike breaks out at the mine, his older brother Tony (Chris Grahamson) and their father (Deka Walmsley) participate in the demonstrations.At the same time, the older man, convinced that Billy, like him and Tony, will become a miner, also in accordance with the family tradition, signs him up for boxing training.The boy doesn't feel like fighting, but he discovers that classical dance lessons are held in the same building.He is encouraged to participate by his friend, Debbie (Demi Lee), the daughter of Mrs. Wilkinson (Ruthie Henshall), who runs the classes.The woman quickly notices that Billy has great talent, and he finds great pleasure in training ballet.However, the problem is the boy's father.When he learns about Billy's passion, he goes crazy.A musical adapted to the screen, which was in turn based on the famous film by Stephen Daldry from 2000.The play, with music by Elton John and libretto by Lee Hall, premiered at the Victoria Palace Theater in the West End.Then it was exhibited with great success in many countries.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Brett Sullivan</director>
      <director>Stephen Daldry</director>
      <actor>Billy - Elliott Hanna</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Wilkinson - Ruthie Henshall</actor>
      <actor>Dad - Deka Walmsley</actor>
      <actor>Grandma - Ann Emery</actor>
      <actor>Tony - Chris Grahamson</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Ollie Jochim</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Bradley Perret</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Matteo Zecca</actor>
      <actor>George - Howard Crossley</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Braithwaite - David Muscat</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Musical</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422145000 +0500" stop="20260422151500 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Crackback</sub-title>
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of players of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422151500 +0500" stop="20260422155000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Yay Area</sub-title>
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of players of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422155000 +0500" stop="20260422174000 +0500">
    <title>Force of Nature: The Dry 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Australia.Federal agent Aaron Falk (Eric Bana) unsuccessfully tries to extort information from Alice Russell (Anna Torv) regarding money laundering at her company.The next day, the woman goes on a team-building trip with her colleagues, including:boss Jill Bailey (Deborra-Lee Furness), childhood friend Lauren (Robin McLeavy) and sisters Brianna (Lucy Ansell) and Bethany (Sisi Stringer).Three days later, he calls a policeman, but the call quickly ends.Soon, Aaron's friend, agent Carmen Cooper (Jacqueline McKenzie), informs him that the woman's companions returned from the trip injured and she is missing.They both go to one of the regions of the Australian Alps to take part in the search.They also interrogate the other participants of the expedition, but their testimonies do not coincide.Moreover, it turns out that these people have a lot on their conscience.A continuation of the 2020 crime story, in which Eric Bana also played the role of Agent Falk.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Connolly</director>
      <actor>Falk - Eric Bana</actor>
      <actor>Alice - Anna Torv</actor>
      <actor>Jill Bailey - Deborra-Lee Furness</actor>
      <actor>Lauren - Robin McLeavy</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Sisi Stringer</actor>
      <actor>Bree - Lucy Ansell</actor>
      <actor>Carmen - Jacqueline McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Eric Falk - Jeremy Lindsay Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Daniel Bailey - Richard Roxburgh</actor>
      <actor>Ian Chase - Tony Briggs</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422174000 +0500" stop="20260422181000 +0500">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greg Russo (Steve Carell) has written a best-selling series of books, and readers identify him with his literary hero nicknamed Rooster.A famous writer comes to the university campus to support his daughter (Charly Clive) who is going through a marital crisis in a difficult moment.Her partner has just left her for a student, which everyone knows perfectly well.The situation is further complicated by scandals involving a woman who are the subject of gossip in the academic community.The father declares help, but his presence quickly reveals old conflicts and uncomfortable topics, instead of bringing the expected solution.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Lawrence</director>
      <director>Matt Tarses</director>
      <actor>Greg Russo - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Walter Mann - John C. McGinley</actor>
      <actor>Cristle - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Maximo Salas</actor>
      <actor>Spooner - Evan Jachelski</actor>
      <actor>George - Xavier Beloved</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422181000 +0500" stop="20260422184500 +0500">
    <title>Comeback 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Valerie Cherish, a once popular television actress, rose to fame as a sitcom star.After many years, he wants to return to the small screen at all costs.He decides to take part in a new reality show.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Patrick King</director>
      <actor>Valerie Cherish - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Jane Benson - Laura Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mark Berman - Damian Young</actor>
      <actor>Billy Stanton - Dan Bucatinsky</actor>
      <actor>Juna Millken - Malin Akerman</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422184500 +0500" stop="20260422205000 +0500">
    <title>Dawn of the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ten years have passed since a virus wiped out almost the entire human race.The metropolises were deserted and civilization came to an end.Another intelligent species took over the world - genetically modified monkeys.They create their own world with a specific hierarchy.Caesar, a human-raised male who led the apes to revolution, is the leader of the pack.He was one of the few who experienced both evil and good from people.He hadn't seen a human for two years and thought the species was extinct.However, he is wrong.One day it turns out that in the ruins of San Francisco there lives a colony of people immune to the virus, led by a former policeman.Confrontation between both sides is inevitable.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Reeves</director>
      <actor>Dreyfus - Gary Oldman</actor>
      <actor>Malcolm - Jason Clarke</actor>
      <actor>Ellie - Keri Russell</actor>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>Koba - Toby Kebbell</actor>
      <actor>Alexander - Kodi Smit-McPhee</actor>
      <actor>Carver - Kirk Acevedo</actor>
      <actor>Blue Eyes - Nick Thurston</actor>
      <actor>Rocket - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Maurice - Karin Konoval</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422205000 +0500" stop="20260422221500 +0500">
    <title>Locke</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ivan Locke (Tom Hardy) is one of the best civil engineers in England.He has just finished working on a construction site in Birmingham and is driving to London, where he lives.Tomorrow is the most important day of his career so far, and it is related to the project of a gigantic apartment building.While traveling home, Ivan receives one phone call that completely changes his life... Tom Hardy and Steven Knight had already met during the production of the second season of the series about English gangs of the 1920s, entitled"Peaky Blinders".Hardy played the boss of a Jewish gang, Alfie Salomons, and Knight co-wrote the script.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Steven Knight</director>
      <actor>Ivan Locke - Tom Hardy</actor>
      <actor>Katrin - Ruth Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Bethan - Olivia Colman</actor>
      <actor>Gereth - Ben Daniels</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422221500 +0500" stop="20260422230500 +0500">
    <title>Industry</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Sesh</sub-title>
    <desc>Harper Stern (Myha'la Herrold) moves to London from a small town in upstate New York.He takes up a job at a major international bank, Pierpoint &amp; Co.She really wants to prove herself to her superiors and do better than her peers.However, he quickly comes face to face with the brutal reality.He discovers that in the fight for a job it is not only competence that counts, but also origin.People from privileged families have much greater opportunities.However, this does not take away from her enthusiasm and motivates her even more to try to get her dream job.Together with other graduates from his age group, he learns about the hierarchical realities of the industry.Young people fall into the ruthless corporate machine where no one trusts anyone, and everyone, regardless of ethical issues, tries to take the place of their colleagues in a better position.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Ed Lilly</director>
      <actor>Gus - David Jonsson</actor>
      <actor>Hari - Nabhaan Rizwan</actor>
      <actor>Harper - Myha'la Herrold</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Kilblane - Conor MacNeill</actor>
      <actor>Yasmin - Marisa Abela</actor>
      <actor>Sara Dhadwal - Priyanga Burford</actor>
      <actor>Tate Connelley - Trader - Charlotte Callaghan</actor>
      <actor>Graduate - Clemmie France Hayhurst</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Harry Lawtey</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ken Leung</actor>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260422230500 +0500" stop="20260423000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">You the People</sub-title>
    <desc>A continuation of the story about Tsarina Catherine (Elle Fanning), in which facts mix with satire.After the woman recently tried to kill her husband, Piotr (Nicholas Hoult), and imprisoned all his friends, the relationship between them is not good.Meanwhile, Katarzyna also faces political problems.Wanting to solve them, the ruler becomes famous also outside Russia.During this time, Piotr tries to accept the fact that he lives in his wife's shadow.He devotes himself to fatherhood, takes part in hunting and discovers culinary novelties.Finally, they both decide to take a responsible step - they decide to save their marriage.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <director>Sheree Folkson</director>
      <director>Matthew Moore</director>
      <director>Bert</director>
      <actor>Katarzyna - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Piotr - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Marial - Phoebe Fox</actor>
      <actor>Velementov - Douglas Hodge</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Elizabeth - Belinda Bromilow</actor>
      <actor>Archbishop - Adam Godley</actor>
      <actor>Georgina - Charity Wakefield</actor>
      <actor>Queen Agnes - Grace Molony</actor>
      <actor>Grigor Dymov - Gwilym Lee</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423000000 +0500" stop="20260423001500 +0500">
    <title>Georgie \u0026 Mandy'S First Marriage Ii. Ep. 01</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The 6:10 To Lubbock</sub-title>
    <desc>1990s.Young married couple Georgie Cooper (Montana Jordan) and Mandy McAllister (Emily Osment) living in Texas are taking care of their several-month-old daughter CeeCee.The couple lives with the woman's parents, Audrey (Rachel Bay Jones) and Jim (Will Sasso), and her younger brother Connor (Dougie Baldwin).Every day, young parents face the challenges of adulthood, relationship life and parenthood.The third television series in the series "The Big Bang Theory", a direct continuation of "Young Sheldon".</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Mark Cendrowski</director>
      <actor>Ruben - Jessie Prez</actor>
      <actor>Roy - Dale E. Turner</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Zoe Perry</actor>
      <actor>Meemaw - Annie Potts</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Casey Wilson</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423001500 +0500" stop="20260423004000 +0500">
    <title>Georgie \u0026 Mandy's First Marriage</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Some New York Nonsense</sub-title>
    <desc>1990s.Young married couple Georgie Cooper (Montana Jordan) and Mandy McAllister (Emily Osment) living in Texas are taking care of their several-month-old daughter CeeCee.The couple lives with the woman's parents, Audrey (Rachel Bay Jones) and Jim (Will Sasso), and her younger brother Connor (Dougie Baldwin).Every day, young parents face the challenges of adulthood, relationship life and parenthood.The third television series in the series "The Big Bang Theory", a direct continuation of "Young Sheldon".</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Mark Cendrowski</director>
      <actor>Georgie Cooper - Montana Jordan</actor>
      <actor>Mandy McAllister - Emily Osment</actor>
      <actor>Audrey McAllister - Rachel Bay Jones</actor>
      <actor>Jim McAllister - Will Sasso</actor>
      <actor>Connor McAllister - Dougie Baldwin</actor>
      <actor>Ruben - Jessie Prez</actor>
      <actor>Roy - Dale E. Turner</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Zoe Perry</actor>
      <actor>Meemaw - Annie Potts</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Casey Wilson</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423004000 +0500" stop="20260423012500 +0500">
    <title>Doc Ii.</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dr. Amy Larsen, former chief of internal medicine, is rebuilding her life after a tragic accident that left her with no memory.Now she is an intern.Her past still haunts me.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E12</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Russell Lee Fine</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423012500 +0500" stop="20260423031000 +0500">
    <title>Trap</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Philadelphia firefighter Cooper Abbott (Josh Hartnett) takes his teenage daughter, Riley (Ariel Donoghue), to a concert by a pop star named Lady Raven (Saleka Shyamalan) as a reward for her good grades.He notes that there are a large number of police officers on site, guarding the exits, installing cameras and checking some of the men.When the concert starts, she leaves her daughter there to find out what's going on.He learns from the newly met Jamie (Jonathan Langdon), who is in charge of the event, that the services have information that a serial killer known as the Butcher is present at the event and they plan to catch him.Upon learning of this, Cooper goes to the toilet to check the reading from the camera in his basement on his phone.It shows his future victim, Spencer (Mark Bacolcol), tied up and calling for help.When Abbott finds out that the man has not escaped, he starts looking for a way to avoid falling into the hands of the police.Meanwhile, more units of officers, even SWAT, arrive at the scene, which causes even greater nervousness of the Butcher's true face under the mask of super-dad.The film was directed by the 2000 Oscar-nominated creator of the cult "The Sixth Sense".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>M. Night Shyamalan</director>
      <actor>Cooper - Josh Hartnett</actor>
      <actor>Riley - Ariel Donoghue</actor>
      <actor>Lady Raven - Saleka Shyamalan</actor>
      <actor>Rachel - Alison Pill</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Josephine Grant - Hayley Mills</actor>
      <actor>Jamie - Jonathan Langdon</actor>
      <actor>Spencer - Mark Bacolcol</actor>
      <actor>Jody's Mom - Marnie McPhail</actor>
      <actor>The Thinker - Kid Cudi</actor>
      <actor>Parker Wayne - Russ</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423031000 +0500" stop="20260423050500 +0500">
    <title>30 days of darkness</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The town of Barrow, Alaska, goes dark for thirty days every year.Most residents leave their homes at this time.The safety of those who decided to stay is ensured by young sheriff Eben Olsen (Josh Hartnett).He is struggling with serious personal problems.His marriage with Stella (Melissa George) is in crisis and she wants to leave him.Soon, however, they must unite their forces and fight the vampires who attack a town cut off from the world and plunged in darkness.Hungry monsters launch a bloody hunt for people imprisoned in Barrow.Eben, Stella and a handful of survivors begin their fight for survival.They do everything to wait for the end of the polar night.Adapted from a comic book by Steve Niles and Ben Templesmith.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Slade</director>
      <actor>Marlow - Danny Huston</actor>
      <actor>Beau Brower - Mark Boone Junior</actor>
      <actor>Jake Oleson - Mark Rendall</actor>
      <actor>Denise - Amber Sainsbury</actor>
      <actor>Billy Kitka - Manu Bennett</actor>
      <actor>Iris - Megan Franich</actor>
      <actor>Doug Hertz - Joel Tobeck</actor>
      <actor>Lucy Ikos - Elizabeth Hawthorne</actor>
      <actor>Carter Davies - Nathaniel Lees</actor>
      <actor>Wilson Bulosan - Craig Hall</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423050500 +0500" stop="20260423052000 +0500">
    <title>Georgie \u0026 Mandy's First Marriage</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The 6:10 To Lubbock</sub-title>
    <desc>1990s.Young married couple Georgie Cooper (Montana Jordan) and Mandy McAllister (Emily Osment) living in Texas are taking care of their several-month-old daughter CeeCee.The couple lives with the woman's parents, Audrey (Rachel Bay Jones) and Jim (Will Sasso), and her younger brother Connor (Dougie Baldwin).Every day, young parents face the challenges of adulthood, relationship life and parenthood.The third television series in the series "The Big Bang Theory", a direct continuation of "Young Sheldon".</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Georgie Cooper - Montana Jordan</actor>
      <actor>Mandy McAllister - Emily Osment</actor>
      <actor>Audrey McAllister - Rachel Bay Jones</actor>
      <actor>Jim McAllister - Will Sasso</actor>
      <actor>Connor McAllister - Dougie Baldwin</actor>
      <actor>Ruben - Jessie Prez</actor>
      <actor>Roy - Dale E. Turner</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Zoe Perry</actor>
      <actor>Meemaw - Annie Potts</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Casey Wilson</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423052000 +0500" stop="20260423054500 +0500">
    <title>Georgie \u0026 Mandy's First Marriage</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Some New York Nonsense</sub-title>
    <desc>1990s.Young married couple Georgie Cooper (Montana Jordan) and Mandy McAllister (Emily Osment) living in Texas are taking care of their several-month-old daughter CeeCee.The couple lives with the woman's parents, Audrey (Rachel Bay Jones) and Jim (Will Sasso), and her younger brother Connor (Dougie Baldwin).Every day, young parents face the challenges of adulthood, relationship life and parenthood.The third television series in the series "The Big Bang Theory", a direct continuation of "Young Sheldon".</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Mark Cendrowski</director>
      <actor>Georgie Cooper - Montana Jordan</actor>
      <actor>Mandy McAllister - Emily Osment</actor>
      <actor>Audrey McAllister - Rachel Bay Jones</actor>
      <actor>Jim McAllister - Will Sasso</actor>
      <actor>Connor McAllister - Dougie Baldwin</actor>
      <actor>Ruben - Jessie Prez</actor>
      <actor>Roy - Dale E. Turner</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Zoe Perry</actor>
      <actor>Meemaw - Annie Potts</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Casey Wilson</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423054500 +0500" stop="20260423073500 +0500">
    <title>Final Destination: Bloodlines</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Student Stefani (Kaitlyn Santa Juana) is plagued by nightmares about her grandparents.In their dreams, they die along with other people in the Skyview skyscraper in 1969.Although such an event never happened, the girl decides to investigate the cause of her visions.To do this, he returns to his hometown, Cloverdale.She is greeted there by her father, Marty (Tinpo Lee), and younger brother, Charlie (Teo Briones).Stefani begins searching for Iris (Brec Bassinger), the grandmother she sees in her nightmares and who has broken off contact with her family.To do this, he visits his Uncle Howard (Alex Zahara) and Aunt Brenda (April Telek).Thanks to the letters found among them, he reaches a woman (Gabrielle Rose) who is dying of cancer and lives in a remote area.She tells her that the skyscraper did not collapse only thanks to her vision and earlier intervention.At the same time, he warns that from that day on, death has haunted everyone who died in the disaster, and even the descendants of the would-be victims.As she dies, her words quickly come true.Stefani wants to save her relatives from the gruesome death that inevitably awaits them.The sixth installment of the series launched in 2000.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zach Lipovsky</director>
      <director>Adam B. Stein</director>
      <actor>Stefani Reyes - Kaitlyn Santa Juana</actor>
      <actor>Old Iris - Gabrielle Rose</actor>
      <actor>William Bludworth - Tony Todd</actor>
      <actor>Erik - Richard Harmon</actor>
      <actor>Iris Campbell - Brec Bassinger</actor>
      <actor>Paul Campbell - Max Lloyd-Jones</actor>
      <actor>Darlene Lewis - Rya Kihlstedt</actor>
      <actor>Val - Brenna Llewellyn</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Brenda - April Telek</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Lewis - Teo Briones</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423073500 +0500" stop="20260423090000 +0500">
    <title>Locke</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ivan Locke (Tom Hardy) is one of the best civil engineers in England.He has just finished working on a construction site in Birmingham and is driving to London, where he lives.Tomorrow is the most important day of his career so far, and it is related to the project of a gigantic apartment building.While traveling home, Ivan receives one phone call that completely changes his life... Tom Hardy and Steven Knight had already met during the production of the second season of the series about English gangs of the 1920s, entitled"Peaky Blinders".Hardy played the boss of a Jewish gang, Alfie Salomons, and Knight co-wrote the script.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Steven Knight</director>
      <actor>Ivan Locke - Tom Hardy</actor>
      <actor>Katrin - Ruth Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Bethan - Olivia Colman</actor>
      <actor>Gereth - Ben Daniels</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423090000 +0500" stop="20260423111500 +0500">
    <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Harry Potter spends the summer with the Dursleys in London.In the Muggle neighborhood, he and his cousin Dudley are attacked by Dementors.Soon, members of the Order of the Phoenix escort him to their organization's headquarters.Harry learns that the association was established to fight Voldemort.After the holidays, Potter returns to Hogwarts to begin his fifth year of study.A rumor begins to circulate about him that he lied and never actually met Voldemort.This time, Defense Against the Dark Arts is taught at Dolores Umbridge's school.As it turns out, the woman does not intend to practically prepare students to fight dark forces, because she believes that there is no need.Soon the teacher takes over the office of the school's grand inquisitor.Harry, sensing the approaching danger, shares his fears with Ron and Hermione.He secretly begins teaching selected colleagues Defense Against the Dark Arts.It soon turns out that he was right.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Yates</director>
      <actor>Harry Potter - Daniel Radcliffe</actor>
      <actor>Ron Weasley - Rupert Grint</actor>
      <actor>Hermione Granger - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Lord Voldemort - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Sirius Black - Gary Oldman</actor>
      <actor>Dolores Umbridge - Imelda Staunton</actor>
      <actor>Dudley Dursley - Harry Melling</actor>
      <actor>Piers - Jason Boyd</actor>
      <actor>Malcolm - Richard Macklin</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Arabella Figg - Kathryn Hunter</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423111500 +0500" stop="20260423131000 +0500">
    <title>Yesterday</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jack Malik (Himesh Patel), a supermarket employee, dreams of a musical career.Despite his efforts, he is still far from achieving the desired fame, and his songs do not impress anyone.He is supported only by his manager and closest friend, Ellie Appleton (Lily James).One morning, the day after a mysterious power outage, Jack wakes up in a completely different world - it turns out that no one remembers the Beatles.The singer quickly sees an opportunity for himself.He records the greatest hits of the cult band and presents them as his own songs.He achieves instant success and becomes a real star in the music world.Ed Sheeran himself (Ed Sheeran) wants to go on tour with him.There are also proposals for contracts with record labels, and manager Debra Hammer (Kate McKinnon) intends to establish permanent cooperation with the singer.Director Danny Boyle and screenwriter Richard Curtis were looking for an actor who could sing and play the guitar and piano for the main role.Himesh Patel was chosen because of his rendition of "USSR".Ed Sheeran stated that Himesh did an excellent job with the vocals and should consider recording an album.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Danny Boyle</director>
      <actor>Jack Malik - Himesh Patel</actor>
      <actor>Ellie Appleton - Lily James</actor>
      <actor>Carol - Sophia Di Martino</actor>
      <actor>Lucy - Ellise Chappell</actor>
      <actor>Sheila Malik - Meera Syal</actor>
      <actor>Nick - Harry Michell</actor>
      <actor>Brian - Vincent Franklin</actor>
      <actor>Rocky - Joel Fry</actor>
      <actor>Michael Kiwanuka - Michael Kiwanuka</actor>
      <actor>Young Jack - Karma Sood</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423131000 +0500" stop="20260423144500 +0500">
    <title>Karate Kid: Legends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li Fong's friend needs help.He decided to take part in a karate tournament, but his skills are insufficient.Teacher Han turns to the legendary Daniel LaRusso for help.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Li Fong - Ben Wang</actor>
      <actor>Victor Lipani - Joshua Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Mia Lipani - Sadie Stanley</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Fong - Ming-Na</actor>
      <actor>Alan - Wyatt Oleff</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Aramis Knight</actor>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Young Girl - Olivia Yang Avis</actor>
      <actor>Young Student - Aaron Wang</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423144500 +0500" stop="20260423151000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Rough Ride</sub-title>
    <desc>The further fate of Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne Johnson), a former American football star who, after ending his brilliant sports career, tries to rebuild his life.Strasmore does not want to go against his ideals and rejects the possibility of collaborating with the Anderson brothers.Together with his business partner, Joe Krutel (Rob Corddry), he decides to develop a customer relationship management company.The men also plan to make new investments.The fourth season of the series about the lives of former and current American football stars.Full of emotion and humor, the production reveals the behind-the-scenes life of representatives of one of the most popular sports disciplines in America.It shows their wealth, but also the pressure they are subjected to every day.The originator and producer of the series is Steve Levinson (HBO series "Entourage", "Boardwalk Empire").The main roles are played by, among others: action movie star Dwayne Johnson ("Bars and Cash", "The Scorpion King"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile"), winner of two Emmy Awards Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow") and John David Washington ("Malcolm X").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Julian Farino</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423151000 +0500" stop="20260423154000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Don't You Wanna Be Obama?</sub-title>
    <desc>The further fate of Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne Johnson), a former American football star who, after ending his brilliant sports career, tries to rebuild his life.Strasmore does not want to go against his ideals and rejects the possibility of collaborating with the Anderson brothers.Together with his business partner, Joe Krutel (Rob Corddry), he decides to develop a customer relationship management company.The men also plan to make new investments.The fourth season of the series about the lives of former and current American football stars.Full of emotion and humor, the production reveals the behind-the-scenes life of representatives of one of the most popular sports disciplines in America.It shows their wealth, but also the pressure they are subjected to every day.The originator and producer of the series is Steve Levinson (HBO series "Entourage", "Boardwalk Empire").The main roles are played by, among others: action movie star Dwayne Johnson ("Bars and Cash", "The Scorpion King"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile"), winner of two Emmy Awards Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow") and John David Washington ("Malcolm X").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Julian Farino</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423154000 +0500" stop="20260423173000 +0500">
    <title>Hail Mary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Popular writer Maria (Laura Weissmahr) has recently become a mother.Her days are filled with caring for her son and visiting doctors.There is virtually no time left to create.To make matters worse, the husband keeps postponing the promised paternity leave and ignores the difficulties his wife is facing.At this time, Barcelona is shaken by information about the crime committed by a young French woman who drowned her 10-month-old twins in the bathtub.Maria follows this case with increasing attention, which slowly becomes her obsession.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mar Coll</director>
      <actor>Laura Weissmahr - Laura Weissmahr</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423173000 +0500" stop="20260423195000 +0500">
    <title>War for the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The situation of the mutant monkeys changes with the appearance of a formation led by the Colonel, which seeks to take control of the apes.Meanwhile, Blue Eyes informs his father that he has found a place for their tribe to live.The decision is made to march.Under the cover of darkness, an attack occurs.Caesar's son and wife are killed.Despite the tragedy, the primate leader believes in the success of a peaceful solution.On his own, he searches for the person responsible for the massacre, but falls into the hands of the enemy.He then finds out that his compatriots were forced to work as slaves.People are attacked by a virus that reverses the process of evolution.The final showdown is inevitably approaching.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Reeves</director>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>The Colonel - Woody Harrelson</actor>
      <actor>Bad Ape - Steve Zahn</actor>
      <actor>Maurice - Karin Konoval</actor>
      <actor>Nova - Amiah Miller</actor>
      <actor>Rocket - Terry Notary</actor>
      <actor>Red Donkey - Ty Olsson</actor>
      <actor>Luca - Michael Adamthwaite</actor>
      <actor>Koba - Toby Kebbell</actor>
      <actor>Preacher - Gabriel Chavarria</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423195000 +0500" stop="20260423221000 +0500">
    <title>Kingdom of Heaven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>12th century.The young blacksmith Balian (Orlando Bloom) loses his entire family in tragic circumstances.He begins to doubt the existence of God.Then he is visited by the crusader Godfrey of Ibelin (Liam Neeson), who turns out to be his father.He suggests his son learn knightly crafts.One day, Balian kills a priest in a fight.He must escape.Together with Godfrey, he sets off for Jerusalem.On the way, his father is killed by the bishop's men.Prudent King Baldwin IV (Edward Norton) and his advisor Tiberias (Jeremy Irons) strive for peaceful solutions.Thanks to them, there are no hostilities in Jerusalem.They even manage to reach a truce with the leader of the Muslims, Saladin (Ghassan Massoud).However, the ruler's conciliatory policy does not please some greedy and fanatical crusaders.Meanwhile, Balian falls in love with the king's sister, the already married princess Sibyl (Eva Green).The girl does not love her husband, Baron Guy de Lusignan (Marton Csokas).Soon the Crusaders start a war with the Muslims.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Balian - Orlando Bloom</actor>
      <actor>Sybilla - Eva Green</actor>
      <actor>Tiberias - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Godfrey z Ibelinu - Liam Neeson</actor>
      <actor>Gravedigger - Martin Hancock</actor>
      <actor>Guy de Lusignan - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Reynald de Chatillon - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Stary Strażnik - Tim Barlow</actor>
      <actor>król Baldwin IV - Edward Norton</actor>
      <actor>Saladin - Ghassan Massoud</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423221000 +0500" stop="20260423230500 +0500">
    <title>Industry</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Learned Behaviour</sub-title>
    <desc>Harper Stern (Myha'la Herrold) moves to London from a small town in upstate New York.He takes up a job at a major international bank, Pierpoint &amp; Co.She really wants to prove herself to her superiors and do better than her peers.However, he quickly comes face to face with the brutal reality.He discovers that in the fight for a job it is not only competence that counts, but also origin.People from privileged families have much greater opportunities.However, this does not take away from her enthusiasm and motivates her even more to try to get her dream job.Together with other graduates from his age group, he learns about the hierarchical realities of the industry.Young people fall into the ruthless corporate machine where no one trusts anyone and everyone, regardless of ethical issues, tries to take the place of their colleagues in a better position.
A former employee of Pierpoint Bank speaks critically of the institution.Eric decides to spend the entire day away from the office.Meanwhile, Harper unannounced joins a meeting with an important client of Eric's, who changed banks because of the service.In turn, Gus and Harper, risking their future in the bank, cross a certain line.Just after a fruitful business trip, Robert unexpectedly receives an invitation from Clement.Yasmin does not hesitate to use her contacts to arrange a meeting with an influential client.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Ed Lilly</director>
      <actor>Gus - David Jonsson</actor>
      <actor>Hari - Nabhaan Rizwan</actor>
      <actor>Harper - Myha'la Herrold</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Kilblane - Conor MacNeill</actor>
      <actor>Yasmin - Marisa Abela</actor>
      <actor>Sara Dhadwal - Priyanga Burford</actor>
      <actor>Tate Connelley - Trader - Charlotte Callaghan</actor>
      <actor>Graduate - Clemmie France Hayhurst</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Harry Lawtey</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ken Leung</actor>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260423230500 +0500" stop="20260424000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Stag</sub-title>
    <desc>A continuation of the story about Tsarina Catherine (Elle Fanning), in which facts mix with satire.After the woman recently tried to kill her husband, Piotr (Nicholas Hoult), and imprisoned all his friends, the relationship between them is not good.Meanwhile, Katarzyna also faces political problems.Wanting to solve them, the ruler becomes famous also outside Russia.During this time, Piotr tries to accept the fact that he lives in his wife's shadow.He devotes himself to fatherhood, takes part in hunting and discovers culinary novelties.Finally, they both decide to take a responsible step - they decide to save their marriage.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <director>Sheree Folkson</director>
      <director>Matthew Moore</director>
      <director>Bert</director>
      <actor>Katarzyna - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Piotr - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Marial - Phoebe Fox</actor>
      <actor>Velementov - Douglas Hodge</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Elizabeth - Belinda Bromilow</actor>
      <actor>Archbishop - Adam Godley</actor>
      <actor>Georgina - Charity Wakefield</actor>
      <actor>Queen Agnes - Grace Molony</actor>
      <actor>Grigor Dymov - Gwilym Lee</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>