<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Travel-Channel-PL">
    <display-name>Travel Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Travel-Channel-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423093500 +0500" stop="20260423100500 +0500">
    <title>Mexico Life 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The creators of the program will follow people looking for their perfect home from the warm waters of Caribbean beaches to the Pacific coast.Most of them dream of constant sun, beautiful beaches and water sports.Some people are looking for the fun nightlife in Mexico, while others are looking for the excellent, traditional cuisine of this region.There are also those who simply dream of living in a secluded and quiet place on the coast.Local real estate agents will help each of them find their place in Mexican paradise.In each episode, specialists will present the program's heroes with numerous offers from the real estate market, both the more expensive ones, but ready to move in, and the cheaper ones, but requiring renovation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E26/28</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423100500 +0500" stop="20260423103500 +0500">
    <title>Mexico Life 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The creators of the program will follow people looking for their perfect home from the warm waters of Caribbean beaches to the Pacific coast.Most of them dream of constant sun, beautiful beaches and water sports.Some people are looking for the fun nightlife in Mexico, while others are looking for the excellent, traditional cuisine of this region.There are also those who simply dream of living in a secluded and quiet place on the coast.Local real estate agents will help each of them find their place in Mexican paradise.In each episode, specialists will present the program's heroes with numerous offers from the real estate market, both the more expensive ones, but ready to move in, and the cheaper ones, but requiring renovation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E27/28</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423103500 +0500" stop="20260423110500 +0500">
    <title>Mexico Life 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The creators of the program will follow people looking for their perfect home from the warm waters of Caribbean beaches to the Pacific coast.Most of them dream of constant sun, beautiful beaches and water sports.Some people are looking for the fun nightlife in Mexico, while others are looking for the excellent, traditional cuisine of this region.There are also those who simply dream of living in a secluded and quiet place on the coast.Local real estate agents will help each of them find their place in Mexican paradise.In each episode, specialists will present the program's heroes with numerous offers from the real estate market, both the more expensive ones, but ready to move in, and the cheaper ones, but requiring renovation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E28</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423110500 +0500" stop="20260423114000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska visits Malaysia.There he meets with members of the Badjao community, which the rest of the world has not yet heard of.According to legends, their ancestors had gills.Currently, these people can stay underwater for several minutes on one breath and dive to a depth of 20-30 meters without any specialized equipment.The Badjao live on boats or in houses built on stilts.They spend their whole lives there, so when they come ashore, they get land sickness.Their children learn to swim before they can even walk.The traveler visits a local healer, Djirajniha, who enjoys great trust and respect.Thanks to it, Martyna Wojciechowska can get to know the extraordinary world of Badjao.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S9E1/9</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423114000 +0500" stop="20260423121000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska visits Mongolia.There, in the inaccessible mountain areas of Altai, the Kazakh minority lives.They are cut off from their roots, but they maintain traditions from 3,000 years ago.The traveler meets a fourteen-year-old girl with strength and courage greater than many men.Petite, charming Akhbota practices falconry every day after school.It's hard to believe that such a delicate girl can communicate with a predatory bird weighing eight kilograms and whose wingspan reaches up to two meters.Martyna Wojciechowska tells a story about true strength, courage and the bond between man and animal.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S9E2/9</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423121000 +0500" stop="20260423124000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska is visiting Japan.He decides to meet the doll woman.So she goes to Tokyo, where she meets a man who is in love with Megumi.Practical Japanese people increasingly replace true love in this way.They even marry artificial women.According to estimates, there are as many as twenty thousand men in the Land of the Rising Sun who have such a doll.Their size, weight and appearance reflect humans.The traveler is looking for answers to the questions whether it is possible to fall in love with a doll and whether it is an image of the future.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S9E3/9</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423124000 +0500" stop="20260423131000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This time, Martyna Wojciechowska moves not only in space, but also in time.He goes to a place that is only thirty kilometers from Santa Cruz - one of the largest, most populated cities in Bolivia.The traveler visits Mennonites living in harsh and wild rural communities.They consciously reject electricity and modern technology.They devote themselves to religion, farming and animal husbandry.They don't do any sports, they don't have access to TV or phones because all of this is prohibited.Their education ends with basic knowledge of arithmetic and the study of the Bible.Viewers will see how Martyna Wojciechowska finds herself in this extraordinary world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S9E4/9</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423131000 +0500" stop="20260423134500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423134500 +0500" stop="20260423141500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423141500 +0500" stop="20260423144500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423144500 +0500" stop="20260423151500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E7</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423151500 +0500" stop="20260423162000 +0500">
    <title>Alaskan Killer Bigfoot</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seventy years ago, Nantinaq forced the inhabitants to flee Portlock, Alaska.A team of daredevils arrives at an abandoned fishing village.What is a 40-day stay in a dangerous wilderness?</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Self - Ash Naderhoff</actor>
      <actor>Self - Keith Seville</actor>
      <actor>Self - D.J. Brewster</actor>
      <actor>Self - Jefferson Davis</actor>
      <actor>Self - Kyle McDowell</actor>
      <actor>Self - Tommy Evans</actor>
      <actor>Self - Ron Morehead</actor>
      <actor>Self - Noah Craig</actor>
      <actor>Self - Alyson Seville</actor>
      <actor>Self - Polly Wirum</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423162000 +0500" stop="20260423172000 +0500">
    <title>Men, Women, Wild</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three couples, husband and wife, mother and father, and a boy and a girl, set off on an extreme expedition.For three weeks they try to survive in the most dangerous places on the planet.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1/6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Pete Sepenuk</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423172000 +0500" stop="20260423175500 +0500">
    <title>Man v Food 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Adam sets off on a journey across the United States to take part in subsequent rounds of timed eating competitions.Adam will take on Badass Burrito in Las Vegas and a 106-centimetre pizza in San Antonio.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E1</episode-num>
    <date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Culinary Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423175500 +0500" stop="20260423183000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sally Mae Hassona grew up in Australia.When she was very young, she started training kickboxing, then football, and in 2012 she became interested in boxing.That's how she got into the amateur league.As a talented player, she won the Golden Gloves Championship.Some time later she became a trainer.Together with her Egyptian husband, they are the parents of two children.They moved to Cairo four years ago.Women's boxing is a completely new phenomenon in this city.Society often cannot accept that women practice this "men's sport".However, Sally Mae Hassona decided to start her own boxing academy: Impact Sports Academy.There he trains girls and boys from poor families.She also hopes that in the future, her students' fighting skills will enable them to defend themselves against violence.Some of Sally's students successfully participate in competitions organized by the federation in Egypt.The woman's children also train, and her son became a boxing champion.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E6/7</episode-num>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423183000 +0500" stop="20260423190500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska once again managed to reach the titular "end of the world", despite restrictions, difficulties in traveling, and the fact that the thirteenth series of the program could have been the unlucky one.During the uncertain time of the pandemic, she showed viewers moving stories that gave hope that miracles can be achieved even in the most difficult circumstances.She produced an extraordinary series of stories from Dubai, Georgia, Kenya, Malawi, Egypt and Romania.Now viewers will learn the behind-the-scenes of all these expeditions.For the host of the program, it is also a sentimental journey - one of the heroines of the reports, Raha Moharrak, just like her, reached for the Crown of the Earth, and in the desert in Dubai, Martyna Wojciechowska met her colleagues from the Dakar Rally: Marek Dąbrowski and Jacek Czachor.In Kenya, she appeared in a music video for a gospel song by Darlan Rukish.However, during filming in Malawi, she refused to eat a roasted mouse.This is just some of the information that will appear in the episode.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E7</episode-num>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423190500 +0500" stop="20260423194000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The program returns to the air after a break.Over the last few months, Martyna Wojciechowska and her team have traveled all over the world to look for inspiring women who will talk about what is currently most important.For some topics, the host had to wait many years, but for the good stuff, it's definitely worth it.The latest season will bring meetings with the oldest and youngest heroines in the history of the show.Viewers will see episodes shot in eight countries and on five continents.However, it is not about records or the number of kilometers traveled.The most important thing is meeting another person, time spent together, intimate conversation, and the truth about the world
The whole world heard about Anja Ringgren Loven in 2016.All because of a photo showing a woman giving water to an extremely exhausted two-year-old who was close to death in a Nigerian village.The boy accused of witchcraft was driven out of his home.He wandered for a long time before help arrived.In Nigeria, they still believe in magic and use it to explain all misfortunes and accidents.People living in poverty and deprived of the opportunity for education may, under the pretext of accusing them of witchcraft, get rid of another person to feed from their home.Martyna Wojciechowska's heroine, Anja, has been active in this country for years.She founded the "Land of Hope" organization, which deals with rescuing and providing a safe haven for children suspected of being associated with evil forces.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E1/8</episode-num>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423194000 +0500" stop="20260423201500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The program returns to the air after a break.Over the last few months, Martyna Wojciechowska and her team have traveled all over the world to look for inspiring women who will talk about what is currently most important.For some topics, the host had to wait many years, but for the good stuff, it's definitely worth it.The latest season will bring meetings with the oldest and youngest heroines in the history of the show.Viewers will see episodes shot in eight countries and on five continents.However, it is not about records or the number of kilometers traveled.The most important thing is meeting another person, time spent together, intimate conversation, and the truth about the world
The camera visits the San Blas archipelago in Panama, famous for its spectacular views.However, it is a paradise that may soon disappear.Sea levels are constantly rising around the islands of the Guna Yala region and they are sinking.The indigenous Guna people live here.They are already being called among the first climate refugees in the world.Activist and educator Kandra leads the fight to save everything important to the community, and is also active in the local congress.He knows a lot about organic farming and teaches others.It cooperates with the Reef2Reef Restoration organization to ensure the restoration of coral reefs.Kandra, the first female diver among the Guna.Martyna Wojciechowska literally immerses herself in her story.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E2/8</episode-num>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423201500 +0500" stop="20260423211500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seattle, a city full of contrasts, is known as both the birthplace of grunge and the headquarters of technology giants, including:Amazon and Microsoft.In the 1990s, it was known for the music of bands such as Nirvana, Pearl Jam, Soundgarden and Alice in Chains.Marcin Prokop will meet the author of a book about Kurt Cobain, visit a photographer who collaborates with important grunge artists and talk to the owner of a music store in the Georgetown district, who will share interesting anecdotes about the Nirvana singer.A key experience will be a visit to the Sub Pop label and a conversation with its founder, Jonathan Poneman, who had a huge impact on the development of the contemporary music scene, promoting bands such as Nirvana and The Shins.The culmination of this trip will be an important conversation for Marcin with Kim Thail, the vocalist of Soundgarden.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5E7/8</episode-num>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423211500 +0500" stop="20260423215000 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes to the USA to explore myths and compare them with reality.It focuses on issues such as stories about Indians and cowboys, UFO mysteries and Stephen King's horror films.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5E8</episode-num>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423215000 +0500" stop="20260423222000 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop sets off overseas once again.According to the stereotype, the United States is a place of endless possibilities, where everyone can fulfill their dreams.In the new season of the program, the host will meet people who have found the recipe for success in life.In this way, he wants to find out whether there is a set of universal rules that guarantee happiness.He will visit, among others, the Skid Row district in Los Angeles, the NASA headquarters in Pasadena, the desert in Utah and a gold mine in Colorado.In each episode, viewers will discover new stories and places.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E1/11</episode-num>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423222000 +0500" stop="20260423230500 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A journey through the most interesting parts of the USA.The guide and main character is Dawid Andres - a driver from Poland who drives a truck every day.Thanks to it, we will see the USA from a different side.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E6/8</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423230500 +0500" stop="20260423235000 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A journey through the most interesting parts of the USA.The guide and main character is Dawid Andres - a driver from Poland who drives a truck every day.Thanks to it, we will see the USA from a different side.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E7/8</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260423235000 +0500" stop="20260424004000 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A journey through the most interesting parts of the USA.The guide and main character is Dawid Andres - a driver from Poland who drives a truck every day.Thanks to it, we will see the USA from a different side.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E8</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424004000 +0500" stop="20260424014000 +0500">
    <title>Luxury embassies</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Holidays in the Maldives mean, above all, the beauty of nature.The ocean delights with the transparency of its azure waters, sandy beaches encourage you to relax on the golden sand, green palm trees enchant with their exotic nature.Traveler Justyna Adamczyk will visit the most exclusive hotels in the world.The price of accommodation in some of them reaches the cost of a mid-range car.Only specialists work in these places;professional designers, cuisine and wine experts.They make sure that guests lack nothing and can fully enjoy their vacation.The host will visit the most luxurious apartments on coral reefs with retractable roofs.He will see a cinema located in the middle of the ocean and a restaurant located six meters below its surface.There is also a wine collection and golf courses watered with desalinated sea water.The expert will also meet the people who designed all these wonders.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424014000 +0500" stop="20260424022500 +0500">
    <title>Luxury embassies</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Holidays in the Maldives mean, above all, the beauty of nature.The ocean delights with the transparency of its azure waters, sandy beaches encourage you to relax on the golden sand, green palm trees enchant with their exotic nature.Traveler Justyna Adamczyk will visit the most exclusive hotels in the world.The price of accommodation in some of them reaches the cost of a mid-range car.Only specialists work in these places;professional designers, cuisine and wine experts.They make sure that guests lack nothing and can fully enjoy their vacation.The host will visit the most luxurious apartments on coral reefs with retractable roofs.He will see a cinema located in the middle of the ocean and a restaurant located six meters below its surface.There is also a wine collection and golf courses watered with desalinated sea water.The expert will also meet the people who designed all these wonders.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E5</episode-num>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424022500 +0500" stop="20260424030000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska once again sets out on a fascinating journey to learn about different aspects of the lives of women living in distant corners of the world.Some of the points of the route in this edition will be India, Senegal, South Korea, South Africa, Israel and Mexico.The program participants will talk about their everyday lives and reveal intimate secrets to the traveler.Some of them will be truly moving.This season, the journalist will look at how the Orthodox Jewish community functions on a daily basis and how they celebrate the joyful holiday of Purim.He will visit a nursing home for women who were once involved in prostitution.Although this profession is legal in Mexico, women are not entitled to any benefits.The traveler will also meet teenage Karolina, who works almost 24 hours a day at a garbage dump, and in South Africa she will meet a girl who dives with sharks.These are just some of the many amazing experiences that await Martyna Wojciechowska
Martyna Wojciechowska's goal is Mexico.This is the country where most disappearances of women occur.Kidnapped or lured, they become part of one of the most profitable businesses - prostitution.The traveler visits the nursing home intended for them.Professional sex work is legal in Mexico, but women who engage in it cannot count on any pension or health benefits.At Casa Xochiquetzal, Martyna Wojciechowska talks to eighteen residents and the director of the home, who fights for them to age with dignity and to experience warmth.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E2/9</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424030000 +0500" stop="20260424033500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska once again sets out on a fascinating journey to learn about different aspects of the lives of women living in distant corners of the world.Some of the points of the route in this edition will be India, Senegal, South Korea, South Africa, Israel and Mexico.The program participants will talk about their everyday lives and reveal intimate secrets to the traveler.Some of them will be truly moving.This season, the journalist will look at how the Orthodox Jewish community functions on a daily basis and how they celebrate the joyful holiday of Purim.He will visit a nursing home for women who were once involved in prostitution.Although this profession is legal in Mexico, women are not entitled to any benefits.The traveler will also meet teenage Karolina, who works almost 24 hours a day at a garbage dump, and in South Africa she will meet a girl who dives with sharks.These are just some of the many amazing experiences that await Martyna Wojciechowska
Martyna Wojciechowska goes to South Africa, where she visits an unusual teenager, Ella Addison.Her greatest passion is diving with sharks.She first jumped into water full of predators when she was five years old.It was her parents, Gail and Mark, who taught the girl how to dive.Together with her godmother - Julie Andersen, the founder of Shark Angels, an organization that saves sharks - they also instilled in Ella their love for the ocean and these animals.The teenager is the voice of the young generation on saving the world.In 2018, as many as 150 million sharks were killed.Traders obtain their fins, which are the basic ingredient of the most expensive soup in the world.They throw the rest into the ocean, leaving the fish to die.Representatives of this species, on the one hand, have the worst reputation of all animals, and on the other hand, they are greatly underestimated.If they became extinct, the ecosystem would be disturbed.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E3/9</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424033500 +0500" stop="20260424041000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska once again sets out on a fascinating journey to learn about different aspects of the lives of women living in distant corners of the world.Some of the points of the route in this edition will be India, Senegal, South Korea, South Africa, Israel and Mexico.The program participants will talk about their everyday lives and reveal intimate secrets to the traveler.Some of them will be truly moving.This season, the journalist will look at how the Orthodox Jewish community functions on a daily basis and how they celebrate the joyful holiday of Purim.He will visit a nursing home for women who were once involved in prostitution.Although this profession is legal in Mexico, women are not entitled to any benefits.The traveler will also meet teenage Karolina, who works almost 24 hours a day at a garbage dump, and in South Africa she will meet a girl who dives with sharks.These are just some of the many amazing experiences that await Martyna Wojciechowska.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E4/9</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424041000 +0500" stop="20260424051000 +0500">
    <title>Alaskan Killer Bigfoot</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seventy years ago, Nantinaq forced the inhabitants to flee Portlock, Alaska.A team of daredevils arrives at an abandoned fishing village.What is a 40-day stay in a dangerous wilderness?</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Self - Ash Naderhoff</actor>
      <actor>Self - Keith Seville</actor>
      <actor>Self - D.J. Brewster</actor>
      <actor>Self - Jefferson Davis</actor>
      <actor>Self - Kyle McDowell</actor>
      <actor>Self - Tommy Evans</actor>
      <actor>Self - Ron Morehead</actor>
      <actor>Self - Noah Craig</actor>
      <actor>Self - Alyson Seville</actor>
      <actor>Self - Polly Wirum</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424051000 +0500" stop="20260424061500 +0500">
    <title>Men, Women, Wild</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three couples, husband and wife, mother and father, and a boy and a girl, set off on an extreme expedition.For three weeks they try to survive in the most dangerous places on the planet.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1/6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Pete Sepenuk</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424061500 +0500" stop="20260424072000 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seattle, a city full of contrasts, is known as both the birthplace of grunge and the headquarters of technology giants, including:Amazon and Microsoft.In the 1990s, it was known for the music of bands such as Nirvana, Pearl Jam, Soundgarden and Alice in Chains.Marcin Prokop will meet the author of a book about Kurt Cobain, visit a photographer who collaborates with important grunge artists and talk to the owner of a music store in the Georgetown district, who will share interesting anecdotes about the Nirvana singer.A key experience will be a visit to the Sub Pop label and a conversation with its founder, Jonathan Poneman, who had a huge impact on the development of the contemporary music scene, promoting bands such as Nirvana and The Shins.The culmination of this trip will be an important conversation for Marcin with Kim Thail, the vocalist of Soundgarden.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5E7/8</episode-num>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424072000 +0500" stop="20260424075500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes to the USA to explore myths and compare them with reality.It focuses on issues such as stories about Indians and cowboys, UFO mysteries and Stephen King's horror films.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5E8</episode-num>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424075500 +0500" stop="20260424090000 +0500">
    <title>Man v Food 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Adam sets off on a journey across the United States to take part in subsequent rounds of timed eating competitions.Adam will take on Badass Burrito in Las Vegas and a 106-centimetre pizza in San Antonio.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E15</episode-num>
    <date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Culinary Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424090000 +0500" stop="20260424093500 +0500">
    <title>Bahamas Life 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Bahamas is a perfect place for an unforgettable and sunny vacation.However, waking up in paradise conditions can be an everyday occurrence.Real estate agents help program participants find a home.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E3/14</episode-num>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424093500 +0500" stop="20260424100500 +0500">
    <title>Bahamas Life 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Bahamas is a perfect place for an unforgettable and sunny vacation.However, waking up in paradise conditions can be an everyday occurrence.Real estate agents help program participants find a home.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E4/14</episode-num>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424100500 +0500" stop="20260424103500 +0500">
    <title>Bahamas Life 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Bahamas is a perfect place for an unforgettable and sunny vacation.However, waking up in paradise conditions can be an everyday occurrence.Real estate agents help program participants find a home.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E5/14</episode-num>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424103500 +0500" stop="20260424110500 +0500">
    <title>Bahamas Life 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Bahamas is a perfect place for an unforgettable and sunny vacation.However, waking up in paradise conditions can be an everyday occurrence.Real estate agents help program participants find a home.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E6/14</episode-num>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424110500 +0500" stop="20260424114000 +0500">
    <title>Baggage Battles 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Every year, passengers traveling around the world lose millions of pieces of luggage.Many of them do not come forward to collect their lost items.Smart Billy Leroy, self-confident Mark Meyer and eccentric husband and wife Laurence and Sally Martin turned lost suitcases into a source of profit.Each of them visits auctions where unclaimed goods, items seized by the police or left at airports are auctioned.Relying on experience and intuition, they try to gain possession of the treasures hidden in the bags.It turns out that they can earn thousands of dollars in this not very complicated way.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E10</episode-num>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424114000 +0500" stop="20260424121000 +0500">
    <title>Baggage Battles 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Every year, passengers traveling around the world lose millions of pieces of luggage.Many of them do not come forward to collect their lost items.Smart Billy Leroy, self-confident Mark Meyer and eccentric husband and wife Laurence and Sally Martin turned lost suitcases into a source of profit.Each of them visits auctions where unclaimed goods, items seized by the police or left at airports are auctioned.Relying on experience and intuition, they try to gain possession of the treasures hidden in the bags.It turns out that they can earn thousands of dollars in this not very complicated way.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E11</episode-num>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424121000 +0500" stop="20260424124000 +0500">
    <title>Baggage Battles 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Every year, passengers traveling around the world lose millions of pieces of luggage.Many of them do not come forward to collect their lost items.Smart Billy Leroy, self-confident Mark Meyer and eccentric husband and wife Laurence and Sally Martin turned lost suitcases into a source of profit.Each of them visits auctions where unclaimed goods, items seized by the police or left at airports are auctioned.Relying on experience and intuition, they try to gain possession of the treasures hidden in the bags.It turns out that they can earn thousands of dollars in this not very complicated way.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E12</episode-num>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424124000 +0500" stop="20260424131000 +0500">
    <title>Baggage Battles 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Every year, passengers traveling around the world lose millions of pieces of luggage.Many of them do not come forward to collect their lost items.Smart Billy Leroy, self-confident Mark Meyer and eccentric husband and wife Laurence and Sally Martin turned lost suitcases into a source of profit.Each of them visits auctions where unclaimed goods, items seized by the police or left at airports are auctioned.Relying on experience and intuition, they try to gain possession of the treasures hidden in the bags.It turns out that they can earn thousands of dollars in this not very complicated way.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E13</episode-num>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424131000 +0500" stop="20260424134500 +0500">
    <title>It's beautiful here</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dorota Szelągowska discovers the delightful corners of Poland.It shows places whose existence was previously known only to the initiated.It proves that you don't have to leave the country to reach paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4/9</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424134500 +0500" stop="20260424141500 +0500">
    <title>It's beautiful here</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dorota Szelągowska discovers the delightful corners of Poland.It shows places whose existence was previously known only to the initiated.It proves that you don't have to leave the country to reach paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5/9</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424141500 +0500" stop="20260424144500 +0500">
    <title>It's beautiful here</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dorota Szelągowska discovers the delightful corners of Poland.It shows places whose existence was previously known only to the initiated.It proves that you don't have to leave the country to reach paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6/9</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424144500 +0500" stop="20260424151500 +0500">
    <title>It's beautiful here</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dorota Szelągowska discovers the delightful corners of Poland.It shows places whose existence was previously known only to the initiated.It proves that you don't have to leave the country to reach paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E7/9</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424151500 +0500" stop="20260424162000 +0500">
    <title>Shocking dishes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jarek Nowak goes to Singapore, a city that provides tourists with many delights and surprises.He will look for the strangest dishes and the most interesting delicacies of Asian cuisine.The tasting will start with bird's nest soup, the main ingredient of which is dried swallow saliva, which has extremely health-promoting properties.The locals consider it a real delicacy, and you have to pay dearly for a portion of the soup.Then Jarek will try sheep brain and shark head, before snacking on durian dessert, the smelliest fruit in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424162000 +0500" stop="20260424172000 +0500">
    <title>Shocking dishes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Each country has its own traditional dishes.Unusual dishes include:baked bats or bee larvae in honey.Jarosław Nowak gets to know the strangest cuisines in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E3/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424172000 +0500" stop="20260424175500 +0500">
    <title>Man v Food</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Adam Richman travels around the United States to face the greatest culinary challenges.It covers the route from Boston to Seattle.He also goes to any other place where he can overeat.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E9</episode-num>
    <date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Culinary Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424175500 +0500" stop="20260424182500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424182500 +0500" stop="20260424185500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424185500 +0500" stop="20260424192500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424192500 +0500" stop="20260424200000 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop goes on a trip to the east coast of the United States.He will visit, among others:Ohio, Cleveland, New York, the White House will watch.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E7</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424200000 +0500" stop="20260424210000 +0500">
    <title>Secrets of the wrecks of the Baltic Sea</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A hospital ship that could not sink under the laws of war.However, the Germans, for unknown reasons, camouflaged the SS Stuttgart;The Americans, while bombing the port of Gdynia during the day, hit the object several times, which immediately burst into flames.Towed out of port, it sank.Many people died unable to get out.After many years, the shipwreck is blown up to clear communication with the port.Among its remains at the bottom of the Baltic Sea lies mazut - heavy fuel oil.Specialists speak openly about a ticking ecological bomb, and experts and a team of divers check to what extent the substance poses a threat to users of Polish beaches.Some of the crew face a life-threatening situation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E3/10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Sambor Wilk</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424210000 +0500" stop="20260424220000 +0500">
    <title>Secrets of the wrecks of the Baltic Sea</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A team of divers is combing the bottom of the Baltic Sea in search of sunken ships.Witnesses of the events, historians and documentarians discover their history and look for answers to troubling questions.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E4/10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Sambor Wilk</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424220000 +0500" stop="20260424230000 +0500">
    <title>Alaskan Killer Bigfoot</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seventy years ago, Nantinaq forced the inhabitants to flee Portlock, Alaska.A team of daredevils arrives at an abandoned fishing village.What is a 40-day stay in a dangerous wilderness?</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Self - Ash Naderhoff</actor>
      <actor>Self - Keith Seville</actor>
      <actor>Self - D.J. Brewster</actor>
      <actor>Self - Jefferson Davis</actor>
      <actor>Self - Kyle McDowell</actor>
      <actor>Self - Tommy Evans</actor>
      <actor>Self - Ron Morehead</actor>
      <actor>Self - Noah Craig</actor>
      <actor>Self - Alyson Seville</actor>
      <actor>Self - Polly Wirum</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260424230000 +0500" stop="20260425000500 +0500">
    <title>Men, Women, Wild</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three couples, husband and wife, mother and father, and a boy and a girl, set off on an extreme expedition.For three weeks they try to survive in the most dangerous places on the planet.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1/6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Pete Sepenuk</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>