<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Travel-Channel-PL">
    <display-name>Travel Channel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Travel-Channel-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506060000 +0500" stop="20260506070000 +0500">
    <title>World weddings</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Wedding customs can vary greatly from country to country.In Sweden, it is unacceptable for any woman to wear a red dress.However, in China there is another interesting custom - a few days before the wedding, the bride must cry in the presence of other women from the family.Anna Szlęzak will go to a Peruvian village in the Andes to observe the local wedding traditions.Local couples live together on a trial basis before officially getting married.This period may last even several years.If the relationship turns out to be unsuccessful, they break up unless they have children.Otherwise, they are obliged to get married.The entire community, without exception, is involved in organizing the celebration.The host will not only learn about the superstitions and customs prevailing here, but will also keep the bride company just before the wedding.She will then attend an Indian wedding reception.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1/2</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506070000 +0500" stop="20260506080500 +0500">
    <title>World weddings</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Wedding customs can vary greatly from country to country.In Sweden, it is unacceptable for any woman to wear a red dress.However, in China there is another interesting custom - a few days before the wedding, the bride must cry in the presence of other women from the family.Anna Szlęzak will go to a Peruvian village in the Andes to observe the local wedding traditions.Local couples live together on a trial basis before officially getting married.This period may last even several years.If the relationship turns out to be unsuccessful, they break up unless they have children.Otherwise, they are obliged to get married.The entire community, without exception, is involved in organizing the celebration.The host will not only learn about the superstitions and customs prevailing here, but will also keep the bride company just before the wedding.She will then attend an Indian wedding reception.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506080500 +0500" stop="20260506090000 +0500">
    <title>Man v Food</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Adam Richman travels around the United States to face the greatest culinary challenges.It covers the route from Boston to Seattle.He also goes to any other place where he can overeat.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E4</episode-num>
    <date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Culinary Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506090000 +0500" stop="20260506093500 +0500">
    <title>Caribbean Life 19</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The fate of families who decided to move to the Caribbean.They need to find a suitable home.In each episode, the characters will visit several properties to fulfill their dream of living in paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E5/14</episode-num>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506093500 +0500" stop="20260506100500 +0500">
    <title>Caribbean Life 19</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The fate of families who decided to move to the Caribbean.They need to find a suitable home.In each episode, the characters will visit several properties to fulfill their dream of living in paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E6/14</episode-num>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506100500 +0500" stop="20260506103500 +0500">
    <title>Caribbean Life 19</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The fate of families who decided to move to the Caribbean.They need to find a suitable home.In each episode, the characters will visit several properties to fulfill their dream of living in paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E7/14</episode-num>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506103500 +0500" stop="20260506110500 +0500">
    <title>Caribbean Life 19</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The fate of families who decided to move to the Caribbean.They need to find a suitable home.In each episode, the characters will visit several properties to fulfill their dream of living in paradise.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E8/14</episode-num>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506110500 +0500" stop="20260506114000 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop sets off overseas once again.According to the stereotype, the United States is a place of endless possibilities, where everyone can fulfill their dreams.In the new season of the program, the host will meet people who have found the recipe for success in life.In this way, he wants to find out whether there is a set of universal rules that guarantee happiness.He will visit, among others, the Skid Row district in Los Angeles, the NASA headquarters in Pasadena, the desert in Utah and a gold mine in Colorado.In each episode, viewers will discover new stories and places
In this episode, Marcin Prokop sets off on a journey to Silicon Valley.But first, he will visit Sausalito, a city called the Venice of America.In this unique place, houses are built on the water, and residents are separated from the bustling San Francisco by a trip over the Golden Gate Bridge.However, in the heart of Silicon Valley there is Stanford University.This prestigious university counts among its graduates, among others, Elon Musk.This is where Han will tell the host about how to create your own company in the center of American technological thought.Marcin Prokop will also meet Jakub Pachocki.This will be a great opportunity to ask one of the creators of ChatGPT a few questions generated by this tool.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E10/11</episode-num>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506114000 +0500" stop="20260506121000 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop sets off overseas once again.According to the stereotype, the United States is a place of endless possibilities, where everyone can fulfill their dreams.In the new season of the program, the host will meet people who have found the recipe for success in life.In this way, he wants to find out whether there is a set of universal rules that guarantee happiness.He will visit, among others, the Skid Row district in Los Angeles, the NASA headquarters in Pasadena, the desert in Utah and a gold mine in Colorado.In each episode, viewers will discover new stories and places
Opened in 1894, Huntsville Prison is an institution where over 580 people lost their lives.Executions of convicts were carried out using an electric chair, which can now be seen as a museum exhibit.David Stacks, a former prison guard, will talk about working there and the emotions that accompany meetings with the most dangerous criminals in America.Jimi Willet, former prison warden and execution supervisor, will reveal whether he ever managed to get used to death.Marcin will also ask him about the impact his job has on his family life.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E11</episode-num>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506121000 +0500" stop="20260506124000 +0500">
    <title>COOL tourists</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rapper Vienio and chef Filip Głodek will go on a trip around European cities.They will not follow popular tourist trails, but will trample their own paths.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1/8</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506124000 +0500" stop="20260506131000 +0500">
    <title>COOL tourists</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rapper Vienio and chef Filip Głodek will go on a trip around European cities.They will not follow popular tourist trails, but will trample their own paths.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2/8</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506131000 +0500" stop="20260506134500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The program returns to the air after a break.Over the last few months, Martyna Wojciechowska and her team have traveled all over the world to look for inspiring women who will talk about what is currently most important.For some topics, the host had to wait many years, but for the good stuff, it's definitely worth it.The latest season will bring meetings with the oldest and youngest heroines in the history of the show.Viewers will see episodes shot in eight countries and on five continents.However, it is not about records or the number of kilometers traveled.The most important thing is meeting another person, time spent together, intimate conversation, and the truth about the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E8</episode-num>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506134500 +0500" stop="20260506142000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will address the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E1/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506142000 +0500" stop="20260506145500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will tackle the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.
For years, the Iban people living in Borneo were considered one of the most terrifying communities in the world.Its members carried out ritual hunts for people.They believed that a warrior who shed blood gained strength and glory.Nowadays, this tradition is no longer cultivated, but its traces still remain in Iban homes.They never got rid of the trophies they won years ago.Martyna Wojciechowska talks to a descendant of bounty hunters.He also takes part in the skull taming ritual.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E2/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506145500 +0500" stop="20260506153000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will tackle the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.
Martyna Wojciechowska talks to Morena Herrera, who fights for women's rights in El Salvador.The country ranks first in terms of the number of murders of women.About 500 such cases are reported annually, with a population of less than 3 million.More than half of the victims of violence do not seek help and do not reveal the truth even to their closest family members.Moreover, El Salvador has one of the most restrictive anti-abortion laws in the world.Termination of pregnancy is always illegal.If a woman loses a child in unclear circumstances, she immediately becomes a suspect.The penalty for her ranges from 2 to 8 years, and if found guilty, she may be imprisoned for 50 years.A doctor can be sentenced to 6 to 12 years for performing an abortion.Anyone who knew about the situation but did not inform the authorities is also complicit.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E3/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506153000 +0500" stop="20260506162000 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dawid Andres will once again take advantage of the opportunity to combine delivering goods with exploring American nature, architecture and culture.With him, viewers will visit, among others:Atlanta and check out the Daytona track.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E4/10</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506162000 +0500" stop="20260506170500 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dawid Andres will once again take advantage of the opportunity to combine delivering goods with exploring American nature, architecture and culture.With him, viewers will visit, among others:Atlanta and check out the Daytona track.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E5/10</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506170500 +0500" stop="20260506175500 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dawid Andres will once again take advantage of the opportunity to combine delivering goods with exploring American nature, architecture and culture.With him, viewers will visit, among others:Atlanta and check out the Daytona track.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E6/10</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506175500 +0500" stop="20260506182500 +0500">
    <title>Taste the world with Pascal</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pascal Brodnicki likes to explore the world through his sense of taste.He loves to prepare various dishes at street stalls, in African villages or on the beach. However, during his culinary journeys it was not always easy for him.Sometimes elephants stole his ingredients.Of course, Pascal couldn't deny himself the pleasure of tasting local delicacies.In Delhi, he stopped for a long time at a paratha stand, in a Zanzibar village he ate rice with coconut, and in Namibia he tried a zebra steak."Taste the world with Pascal" is not only about cooking.The host visited an elephant orphanage in Sri Lanka, fed cheetahs in Africa and climbed a coconut tree.In Bombay he became a teacher and taught Polish to children, and on the coast of Zanzibar he hunted octopus.Everywhere his passion and positive energy attracted crowds of onlookers
The first stop on Pascal's culinary journey is Sri Lanka.The cook visits the Pinawela center - an elephant orphanage.These huge mammals can eat up to 300 kg of food a day and they love carrots.Pascal will prepare a meal for these unusual gourmets.After a busy day, the chef decides to thank his newfound friends and invites them for dinner on the shores of the Indian Ocean.He chooses a quick recipe for chicken curry with the addition of cashew nuts, which are very popular on the island.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E1/8</episode-num>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506182500 +0500" stop="20260506185500 +0500">
    <title>Taste the world with Pascal</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pascal Brodnicki likes to explore the world through his sense of taste.He loves to prepare various dishes at street stalls, in African villages or on the beach. However, during his culinary journeys it was not always easy for him.Sometimes elephants stole his ingredients.Of course, Pascal couldn't deny himself the pleasure of tasting local delicacies.In Delhi, he stopped for a long time at a paratha stand, in a Zanzibar village he ate rice with coconut, and in Namibia he tried a zebra steak."Taste the world with Pascal" is not only about cooking.The host visited an elephant orphanage in Sri Lanka, fed cheetahs in Africa and climbed a coconut tree.In Bombay he became a teacher and taught Polish to children, and on the coast of Zanzibar he hunted octopus.Everywhere his passion and positive energy attracted crowds of onlookers
Pascal continues to explore the flavors of Sri Lanka - a country that is a leader in tea production.The cook decides to learn the secrets of working on the plantation.The appearance of an almost two-meter tall man will cause quite a sensation among the women working there.Pascal will also visit Negombo.The city on the west coast of the island is known mainly for its old market where you can buy various types of fish - from mackerel, through shark, to "flying fish".All fresh, straight from the sea.While exploring the coast, Pascal meets local fishermen.He offers them help, hoping that he will learn the secrets of preparing fish.However, it quickly turns out that he will have to prove himself as a trade fair seller.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2/8</episode-num>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506185500 +0500" stop="20260506192500 +0500">
    <title>Taste the world with Pascal</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pascal Brodnicki likes to explore the world through his sense of taste.He loves to prepare various dishes at street stalls, in African villages or on the beach. However, during his culinary journeys it was not always easy for him.Sometimes elephants stole his ingredients.Of course, Pascal couldn't deny himself the pleasure of tasting local delicacies.In Delhi, he stopped for a long time at a paratha stand, in a Zanzibar village he ate rice with coconut, and in Namibia he tried a zebra steak."Taste the world with Pascal" is not only about cooking.The host visited an elephant orphanage in Sri Lanka, fed cheetahs in Africa and climbed a coconut tree.In Bombay he became a teacher and taught Polish to children, and on the coast of Zanzibar he hunted octopus.Everywhere his passion and positive energy attracted crowds of onlookers
This time Pascal went to Namibia, famous for its cow breeding and delicious beef.The chef grills his favorite steaks here and, as usual, he will do it in an unusual place.This time on the farm where they are kept.tame cheetahs.After meeting the big cats, Pascal sets off north of the country, to Opuwo, where he goes to a supermarket.Here he meets half-naked women from the Himba tribe who are shopping.He also visits the market where he buys a gift for the Herrero tribe - a goat.His gesture wins great acclaim and Pascal is welcomed into the village with an amazing dance.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E3/8</episode-num>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506192500 +0500" stop="20260506200000 +0500">
    <title>Taste the world with Pascal</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pascal Brodnicki likes to explore the world through his sense of taste.He loves to prepare various dishes at street stalls, in African villages or on the beach. However, during his culinary journeys it was not always easy for him.Sometimes elephants stole his ingredients.Of course, Pascal couldn't deny himself the pleasure of tasting local delicacies.In Delhi, he stopped for a long time at a paratha stand, in a Zanzibar village he ate rice with coconut, and in Namibia he tried a zebra steak."Taste the world with Pascal" is not only about cooking.The host visited an elephant orphanage in Sri Lanka, fed cheetahs in Africa and climbed a coconut tree.In Bombay he became a teacher and taught Polish to children, and on the coast of Zanzibar he hunted octopus.Everywhere his passion and positive energy attracted crowds of onlookers
The next stop on the "Taste the World with Pascal" map is India.Pascal will visit Delhi, where he will taste parathas, traditional wheat pancakes, served with green peas, carrots, bananas or cheese at street stalls.At one of the stalls, Pascal will serve passers-by chicken "Indian style" according to his own recipe.The leader will also visit temples where volunteers prepare free meals for pilgrims.In such kitchens, people cook for up to a thousand people.The cook had never cooked on such a scale.Later, Pascal will go to Bombay, where he will look for the perfect fish for his recipe at the fish market.And then he will prepare it in curry sauce, with peppers and coconut milk.A saleswoman at the local market lends him the kitchen.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4/8</episode-num>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Reality Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506200000 +0500" stop="20260506210000 +0500">
    <title>Shocking dishes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jarek Nowak is looking for shocking dishes in Peru.He visits Iquitos - a city located on the Amazon River, to which no land route leads.Looking for extreme taste sensations, he reaches the market.There you can buy products straight from the jungle, such as turtles, crocodiles, fish and worms.Traders also sell magical herbs and unusual potions that can cure various ailments.Later, the host pays a visit to a tribe that eats monkeys, turtles, eggs, intestines with their contents, and spicy Karachama fish soup.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506210000 +0500" stop="20260506220000 +0500">
    <title>Shocking dishes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jarek Nowak goes to Singapore, a city that provides tourists with many delights and surprises.He will look for the strangest dishes and the most interesting delicacies of Asian cuisine.The tasting will start with bird's nest soup, the main ingredient of which is dried swallow saliva, which has extremely health-promoting properties.The locals consider it a real delicacy, and you have to pay dearly for a portion of the soup.Then Jarek will try sheep brain and shark head, before snacking on durian dessert, the smelliest fruit in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506220000 +0500" stop="20260506230000 +0500">
    <title>Indonesia's Best Ever Eats</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A culinary journey to the largest island country in the world.Gourmets will discover the best dishes from five regions of Indonesia, including the area around Lake Toba in Sumatra.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260506230000 +0500" stop="20260507000500 +0500">
    <title>China according to Jarek Nowak</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jarek Nowak, anthropologist and traveler, goes on an expedition through China to rediscover one of the oldest civilizations in the world.The host will take viewers on a walk through the alleys of the Great Wall of China, tasting street food dishes and trekking through the Leaping Dragon Gorge.There will also be interesting attractions, surprising customs and unusual dishes.The traveler will advise you on how to get around, what to do in your free time and how to experience a once-in-a-lifetime adventure.The program is an alternative guide that contains a lot of interesting facts and practical tips for everyone.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507000500 +0500" stop="20260507010500 +0500">
    <title>Moonshiners 11</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Further adventures of producers of illegal alcohol.The demand for their products is growing, which is why this business is becoming more and more dangerous.To expand production, new helpers are needed.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13/21</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Jeremy Schwartz</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Josh Owens</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Ramsey</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Eric Manes</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Tim Smith</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Steve Tickle</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Rogers</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mike Cockrell</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Jim Tom Hedrick</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Chuck Miller</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507010500 +0500" stop="20260507021000 +0500">
    <title>Moonshiners 11</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Further adventures of producers of illegal alcohol.The demand for their products is growing, which is why this business is becoming more and more dangerous.To expand production, new helpers are needed.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14/21</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Jeremy Schwartz</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Josh Owens</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Ramsey</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Eric Manes</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Tim Smith</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Steve Tickle</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Rogers</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mike Cockrell</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Jim Tom Hedrick</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Chuck Miller</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507021000 +0500" stop="20260507024500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Reports showing the stories of women living in Africa, Asia and America.The heroines have different professions and follow different religions.Presenting their fate is only a pretext to show the exoticism, traditions and culture of the countries in which they live.Martyna Wojciechowska, who kept a diary from these extraordinary journeys, experienced their joys and sorrows together with her interlocutors and participated in their everyday activities.This allowed her to understand contrasts and learn about different approaches to femininity.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E5/10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Małgorzata Łupina</director>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507024500 +0500" stop="20260507032000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Reports showing the stories of women living in Africa, Asia and America.The heroines have different professions and follow different religions.Presenting their fate is only a pretext to show the exoticism, traditions and culture of the countries in which they live.Martyna Wojciechowska, who kept a diary from these extraordinary journeys, experienced their joys and sorrows together with her interlocutors and participated in their everyday activities.This allowed her to understand contrasts and learn about different approaches to femininity.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E6/10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Małgorzata Łupina</director>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507032000 +0500" stop="20260507035500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Reports showing the stories of women living in Africa, Asia and America.The heroines have different professions and follow different religions.Presenting their fate is only a pretext to show the exoticism, traditions and culture of the countries in which they live.Martyna Wojciechowska, who kept a diary from these extraordinary journeys, experienced their joys and sorrows together with her interlocutors and participated in their everyday activities.This allowed her to understand contrasts and learn about different approaches to femininity.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E7/10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Małgorzata Łupina</director>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507035500 +0500" stop="20260507045500 +0500">
    <title>Shocking dishes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jarek Nowak is looking for shocking dishes in Peru.He visits Iquitos - a city located on the Amazon River, to which no land route leads.Looking for extreme taste sensations, he reaches the market.There you can buy products straight from the jungle, such as turtles, crocodiles, fish and worms.Traders also sell magical herbs and unusual potions that can cure various ailments.Later, the host pays a visit to a tribe that eats monkeys, turtles, eggs, intestines with their contents, and spicy Karachama fish soup.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507045500 +0500" stop="20260507060000 +0500">
    <title>Shocking dishes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jarek Nowak goes to Singapore, a city that provides tourists with many delights and surprises.He will look for the strangest dishes and the most interesting delicacies of Asian cuisine.The tasting will start with bird's nest soup, the main ingredient of which is dried swallow saliva, which has extremely health-promoting properties.The locals consider it a real delicacy, and you have to pay dearly for a portion of the soup.Then Jarek will try sheep brain and shark head, before snacking on durian dessert, the smelliest fruit in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2/6</episode-num>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507060000 +0500" stop="20260507070000 +0500">
    <title>Moonshiners 11</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Further adventures of producers of illegal alcohol.The demand for their products is growing, which is why this business is becoming more and more dangerous.To expand production, new helpers are needed.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13/21</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Jeremy Schwartz</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Josh Owens</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Ramsey</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Eric Manes</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Tim Smith</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Steve Tickle</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Rogers</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mike Cockrell</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Jim Tom Hedrick</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Chuck Miller</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507070000 +0500" stop="20260507080500 +0500">
    <title>Moonshiners 11</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Further adventures of producers of illegal alcohol.The demand for their products is growing, which is why this business is becoming more and more dangerous.To expand production, new helpers are needed.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14/21</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Jeremy Schwartz</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Josh Owens</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Ramsey</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Eric Manes</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Tim Smith</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Steve Tickle</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mark Rogers</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Mike Cockrell</actor>
      <actor>Self - Moonshiner - Jim Tom Hedrick</actor>
      <actor>Self - Distiller - Chuck Miller</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507080500 +0500" stop="20260507090000 +0500">
    <title>Man v Food</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Adam Richman travels around the United States to face the greatest culinary challenges.It covers the route from Boston to Seattle.He also goes to any other place where he can overeat.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E5</episode-num>
    <date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Culinary Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507090000 +0500" stop="20260507093500 +0500">
    <title>Mexico Life 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The creators of the program follow people looking for their perfect home in Mexico.Most of them dream of constant sun, beautiful beaches and water sports.Some people are looking for an entertaining nightlife, while others are looking for the traditional cuisine of the region.There are also many people who want to live in a secluded and quiet place on the coast.Local real estate agents will help them make a choice and find their own place in Mexican paradise.In each episode, specialists will present the characters with numerous offers from the real estate market, both the more expensive ones, but ready to move in, and the cheaper ones, but requiring renovation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5/28</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507093500 +0500" stop="20260507100500 +0500">
    <title>Mexico Life 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The creators of the program follow people looking for their perfect home in Mexico.Most of them dream of constant sun, beautiful beaches and water sports.Some people are looking for an entertaining nightlife, while others are looking for the traditional cuisine of the region.There are also many people who want to live in a secluded and quiet place on the coast.Local real estate agents will help them make a choice and find their own place in Mexican paradise.In each episode, specialists will present the characters with numerous offers from the real estate market, both the more expensive ones, but ready to move in, and the cheaper ones, but requiring renovation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6/28</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507100500 +0500" stop="20260507103500 +0500">
    <title>Mexico Life 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The creators of the program follow people looking for their perfect home in Mexico.Most of them dream of constant sun, beautiful beaches and water sports.Some people are looking for an entertaining nightlife, while others are looking for the traditional cuisine of the region.There are also many people who want to live in a secluded and quiet place on the coast.Local real estate agents will help them make a choice and find their own place in Mexican paradise.In each episode, specialists will present the characters with numerous offers from the real estate market, both the more expensive ones, but ready to move in, and the cheaper ones, but requiring renovation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E7/28</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507103500 +0500" stop="20260507110500 +0500">
    <title>Mexico Life 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The creators of the program follow people looking for their perfect home in Mexico.Most of them dream of constant sun, beautiful beaches and water sports.Some people are looking for an entertaining nightlife, while others are looking for the traditional cuisine of the region.There are also many people who want to live in a secluded and quiet place on the coast.Local real estate agents will help them make a choice and find their own place in Mexican paradise.In each episode, specialists will present the characters with numerous offers from the real estate market, both the more expensive ones, but ready to move in, and the cheaper ones, but requiring renovation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E8/28</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507110500 +0500" stop="20260507114000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>For Martyna Wojciechowska, the most important value is freedom.During her travels in the ninth season of the program, she decided to show what she means to others - her characters.The Malaysian fish people have cut themselves off from civilization.The Kazakh girl breaks all stereotypes and excels in activities reserved only for men.Pakistani Masarrat Misbah, thanks to her courage, is changing the world, restoring freedom to others.Kalashka Iran Bibi lives according to the centuries-old tradition of his ancestors despite external pressures.In Japan, Martyna Wojciechowska found people free from any prejudices.However, sometimes honest conversations bring further questions - about the price that Bolivian cholitas pay for their independence;about whether jihadist mothers could limit the freedom of their children, and whether Mennonites are making the right choice by consciously deciding on a life limited by rigid rules.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S9E9</episode-num>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507114000 +0500" stop="20260507121000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will address the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E1/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507121000 +0500" stop="20260507124000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will tackle the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.
For years, the Iban people living in Borneo were considered one of the most terrifying communities in the world.Its members carried out ritual hunts for people.They believed that a warrior who shed blood gained strength and glory.Nowadays, this tradition is no longer cultivated, but its traces still remain in Iban homes.They never got rid of the trophies they won years ago.Martyna Wojciechowska talks to a descendant of bounty hunters.He also takes part in the skull taming ritual.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E2/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507124000 +0500" stop="20260507131000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will tackle the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.
Martyna Wojciechowska talks to Morena Herrera, who fights for women's rights in El Salvador.The country ranks first in terms of the number of murders of women.About 500 such cases are reported annually, with a population of less than 3 million.More than half of the victims of violence do not seek help and do not reveal the truth even to their closest family members.Moreover, El Salvador has one of the most restrictive anti-abortion laws in the world.Termination of pregnancy is always illegal.If a woman loses a child in unclear circumstances, she immediately becomes a suspect.The penalty for her ranges from 2 to 8 years, and if found guilty, she may be imprisoned for 50 years.A doctor can be sentenced to 6 to 12 years for performing an abortion.Anyone who knew about the situation but did not inform the authorities is also complicit.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E3/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507131000 +0500" stop="20260507134500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop sets off overseas once again.According to the stereotype, the United States is a place of endless possibilities, where everyone can fulfill their dreams.In the new season of the program, the host will meet people who have found the recipe for success in life.In this way, he wants to find out whether there is a set of universal rules that guarantee happiness.He will visit, among others, the Skid Row district in Los Angeles, the NASA headquarters in Pasadena, the desert in Utah and a gold mine in Colorado.In each episode, viewers will discover new stories and places
There is a place in downtown Los Angeles that tourists and locals alike stay away from.Tens of thousands of people who have become homeless camp every day in the Skid Row district.Pastor Troy runs a center that helps people in crisis of homelessness get back on their feet.Marcin learns the story of a priest who also struggled with a serious life crisis and now devotes all his energy to supporting others.The leader continues his journey to Slab City, a settlement located on the site of a former military base inhabited by those who want to live on their own terms.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E4/11</episode-num>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507134500 +0500" stop="20260507141500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop sets off overseas once again.According to the stereotype, the United States is a place of endless possibilities, where everyone can fulfill their dreams.In the new season of the program, the host will meet people who have found the recipe for success in life.In this way, he wants to find out whether there is a set of universal rules that guarantee happiness.He will visit, among others, the Skid Row district in Los Angeles, the NASA headquarters in Pasadena, the desert in Utah and a gold mine in Colorado.In each episode, viewers will discover new stories and places
Marcin will meet with Carrie, a representative of the Mormon community, to find out what their faith is based on.This church was founded in 1830, and its followers, fleeing from persecution, settled in Utah and founded the city of Salt Lake City.The guide will also take the leader to meet his family.This will be an opportunity to find out whether the controversies that have been stirring up the lifestyle of followers of this religion for years and the myths circulating about it are confirmed in reality.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E5/11</episode-num>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507141500 +0500" stop="20260507144500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop sets off overseas once again.According to the stereotype, the United States is a place of endless possibilities, where everyone can fulfill their dreams.In the new season of the program, the host will meet people who have found the recipe for success in life.In this way, he wants to find out whether there is a set of universal rules that guarantee happiness.He will visit, among others, the Skid Row district in Los Angeles, the NASA headquarters in Pasadena, the desert in Utah and a gold mine in Colorado.In each episode, viewers will discover new stories and places
Marcin Prokop will meet a man who gave up the pursuit of a career and money in favor of a sense of freedom and communion with nature.An American Air Force pilot gave up everything to live in a small truck and constantly travel.The host talks to him about where this idea came from and whether he regrets it.The journalist will also reach Zion National Park.Kim, who works as a guide in this place, will tell Marcin about what being close to nature gives him and why he is guided by the wabi-sabi philosophy.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E6/11</episode-num>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507144500 +0500" stop="20260507151500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Marcin Prokop sets off overseas once again.According to the stereotype, the United States is a place of endless possibilities, where everyone can fulfill their dreams.In the new season of the program, the host will meet people who have found the recipe for success in life.In this way, he wants to find out whether there is a set of universal rules that guarantee happiness.He will visit, among others, the Skid Row district in Los Angeles, the NASA headquarters in Pasadena, the desert in Utah and a gold mine in Colorado.In each episode, viewers will discover new stories and places
The presenter goes to Denver to meet with representatives of the Soldiers of Jesus.They say about themselves that they exist to train faithful disciples, preach the word of God and bear witness to the Gospel among the motorcyclist community.One of the members of the organization, Smoking Mike, tells Marcin about his dark past and the path he had to take to finally find peace and happiness.The leader continues his journey to meet Amberley, who suffered a spinal injury several years earlier as a result of an accident and uses a wheelchair.Thanks to her passion and religion, she found the strength to put her life back together.She is still an active rodeo competitor and horses are her great love.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E7/11</episode-num>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507151500 +0500" stop="20260507162000 +0500">
    <title>Men, Women, Wild</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three couples, husband and wife, mother and father, and a boy and a girl, set off on an extreme expedition.For three weeks they try to survive in the most dangerous places on the planet.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E4/6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Pete Sepenuk</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507162000 +0500" stop="20260507172000 +0500">
    <title>Men, Women, Wild</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three couples, husband and wife, mother and father, and a boy and a girl, set off on an extreme expedition.For three weeks they try to survive in the most dangerous places on the planet.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E5/6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Narrator - Pete Sepenuk</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507172000 +0500" stop="20260507175500 +0500">
    <title>Man v Food</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Adam Richman travels around the United States to face the greatest culinary challenges.It covers the route from Boston to Seattle.He also goes to any other place where he can overeat.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E16</episode-num>
    <date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Culinary Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507175500 +0500" stop="20260507183000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The program returns to the air after a break.Over the last few months, Martyna Wojciechowska and her team have traveled all over the world to look for inspiring women who will talk about what is currently most important.For some topics, the host had to wait many years, but for the good stuff, it's definitely worth it.The latest season will bring meetings with the oldest and youngest heroines in the history of the show.Viewers will see episodes shot in eight countries and on five continents.However, it is not about records or the number of kilometers traveled.The most important thing is meeting another person, time spent together, intimate conversation, and the truth about the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E8</episode-num>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507183000 +0500" stop="20260507190500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will address the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E1/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507190500 +0500" stop="20260507194000 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will tackle the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.
For years, the Iban people living in Borneo were considered one of the most terrifying communities in the world.Its members carried out ritual hunts for people.They believed that a warrior who shed blood gained strength and glory.Nowadays, this tradition is no longer cultivated, but its traces still remain in Iban homes.They never got rid of the trophies they won years ago.Martyna Wojciechowska talks to a descendant of bounty hunters.He also takes part in the skull taming ritual.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E2/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507194000 +0500" stop="20260507201500 +0500">
    <title>Woman at the end of the world</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martyna Wojciechowska has been wandering the world for many years and looking for interesting people who share their unique stories with her.The traveler not only talks about their everyday lives, but also raises important social issues.In the tenth season of the program he will visit, among others:Spitsbergen - the largest island of the Svalbard archipelago, where it is night for a quarter of the year.He will also reach out to the Wodaabe community living in Chad, and in El Salvador he will tackle the difficult issue of restrictive anti-abortion regulations.
Martyna Wojciechowska talks to Morena Herrera, who fights for women's rights in El Salvador.The country ranks first in terms of the number of murders of women.About 500 such cases are reported annually, with a population of less than 3 million.More than half of the victims of violence do not seek help and do not reveal the truth even to their closest family members.Moreover, El Salvador has one of the most restrictive anti-abortion laws in the world.Termination of pregnancy is always illegal.If a woman loses a child in unclear circumstances, she immediately becomes a suspect.The penalty for her ranges from 2 to 8 years, and if found guilty, she may be imprisoned for 50 years.A doctor can be sentenced to 6 to 12 years for performing an abortion.Anyone who knew about the situation but did not inform the authorities is also complicit.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E3/5</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507201500 +0500" stop="20260507211500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>More than 170,000 members of this tribe live on the Navajo Nation reservation.The picturesque areas located in four states were supposed to be an enclave of free Indians.In fact, they often resemble vast ghettos.The history of the Navajo is rich and painful, as Marcin Prokop discovers during a visit to one of the last living cryptographers from this tribe, who fought in the Pacific during World War II.The next hero is Loren Anthony, who grew up in the mountains, living in primitive conditions.As a teenager, he formed a metal band, which allowed him to express generational frustrations.After various life challenges, Loren decided to focus on music, charity work and supporting his community.For many young residents of the reserve, this type of creativity is a way to shout out wrongs and escape from the sad reality.Navajos fight stereotypes, valuing the value of their community and traditions, which encourages them to remain in the difficult areas of the reservation.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5E2/8</episode-num>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507211500 +0500" stop="20260507221500 +0500">
    <title>The Extraordinary States of Procopius</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A three-day UFO festival takes place every year in a small town in Pennsylvania, attracting extraterrestrial civilization enthusiasts from all over America.This place is not accidental, because most reports of encounters with aliens are reported in this area.Although interest in UFOs appears to be waning in favor of technology and artificial intelligence threats, extraterrestrial enthusiasts remain active.They organize and write petitions to the government asking for the disclosure of secret files.Although UFOs are most often associated with Roswell and Area 51, the center of this phenomenon is currently located in a provincial town near Pittsburgh and in Washington state.Marcin Prokop intends to meet with UFO enthusiasts and researchers to assess the evidence for the existence of cryptids and extraterrestrial civilizations.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5E3/8</episode-num>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507221500 +0500" stop="20260507230000 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dawid Andres will once again take advantage of the opportunity to combine delivering goods with exploring American nature, architecture and culture.With him, viewers will visit, among others:Atlanta and check out the Daytona track.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E4/10</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507230000 +0500" stop="20260507234500 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dawid Andres will once again take advantage of the opportunity to combine delivering goods with exploring American nature, architecture and culture.With him, viewers will visit, among others:Atlanta and check out the Daytona track.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E5/10</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Travel-Channel-PL" start="20260507234500 +0500" stop="20260508003500 +0500">
    <title>By truck across the United States</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dawid Andres will once again take advantage of the opportunity to combine delivering goods with exploring American nature, architecture and culture.With him, viewers will visit, among others:Atlanta and check out the Daytona track.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E6/10</episode-num>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Entertainment Program</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>